{"id": "nearwin.S136.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9424, "question_text": "Was Elizabeth Murray a painter?", "trigger_span": [9320, 9372], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S138.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9553, "question_text": "What would you consider complete?", "trigger_span": [9498, 9518], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S30.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2776, "question_text": "What are the negative aspects of this lifestyle?", "trigger_span": [2728, 2774], "answer_text": "Dealing with addiction, severe weather, laws criminalizing homelessness", "answer_span": [2957.0, 3020.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S37.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3022, "question_text": "What is an example of a specific law criminalizing homelessness?", "trigger_span": [2961, 3020], "answer_text": "Laws against sitting on sidewalks, sleeping in your car", "answer_span": [3082.0, 3122.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "starshade.S78.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4239, "question_text": "Why do you call it a flower pedal sharshade?", "trigger_span": [4215, 4237], "answer_text": "If they make the pedals right it gives them a shadow.", "answer_span": [4350.0, 4376.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S85.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4378, "question_text": "How do you make the edges of the petal exactly right?", "trigger_span": [4254, 4289], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S87.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4534, "question_text": "Why does it have to be bigger than a thumb?", "trigger_span": [4512, 4532], "answer_text": "If it holds right in the shadows you can see the planets.", "answer_span": [4693.0, 4726.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "starshade.S89.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4728, "question_text": "Why is it the size of half a football field?", "trigger_span": [4570, 4591], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S13.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 958, "question_text": "Why did the authors view about success and creativity change?", "trigger_span": [817, 858], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S8.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 730, "question_text": "Which network? ", "trigger_span": [710, 728], "answer_text": "the network is just the community on a map ", "answer_span": [857.0, 894.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "cities.S10.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1034, "question_text": "What are African-American and Latino people concerned about?", "trigger_span": [961, 1013], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S12.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1209, "question_text": "why does it seem like a small town?", "trigger_span": [1158, 1207], "answer_text": "They don't venture outside of their part of Baltimore and explore the rest of the city and always see the same people ", "answer_span": [1209.0, 1251.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief", "Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief", "Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief", "Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "cities.S16.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1509, "question_text": "who do they identify with living in DC/Maryland/Virginia? ", "trigger_span": [1439, 1497], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S20.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1666, "question_text": "Why do sports connect the two communities? ", "trigger_span": [1603, 1664], "answer_text": "They have of sports related things and it acts as a bridge to bring different parts of the cities together", "answer_span": [1846.0, 1876.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S93.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5004, "question_text": "Why do the petals unfurl?", "trigger_span": [4943, 4960], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S99.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5172, "question_text": "Why does it flip?", "trigger_span": [5016, 5027], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S33.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2408, "question_text": "What was she throwing?", "trigger_span": [2285, 2306], "answer_text": "she is an archer (using a bow and arrow)", "answer_span": [2555.0, 2562.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S38.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2516, "question_text": "What activity was she doing?", "trigger_span": [2451, 2484], "answer_text": "at the end of practice, one of the archers...", "answer_span": [2555.0, 2562.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S1.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 241, "question_text": "Is there more to map?", "trigger_span": [128, 168], "answer_text": "There's more to map.", "answer_span": [304.0, 356.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Disjunction", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Disjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S1.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 177, "question_text": "Why does the author feel fortunate about that being their first job", "trigger_span": [51, 88], "answer_text": "The author learned a lot from the person they worked with", "answer_span": [177.0, 203.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S5.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 344, "question_text": "Why did the author love looking at paintings from the 1970's? ", "trigger_span": [295, 342], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S7.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 485, "question_text": "What did the painter think of her early works?", "trigger_span": [446, 483], "answer_text": "The painter didn't think they exactly what she wanted them to be ", "answer_span": [582.0, 612.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S9.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 645, "question_text": "what did she want them to be?", "trigger_span": [617, 643], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S11.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 801, "question_text": "which painting did the neighbor take out of the trash", "trigger_span": [748, 789], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S46.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3314, "question_text": "What is excellence then?", "trigger_span": [3262, 3304], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S53.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3497, "question_text": "But what's the point of the constant pursuit if you're not committed to some sort of goal", "trigger_span": [3470, 3495], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S55.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3712, "question_text": "Isn't this just because difference people can place different values on things?", "trigger_span": [3658, 3710], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S57.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3855, "question_text": "What was her admission?", "trigger_span": [3812, 3853], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S59.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4109, "question_text": "Why did he only sign 10 percent of his paintings?", "trigger_span": [4068, 4107], "answer_text": "Perhaps he wasn't satisfied with his works even when other people were", "answer_span": [4246.0, 4306.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "cities.S59.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4472, "question_text": "How does this data display segregation?", "trigger_span": [4437, 4470], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S61.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4707, "question_text": "Why did you choose to do it?", "trigger_span": [4472, 4507], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S67.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4837, "question_text": "What do you mean by \"shake up the seating chart\"?", "trigger_span": [4783, 4822], "answer_text": "looking only at race is a poor proxy for diversity", "answer_span": [5022.0, 5068.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S6.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 465, "question_text": "Is your home life bad?", "trigger_span": [249, 268], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S169.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9525, "question_text": "What side is this person on?", "trigger_span": [9494, 9523], "answer_text": "planning for the future to reduce risks", "answer_span": [9619.0, 9639.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S8.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 755, "question_text": "Do you want to live on the road?", "trigger_span": [495, 541], "answer_text": "She wanted to live and experience life on the road.", "answer_span": [857.0, 882.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Comparison.Similarity", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S93.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5004, "question_text": "Where does the telescope turn?", "trigger_span": [4980, 5002], "answer_text": "Telescope goes 50k kilometers away", "answer_span": [5045.0, 5086.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "starshade.S99.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5172, "question_text": "What do you do with the shadow?", "trigger_span": [5144, 5170], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S33.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2415, "question_text": "What is the relevance of all these categories?", "trigger_span": [2372, 2413], "answer_text": "ESG is the measure of sustainability", "answer_span": [2419.0, 2455.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "investment.S38.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2730, "question_text": "How is ESG used?", "trigger_span": [2461, 2499], "answer_text": "Investors use ESG to determine financial matters", "answer_span": [2736.0, 2776.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct", "Explicit:Contingency.Condition+SpeechAct"]}
{"id": "investment.S40.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2907, "question_text": "How do CEOs factor in sustainability?", "trigger_span": [2892, 2905], "answer_text": "Sustainability leads to innovation and competitive edges", "answer_span": [3024.0, 3069.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner"]}
{"id": "homeless.S12.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1102, "question_text": "Does she want to live a more primal life?", "trigger_span": [1038, 1086], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S167.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9420, "question_text": "What do they both like?", "trigger_span": [9384, 9397], "answer_text": "the comic that is mentioned", "answer_span": [9431.0, 9476.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "investment.S138.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7771, "question_text": "Is the US the world's largest economy?", "trigger_span": [7695, 7729], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S140.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7942, "question_text": "What's ESG?", "trigger_span": [7921, 7924], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S144.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8234, "question_text": "Is the world in danger of these challenges?", "trigger_span": [8034, 8069], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S148.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8406, "question_text": "Is this risk actually overstated?", "trigger_span": [8335, 8387], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S19.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1553, "question_text": "Are they segregated by interests?", "trigger_span": [1381, 1428], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S171.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9708, "question_text": "How are they planning for the future?", "trigger_span": [9619, 9639], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S19.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1070, "question_text": "what gets us to convert success into mastery?", "trigger_span": [981, 1026], "answer_text": "The author thinks that it happens when \"we\" start to see the value of almost getting it right", "answer_span": [1092.0, 1132.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S29.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2107, "question_text": "Did the archer hit the ten ring?", "trigger_span": [2063, 2105], "answer_text": "twice", "answer_span": [2346.0, 2354.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "investment.S142.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8288, "question_text": "What is ESG?", "trigger_span": [7883, 7940], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S149.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8460, "question_text": "What kind of \"sustainability risk\" stuff?", "trigger_span": [8330, 8360], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S165.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9384, "question_text": "What does the person like?", "trigger_span": [9365, 9382], "answer_text": "the comic", "answer_span": [9420.0, 9454.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "homeless.S16.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1360, "question_text": "Did she want to live in olden times?", "trigger_span": [1133, 1181], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S20.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1514, "question_text": "Does she want to experience life the way we used to?", "trigger_span": [1419, 1482], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S10.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1017, "question_text": "Did she want to live like the hobos and travelers?", "trigger_span": [936, 970], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S91.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4910, "question_text": "Why does it start wrapped around a hub?", "trigger_span": [4878, 4908], "answer_text": "It unfurls and the telescope turns around.", "answer_span": [4976.0, 5002.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "cities.S5.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 431, "question_text": "What is the new map?", "trigger_span": [393, 422], "answer_text": "Relationships.", "answer_span": [482.0, 495.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "investment.S158.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9281, "question_text": "How is performance being maintained?", "trigger_span": [9246, 9279], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S7.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 614, "question_text": "How can you map people?", "trigger_span": [584, 612], "answer_text": "Connecting them through relationships.", "answer_span": [681.0, 728.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S35.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2285, "question_text": "Did the archer hit the tiny ring?", "trigger_span": [2159, 2193], "answer_text": "twice", "answer_span": [2346.0, 2354.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "cities.S9.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 846, "question_text": "How would it look?", "trigger_span": [735, 761], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S11.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1147, "question_text": "Is the city segregated?", "trigger_span": [913, 956], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S13.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1339, "question_text": "Are people isolated?", "trigger_span": [1220, 1245], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S44.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3261, "question_text": "How do CEOs view ESGs?", "trigger_span": [3146, 3178], "answer_text": "CEOs are using ESG for leverage", "answer_span": [3269.0, 3309.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "investment.S42.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3142, "question_text": "How does sustainability result in success?", "trigger_span": [2927, 2995], "answer_text": "They are leveraging ESGs", "answer_span": [3322.0, 3387.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"]}
{"id": "investment.S150.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8591, "question_text": "which ones are acceptable expected risks? ", "trigger_span": [8540, 8589], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S152.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8791, "question_text": "what study are you referring to? ", "trigger_span": [8749, 8789], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S154.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8957, "question_text": "sre you saying there is flaw in the study? ", "trigger_span": [8835, 8855], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S156.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9075, "question_text": "Insurance is one way to vaid disaster, but what other thigs should we do to plan for future? ", "trigger_span": [8992, 9038], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S160.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9246, "question_text": "how is investing sustainability the same is insurance? ", "trigger_span": [9078, 9102], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S48.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2742, "question_text": "What inspiration did he take", "trigger_span": [2709, 2724], "answer_text": "it is a solar eclipse", "answer_span": [2863.0, 2899.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S110.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8014, "question_text": "What do you know?", "trigger_span": [7971, 8012], "answer_text": "We thrive when we focus on our successful products", "answer_span": [8027.0, 8073.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S117.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8255, "question_text": "What do the Navajo have to do with anything?", "trigger_span": [8149, 8163], "answer_text": "Gives companies a way out but also a reason to keep working", "answer_span": [8322.0, 8359.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Implicit:Contingency.Purpose.Arg2-as-goal"]}
{"id": "investment.S164.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9365, "question_text": "what if you don't create a better world, but harm the existing one? ", "trigger_span": [9325, 9349], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S97.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5212, "question_text": "Is it the sun?", "trigger_span": [5172, 5201], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S102.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5262, "question_text": "What makes it not science fiction?", "trigger_span": [5234, 5260], "answer_text": "It was tested out last summer. ", "answer_span": [5321.0, 5363.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "starshade.S104.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5399, "question_text": "What exactly did you test?", "trigger_span": [5326, 5359], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S106.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5457, "question_text": "How big would a full scale shade be?", "trigger_span": [5425, 5455], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S108.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5537, "question_text": "What do the petals look like?", "trigger_span": [5507, 5535], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan", "AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan", "AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S73.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4752, "question_text": "What does ESG mean?", "trigger_span": [4633, 4687], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S119.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8404, "question_text": "What else does it do?", "trigger_span": [8370, 8402], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S121.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8479, "question_text": "Why are masters experts?", "trigger_span": [8436, 8477], "answer_text": "Masters are experts because they realize there is no end", "answer_span": [8508.0, 8536.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S123.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8538, "question_text": "What comes afterward?", "trigger_span": [8521, 8536], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S125.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8749, "question_text": "What does this story have to do with anything?", "trigger_span": [8703, 8747], "answer_text": "You keep building off ideas", "answer_span": [9083.0, 9118.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S131.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9040, "question_text": "What does this story have to do with anything?", "trigger_span": [8974, 9023], "answer_text": "You must continue to build yourself", "answer_span": [9083.0, 9118.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S48.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3388, "question_text": "How are companies using ESGs?", "trigger_span": [3322, 3355], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S52.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3532, "question_text": "What do the applications have to do with anything?", "trigger_span": [3454, 3503], "answer_text": "More mobile workplace and lower real estate footprint", "answer_span": [3639.0, 3681.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "AltLex:Hypophora", "AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S134.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9190, "question_text": "What do you mean by former self?", "trigger_span": [9120, 9156], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S131.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9040, "question_text": "Why are there enough visualization techniques.", "trigger_span": [8770, 8801], "answer_text": "Unfinished paths require more.", "answer_span": [9040.0, 9076.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Implicit:Contingency.Purpose.Arg2-as-goal"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S125.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8749, "question_text": "Why did his coach tell him that?", "trigger_span": [8590, 8615], "answer_text": "Because they are not sufficient.", "answer_span": [9077.0, 9082.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Implicit:Contingency.Purpose.Arg2-as-goal"]}
{"id": "starshade.S112.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5652, "question_text": "How long did it take them to build the petals?", "trigger_span": [5537, 5588], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S116.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5791, "question_text": "Do they rotate clockwise or counterclockwise? ", "trigger_span": [5652, 5690], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S62.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4424, "question_text": "What was the bet?", "trigger_span": [4125, 4148], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S69.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4513, "question_text": "Are they isolated cases?", "trigger_span": [4457, 4487], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S71.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4633, "question_text": "How well do these companies do financially?", "trigger_span": [4516, 4591], "answer_text": "Some of these companies do better than others; the best. ", "answer_span": [4858.0, 4908.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "cities.S6.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 461, "question_text": "what kind of map is it?", "trigger_span": [431, 459], "answer_text": "This is a map that shows relationships of people in this writers hometown ", "answer_span": [471.0, 525.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "homeless.S14.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1414, "question_text": "Are hobos still around?", "trigger_span": [1060, 1100], "answer_text": "Their predecessors still travel around", "answer_span": [1414.0, 1453.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S21.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1635, "question_text": "Where are they going?", "trigger_span": [1522, 1545], "answer_text": "Some of them are going no where in particular ", "answer_span": [1865.0, 1903.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "homeless.S23.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1905, "question_text": "How many \"Travelers\" are there?", "trigger_span": [1758, 1772], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S44.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2544, "question_text": "What are they working on?", "trigger_span": [2414, 2435], "answer_text": "that someone took inspiration from an eclipse", "answer_span": [2713.0, 2740.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S35.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2859, "question_text": "what can be done to reduce barriers", "trigger_span": [2779, 2808], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S2.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 205, "question_text": "Why did you learn?", "trigger_span": [177, 203], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S6.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 424, "question_text": "Tll me about the motifs what are they? ", "trigger_span": [344, 379], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S43.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2398, "question_text": "How far away can a planet be seen?", "trigger_span": [2304, 2321], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S45.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2612, "question_text": "What is that method to detect an Earth-like planet?", "trigger_span": [2561, 2591], "answer_text": "Shielding the bright star like an eclipse does with the sun is that method.", "answer_span": [2713.0, 2740.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S67.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3524, "question_text": "What would we build the screen from?", "trigger_span": [3328, 3346], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S2.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 267, "question_text": "How is the world changing?", "trigger_span": [75, 92], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S27.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2370, "question_text": "What are their political views? ", "trigger_span": [2253, 2293], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S29.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2655, "question_text": "How do local communities feel about them scavenging?", "trigger_span": [2484, 2534], "answer_text": "There are many laws that can get them in trouble ", "answer_span": [2957.0, 3020.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S35.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2776, "question_text": "What are the dangers?", "trigger_span": [2739, 2774], "answer_text": "They can be injured or killed by the fright trains that they ride", "answer_span": [2850.0, 2901.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S2.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 386, "question_text": "who maps out cities", "trigger_span": [342, 384], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S6.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 431, "question_text": "Why are they ignoring it then?", "trigger_span": [398, 416], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S8.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 625, "question_text": "How can they influence sustainability?", "trigger_span": [557, 623], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S10.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 802, "question_text": "What is sustainable investing?", "trigger_span": [708, 729], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S12.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 882, "question_text": "Explain sustainable investing to me?", "trigger_span": [860, 880], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S16.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1170, "question_text": "How should we deal with these problems?", "trigger_span": [1020, 1081], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S20.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1320, "question_text": "How are they relevant?", "trigger_span": [1280, 1299], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S78.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5588, "question_text": "So we should always strive for discovering new things?", "trigger_span": [5578, 5586], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S85.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5802, "question_text": "How do we see this more clearly?", "trigger_span": [5729, 5754], "answer_text": "We would see it more clearly because of the Dunning-Kruger effect.", "answer_span": [5818.0, 5839.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S52.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2788, "question_text": "Is a solar eclipse bright?", "trigger_span": [2764, 2786], "answer_text": "that the mon has moved to block out the light", "answer_span": [2828.0, 2859.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S1.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 223, "question_text": "What is the change?", "trigger_span": [196, 221], "answer_text": "environmental and social issues", "answer_span": [327.0, 358.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S5.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 385, "question_text": "Are those things important?", "trigger_span": [290, 320], "answer_text": "that iit is reckless to ignore these things", "answer_span": [398.0, 429.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S20.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1134, "question_text": "What is the value of a near win?", "trigger_span": [1070, 1100], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S145.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8406, "question_text": "how can you plan for an uncertain future? ", "trigger_span": [8188, 8233], "answer_text": "no action is riskier, so what actions are safest? ", "answer_span": [8643.0, 8672.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "starshade.S40.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2203, "question_text": "how far is the light?", "trigger_span": [2167, 2186], "answer_text": "very bright images wash out the planet", "answer_span": [2255.0, 2292.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S42.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2372, "question_text": "How do we fix the bright light?", "trigger_span": [2337, 2370], "answer_text": "they are working on something cool", "answer_span": [2425.0, 2463.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S74.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5651, "question_text": "What kind of relationships between people are most important?", "trigger_span": [5581, 5619], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S65.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4614, "question_text": "Why is it incomplete?", "trigger_span": [4572, 4585], "answer_text": "about the old testament on the sistene chapel.", "answer_span": [4773.0, 4812.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S70.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4814, "question_text": "Why did he implore that?", "trigger_span": [4736, 4757], "answer_text": "About mastery being reaching", "answer_span": [4906.0, 4938.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S72.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4958, "question_text": "How is the mastery reaching?", "trigger_span": [4912, 4938], "answer_text": "it is about sacrificing your craft", "answer_span": [5089.0, 5139.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "AltLex:Expansion.Substitution.Arg1-as-subst"]}
{"id": "investment.S7.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 489, "question_text": "How can it jeopordize the future", "trigger_span": [448, 469], "answer_text": "investors and pension funds", "answer_span": [625.0, 663.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S9.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 693, "question_text": "How does it rest with them?", "trigger_span": [665, 691], "answer_text": "less complicated than you think", "answer_span": [733.0, 764.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S11.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 842, "question_text": "How is it important", "trigger_span": [806, 825], "answer_text": "that the population will be growing and aging", "answer_span": [892.0, 932.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S13.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1017, "question_text": "Will the number continue to grow", "trigger_span": [979, 1015], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S48.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3725, "question_text": "What's the most popular kind of music in Rio De Janeiro?", "trigger_span": [3653, 3677], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S115.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8014, "question_text": "Should you trust your gut?", "trigger_span": [7982, 7996], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S74.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5141, "question_text": "How do you craft your career?", "trigger_span": [5119, 5139], "answer_text": "that the triumphs are the result of grand achievement", "answer_span": [5333.0, 5366.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S76.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5368, "question_text": "What are the achievements", "trigger_span": [5349, 5366], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S80.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5465, "question_text": "What is the leading edge", "trigger_span": [5443, 5463], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S84.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5626, "question_text": "How does he compose", "trigger_span": [5603, 5624], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S1.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 142, "question_text": "How many planets are there?", "trigger_span": [108, 140], "answer_text": "There are as many planets as there are stars.", "answer_span": [477.0, 514.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S5.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 448, "question_text": "How much progress has been made on the technology?", "trigger_span": [371, 392], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S19.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1246, "question_text": "Are environmental and social issues important", "trigger_span": [1193, 1224], "answer_text": "not to bury our heads in the sand", "answer_span": [1421.0, 1447.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S29.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2698, "question_text": "what can be done to move communities closer", "trigger_span": [2568, 2598], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S7.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 658, "question_text": "Are any of these Earth-like planets close to Earth?", "trigger_span": [546, 589], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S9.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 747, "question_text": "Are there plans to directly identify them?", "trigger_span": [664, 693], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S11.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 986, "question_text": "Where did Voyager go after leaving our solar system?", "trigger_span": [832, 856], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S13.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1030, "question_text": "Have we attempted it before?", "trigger_span": [986, 1011], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S19.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1226, "question_text": "Where is the Hubble Space Telescope currently?", "trigger_span": [1121, 1153], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S107.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7733, "question_text": "What was the high score before Jackie?", "trigger_span": [7681, 7731], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S109.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7927, "question_text": "How can we manufacture a near win?", "trigger_span": [7876, 7925], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S8.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 559, "question_text": "What was her response?", "trigger_span": [435, 483], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S10.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 774, "question_text": "What was her mark, comments are to vague. ", "trigger_span": [672, 695], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S12.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 860, "question_text": "How did your veiw change, from what to what? ", "trigger_span": [817, 858], "answer_text": "sucess is short term celebrate the creativity long term", "answer_span": [901.0, 956.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S16.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1027, "question_text": "why would you think success is a moment? ", "trigger_span": [876, 896], "answer_text": "almost winning is now the standard? Really? ", "answer_span": [1104.0, 1132.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S33.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2070, "question_text": "Are the stars bright?", "trigger_span": [1993, 2018], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S38.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2141, "question_text": "When will we see the red circle?", "trigger_span": [2094, 2111], "answer_text": "that the light is defracting from the star", "answer_span": [2163.0, 2201.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "cities.S25.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2135, "question_text": "how is the media bringing communities closer?", "trigger_span": [2054, 2069], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S27.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2379, "question_text": "why is one group dominating? How does it harm all others?", "trigger_span": [2139, 2180], "answer_text": "gentrification old vs new ", "answer_span": [2639.0, 2673.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "AltLex:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S73.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5051, "question_text": "Were any other artists reaching and never finding mastery?", "trigger_span": [4912, 4938], "answer_text": "Explorer Saunders supports the view of struggling to improve without merely succeeding.", "answer_span": [5309.0, 5366.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S75.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5211, "question_text": "Doesn't this provide a slanted view since many people are very skilled and practical?", "trigger_span": [5051, 5094], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S77.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5417, "question_text": "Is it mastery if you don't accomplish goals?", "trigger_span": [5393, 5415], "answer_text": "Pushing harder leads to higher skills and that is part of mastery.", "answer_span": [5650.0, 5684.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S87.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5953, "question_text": "How does Dunning-Kruger effect work?", "trigger_span": [5818, 5839], "answer_text": "A near win is more important then success, as it pushes us harder to reach the end goal, thus making us learn more in the process.", "answer_span": [6027.0, 6049.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "starshade.S51.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2764, "question_text": "What space telescope did Lyman Spitzer inspire?", "trigger_span": [2638, 2686], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S65.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4929, "question_text": "What is a better proxy for diversity than race?", "trigger_span": [4886, 4927], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S70.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5252, "question_text": "What are those problems which can be addressed by more diversity?", "trigger_span": [5141, 5194], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S72.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5447, "question_text": "What problems require such new ways to think about diversity?", "trigger_span": [5287, 5338], "answer_text": "This is a high level look at solving unspecified, but real problems. Seems like TED talk nonsense.", "answer_span": [5766.0, 5819.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S93.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6780, "question_text": "Can this near win phenomenon be applied to anything else?", "trigger_span": [6538, 6555], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S99.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6964, "question_text": "How do we see our goals?", "trigger_span": [6953, 6962], "answer_text": "The near win phenomenon puts our goals closer to us. ", "answer_span": [7000.0, 7028.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S33.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2831, "question_text": "What aspects are far from idyllic?", "trigger_span": [2723, 2774], "answer_text": "There is addiction and other things that could get you killed.", "answer_span": [2831.0, 2892.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "homeless.S38.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3154, "question_text": "In which cities?", "trigger_span": [3045, 3099], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S40.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3233, "question_text": "How do you know?", "trigger_span": [3209, 3232], "answer_text": "They have seen people arrested or ticketed.", "answer_span": [3241.0, 3300.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S62.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4524, "question_text": "Who is this friend mentioned in the passage?", "trigger_span": [4416, 4426], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S69.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4680, "question_text": "Is the editor or author of those works famous?", "trigger_span": [4524, 4563], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S71.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4912, "question_text": "Is there other symbolism in Michaelangelo's works?", "trigger_span": [4852, 4894], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S40.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3168, "question_text": "What does Rio de Janerio have to do with this?", "trigger_span": [3131, 3166], "answer_text": "It's different from San Francisco.", "answer_span": [3326.0, 3355.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "cities.S42.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3405, "question_text": "How are Rio de Janeiro and San Francisco different?", "trigger_span": [3383, 3403], "answer_text": "The people get along even though they are different.", "answer_span": [3580.0, 3629.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S128.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7421, "question_text": "Can anyone else drive the efforts of sustainability? ", "trigger_span": [7335, 7394], "answer_text": "The ones with the money", "answer_span": [7451.0, 7470.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Q/A"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Q/A"]}
{"id": "homeless.S42.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3483, "question_text": "Why would they choose that lifestyle?", "trigger_span": [3378, 3431], "answer_text": "People want to be free.", "answer_span": [3702.0, 3709.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "homeless.S44.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3702, "question_text": "What word?", "trigger_span": [3658, 3700], "answer_text": "they want to be free", "answer_span": [3702.0, 3709.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "homeless.S46.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3826, "question_text": "How can we be assured dignity?", "trigger_span": [3744, 3774], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S48.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3982, "question_text": "Why do they choose rebellion?", "trigger_span": [3971, 3980], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S30.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2859, "question_text": "Why is the LGBT community not getting along with the geek community?", "trigger_span": [2761, 2803], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S52.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3882, "question_text": "What kind of stand-up comedians are popular?", "trigger_span": [3790, 3805], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S30.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2285, "question_text": "Did the archer hit the target?", "trigger_span": [1923, 1948], "answer_text": "Yes, she hit the target.", "answer_span": [2285.0, 2306.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S37.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2486, "question_text": "Did she hit any more tens?", "trigger_span": [2451, 2484], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S39.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2626, "question_text": "Were all of the archers exhausted?", "trigger_span": [2544, 2575], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S41.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2739, "question_text": "What did the archer do next?", "trigger_span": [2626, 2656], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S23.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1952, "question_text": "how would you find more connectivity?", "trigger_span": [1916, 1950], "answer_text": "offered up the media in Baltimore as further connections ", "answer_span": [2074.0, 2116.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "cities.S33.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2880, "question_text": "Why don't the LGBT and geek communities get along?", "trigger_span": [2779, 2827], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S38.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3043, "question_text": "What is the photo of?", "trigger_span": [2952, 2962], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S94.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6964, "question_text": "Are they addicted to playing?", "trigger_span": [6705, 6741], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S101.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7157, "question_text": "How would you describe a great day, tomorrow?", "trigger_span": [7064, 7110], "answer_text": "A great day tomorrow will be described with more clarity and detail.", "answer_span": [7225.0, 7269.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S103.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7305, "question_text": "Does a near win improve self esteem?", "trigger_span": [7283, 7303], "answer_text": "It improves drive and determination.", "answer_span": [7614.0, 7661.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S105.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7505, "question_text": "Did Jackie feel like a failure?", "trigger_span": [7404, 7460], "answer_text": "It made her feel more determined to succeed.", "answer_span": [7542.0, 7574.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"]}
{"id": "investment.S17.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1320, "question_text": "What happens if we do not reduce emissions?", "trigger_span": [1091, 1147], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S22.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1497, "question_text": "Will there be consequences for burying our heads in the sand?", "trigger_span": [1472, 1495], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S24.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1617, "question_text": "What are the investment rules?", "trigger_span": [1561, 1615], "answer_text": "Investers look at different aspects of a company to decide if they want to invest.", "answer_span": [1673.0, 1697.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous"]}
{"id": "investment.S26.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1826, "question_text": "Is it very risky?", "trigger_span": [1704, 1753], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S107.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6425, "question_text": "What is the historical track record for ESG relted investments? Is this a fad or something which will demonstrate itself long term? ", "trigger_span": [6395, 6412], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S43.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3023, "question_text": "Why is it so rare in American culture?", "trigger_span": [2739, 2771], "answer_text": "It's very difficult so not many people reach that level.", "answer_span": [3212.0, 3250.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast", "Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S45.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3144, "question_text": "How long did they stay for?", "trigger_span": [3023, 3035], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S51.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3314, "question_text": "What else besides excellence is involved with mastery?", "trigger_span": [3262, 3304], "answer_text": "Mastery is not just focused on achieving one thing, but trying to constantly improve yourself.", "answer_span": [3449.0, 3495.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "starshade.S33.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2070, "question_text": "Who is present in this passage?", "trigger_span": [1689, 1700], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S38.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2141, "question_text": "Why do we want to see it?", "trigger_span": [2113, 2139], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S40.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2203, "question_text": "Will we see the planet?", "trigger_span": [2152, 2161], "answer_text": "Maybe, if we do something about the light.", "answer_span": [2323.0, 2370.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "investment.S36.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2415, "question_text": "Does the board and investors punish companies for violations?", "trigger_span": [2287, 2351], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S26.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2208, "question_text": "Is it better to be homeless and a nomad vs staying in one place?", "trigger_span": [2199, 2206], "answer_text": "Eating out of garbage cans is freedom?", "answer_span": [2484.0, 2534.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner"]}
{"id": "homeless.S28.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2551, "question_text": "Is thre hope for these nomads to level up?", "trigger_span": [2370, 2389], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S42.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2372, "question_text": "How do we get rid of the light?", "trigger_span": [2323, 2370], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S44.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2544, "question_text": "What technology is the coolest?", "trigger_span": [2535, 2542], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S48.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2742, "question_text": "How did the eclipse inspire Spitzer?", "trigger_span": [2701, 2740], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S52.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2788, "question_text": "How does the eclipse help?", "trigger_span": [2764, 2786], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S1.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 223, "question_text": "How is the world changing?", "trigger_span": [71, 92], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S105.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6351, "question_text": "If pensions are 'integrating ESG' accross their entre funds - doesn't that increase their long term risk due to reduced diversification overall? ", "trigger_span": [6259, 6270], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S44.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3571, "question_text": "What is TEDxRio?", "trigger_span": [3499, 3506], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S32.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2709, "question_text": "Is music art better that a roof and security?", "trigger_span": [2575, 2622], "answer_text": "Mnay this are far from ideal", "answer_span": [2723.0, 2774.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "homeless.S36.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2831, "question_text": "what does one lose", "trigger_span": [2776, 2807], "answer_text": "being homeless is considered criminal", "answer_span": [2957.0, 3010.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S14.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1553, "question_text": "Do you want to meet new people", "trigger_span": [1209, 1251], "answer_text": "Do you like the individuality or the connectivity more?", "answer_span": [1585.0, 1636.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "cities.S21.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1763, "question_text": "Is sport the only connector?", "trigger_span": [1688, 1761], "answer_text": "the only connector sports and one company", "answer_span": [1861.0, 1876.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S17.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1514, "question_text": "Where can we see these color photographs?", "trigger_span": [1234, 1264], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S22.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1758, "question_text": "Are today's nomads there by choice or is the economy to blame?", "trigger_span": [1571, 1592], "answer_text": "What can be done to help them?", "answer_span": [1905.0, 1947.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "homeless.S24.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2013, "question_text": "Whst adventure do they find?", "trigger_span": [1868, 1903], "answer_text": "they feel liberated and free", "answer_span": [2128.0, 2194.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S132.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7496, "question_text": "How much money?", "trigger_span": [7451, 7491], "answer_text": "global market is at 55 trillion dolars", "answer_span": [7528.0, 7576.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "starshade.S30.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1965, "question_text": "How far away are we now?", "trigger_span": [1889, 1912], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S37.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2113, "question_text": "Is the planet visible at all anymore?", "trigger_span": [2026, 2068], "answer_text": "It could be visible, but is very difficult to see.", "answer_span": [2141.0, 2161.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S39.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2163, "question_text": "What are some ways to see a dim planet like that?", "trigger_span": [2120, 2139], "answer_text": "Overcoming the brightness of the star is the way to see the planet.", "answer_span": [2334.0, 2370.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S41.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2301, "question_text": "Can other methods be used to detect the planet?", "trigger_span": [2278, 2299], "answer_text": "Light from the star needs to be blocked out to see the planet.", "answer_span": [2375.0, 2396.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "cities.S37.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2917, "question_text": "What does it lead to?", "trigger_span": [2887, 2915], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S118.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6983, "question_text": "So did you stay working there when it was so tough?", "trigger_span": [6863, 6891], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S120.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7061, "question_text": "What needs clarifying?", "trigger_span": [7024, 7048], "answer_text": "That companies are not obligated to do it all.", "answer_span": [7144.0, 7190.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S12.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1302, "question_text": "Is there a way to speed up the comfort period?", "trigger_span": [1232, 1258], "answer_text": "doesn't matter how strong the prosthetic is", "answer_span": [1561.0, 1617.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession+SpeechAct.Arg2-as-denier+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession+SpeechAct.Arg2-as-denier+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S16.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1428, "question_text": "Is there a new method that could be used?", "trigger_span": [1334, 1356], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S51.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3864, "question_text": "What is the most popular kind of music there?", "trigger_span": [3731, 3785], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S17.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1134, "question_text": "How do we value the gift of a near win?", "trigger_span": [1092, 1132], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S22.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1335, "question_text": "What did you see the archers do?", "trigger_span": [1195, 1228], "answer_text": "He saw one eating ice cream while holding arrows and others saying numbers.", "answer_span": [1612.0, 1656.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S24.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1608, "question_text": "Did you see the archer's paradox?", "trigger_span": [1335, 1381], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S26.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1848, "question_text": "Why were they speaking numbers?", "trigger_span": [1795, 1846], "answer_text": "They were saying the degree numbers they needed for positioning.", "answer_span": [1848.0, 1877.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous", "Explicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S28.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2039, "question_text": "What did she do next?", "trigger_span": [1923, 1948], "answer_text": "Her next arrow missed the target.", "answer_span": [2369.0, 2406.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "investment.S9.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 693, "question_text": "How can institutional investors influence sustainability?", "trigger_span": [548, 623], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S11.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 842, "question_text": "Why is sustainable investing so important?", "trigger_span": [806, 840], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S13.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1017, "question_text": "What kind of problems will the growing population cause?", "trigger_span": [979, 1015], "answer_text": "We will consume natural resources faster and faster.", "answer_span": [1017.0, 1052.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S19.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1246, "question_text": "What else is there?", "trigger_span": [1226, 1244], "answer_text": "There are also economic issues.", "answer_span": [1246.0, 1269.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S25.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2276, "question_text": "How can you get them to the masses?", "trigger_span": [1933, 1966], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S32.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2220, "question_text": "Did the archer hit the ten ring?", "trigger_span": [2072, 2105], "answer_text": "The archer hit 7, 9 and then two tens.", "answer_span": [2301.0, 2349.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S36.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2408, "question_text": "What did she do after she missed the target?", "trigger_span": [2380, 2406], "answer_text": "She kept practicing at her target for the next three hours.", "answer_span": [2451.0, 2484.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S10.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1054, "question_text": "Could make the sockets not painful?", "trigger_span": [1002, 1022], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S28.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2002, "question_text": "Will that improve investers accuracy and returns?", "trigger_span": [1961, 2000], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S32.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2283, "question_text": "Are companies very environmentally conscious?", "trigger_span": [2023, 2082], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S70.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4814, "question_text": "How does mastery relate to not finishing things?", "trigger_span": [4654, 4678], "answer_text": "Mastery comes from trying for a goal, not reaching the goal.", "answer_span": [4912.0, 4956.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "AltLex:Expansion.Substitution.Arg1-as-subst"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S72.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4958, "question_text": "How does reaching help mastery?", "trigger_span": [4912, 4938], "answer_text": "Mastery comes from wanting to bridge a gap in your ability.", "answer_span": [4988.0, 5002.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S74.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5141, "question_text": "Crafting your career is bad?", "trigger_span": [5099, 5139], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S76.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5368, "question_text": "What are Saunders' triumphs the result of?", "trigger_span": [5322, 5346], "answer_text": "The motivation he got from almost achieving his goals, but failing.", "answer_span": [5379.0, 5415.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S80.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5465, "question_text": "What does the author mean by \"leading edge?\"", "trigger_span": [5451, 5463], "answer_text": "It might mean the things we will achieve in the future.", "answer_span": [5563.0, 5586.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S7.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 489, "question_text": "What things are investors ignoring?", "trigger_span": [393, 429], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S85.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4378, "question_text": "what does the shadow look like?", "trigger_span": [4350, 4376], "answer_text": "10 billion times dimmer", "answer_span": [4389.0, 4431.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S72.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4720, "question_text": "What does ESG performance mean? ", "trigger_span": [4672, 4687], "answer_text": "While not fully explained - ESG pervoemance is clearly related to overall environmental sustainability and represents some form of ranking system. ", "answer_span": [4888.0, 4908.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "investment.S74.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4826, "question_text": "What is the purpose of the MSCI World index and what data from it is relevant to this discussion? ", "trigger_span": [4740, 4750], "answer_text": "The MSCI World Index must categorize companies related to their 'sustainability for easy reference. ", "answer_span": [4858.0, 4873.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "investment.S76.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4958, "question_text": "How is ESG performance calculated? ", "trigger_span": [4933, 4956], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S80.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4995, "question_text": "Why is the goal of the author to increase sustainability? ", "trigger_span": [4981, 4994], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S84.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5061, "question_text": "What does out-performance mean in this context?", "trigger_span": [5036, 5050], "answer_text": "I take this to mean that the companies have 'out-performed the other companies in terms of financial success? ", "answer_span": [5070.0, 5092.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S84.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5626, "question_text": "Are there more examples of this \"wisdom?\"", "trigger_span": [5465, 5478], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S125.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6617, "question_text": "Why is it so impressive to see planets through a space telescope - this has been done an endless amount of times before, but what is new about this situation?", "trigger_span": [6588, 6601], "answer_text": "These individuals are attempting to determine if other plants are able to sustain life - which explains their project. ", "answer_span": [6719.0, 6730.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S93.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5004, "question_text": "why does the telescope turn around?", "trigger_span": [4980, 5002], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S99.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5172, "question_text": "how does it know where to go?", "trigger_span": [5102, 5127], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S33.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2415, "question_text": "What is the purpose of this?", "trigger_span": [2372, 2413], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S38.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2730, "question_text": "What does ESG stand for?", "trigger_span": [2419, 2422], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S94.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5967, "question_text": "Is the individual involved in this discussion an environmentalist or a financial advisor?", "trigger_span": [5881, 5899], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S101.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6022, "question_text": "This discussions seems rather formal and professional, so why is the speaker using casual slang regarding Australians? ", "trigger_span": [5987, 6013], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S103.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6156, "question_text": "Why is this individual interested in the financial success of various pension funds? ", "trigger_span": [6022, 6048], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S78.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4239, "question_text": "why does softening the edges work?", "trigger_span": [4003, 4021], "answer_text": "control their shape, we can control diffraction, and now we have a great shadow", "answer_span": [4364.0, 4376.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "investment.S115.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6698, "question_text": "What is the data that the people 'who don't see it this way' point to to support their positions?", "trigger_span": [6681, 6697], "answer_text": "I can certainly understand people viewing sustainability metrics as a political statement as opposed to a long-term track record for future value generation. ", "answer_span": [6820.0, 6842.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Explicit:Expansion.Disjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S62.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3524, "question_text": "Which planets will you see?", "trigger_span": [3501, 3522], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S69.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3618, "question_text": "Why aren't there any planets?", "trigger_span": [3598, 3616], "answer_text": "There aren't any planets visible because the screen idea doesn't work very well. ", "answer_span": [3626.0, 3664.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "starshade.S71.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3790, "question_text": "Can you see planets through the telescope?", "trigger_span": [3756, 3788], "answer_text": "We can't see planets.", "answer_span": [3914.0, 3934.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Similarity"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S73.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3910, "question_text": "How can you preserve the shadow?", "trigger_span": [3854, 3884], "answer_text": "You can feather or soften the edges to control diffraction.", "answer_span": [4134.0, 4166.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S87.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4534, "question_text": "why is the planet more visible?", "trigger_span": [4452, 4468], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S89.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4728, "question_text": "Why does it have to be so far away?", "trigger_span": [4599, 4632], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S91.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4910, "question_text": "what happens after the hub?", "trigger_span": [4881, 4908], "answer_text": "separates from the telescope", "answer_span": [4913.0, 4941.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "investment.S122.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7270, "question_text": "Why aren't companies and investors responsible for the planet?", "trigger_span": [7089, 7142], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S124.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7331, "question_text": "How are they compatible? ", "trigger_span": [7270, 7288], "answer_text": "The x-factors are the investors", "answer_span": [7335.0, 7393.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S65.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4614, "question_text": "Why did his friend refuse to honor his request?", "trigger_span": [4420, 4443], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S75.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3974, "question_text": "What was Spitzer's answer?", "trigger_span": [3940, 3972], "answer_text": "If you soften the edges you can see the planets because you are controlling diffraction.", "answer_span": [4058.0, 4082.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S77.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4168, "question_text": "Are there any other solutions?", "trigger_span": [4134, 4151], "answer_text": "You can make the edges of the petals exactly right to control diffraction.", "answer_span": [4245.0, 4289.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond", "EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S83.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4239, "question_text": "Who else calls it the flower petal starshade?", "trigger_span": [4198, 4237], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S5.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 385, "question_text": "Why is sustainability important?", "trigger_span": [223, 265], "answer_text": "Because ignoring it can reduce future returns.", "answer_span": [431.0, 487.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief"]}
{"id": "investment.S109.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6564, "question_text": "Is there really any value in simply breaking down value generation into three broad categories? ", "trigger_span": [6508, 6530], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S23.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1905, "question_text": "How do they get food?", "trigger_span": [1801, 1841], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S25.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2068, "question_text": "How young are the people who run away?", "trigger_span": [2030, 2066], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S27.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2462, "question_text": "How does it relieve pressure?", "trigger_span": [2394, 2430], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg1-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg1-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S29.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2691, "question_text": "What did the veteran think of your prosthetic?", "trigger_span": [2587, 2622], "answer_text": "Thought it was very comfortable.", "answer_span": [2745.0, 2768.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S31.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2882, "question_text": "What can you do now with a new prosthetic?", "trigger_span": [2833, 2880], "answer_text": "They can begin the healing", "answer_span": [3059.0, 3100.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S113.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6845, "question_text": "could you do both?", "trigger_span": [6732, 6774], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S89.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6071, "question_text": "How is the near win related to increasing knowledge?", "trigger_span": [6056, 6069], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S91.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6361, "question_text": "Why does this difference in frustration exist?", "trigger_span": [6132, 6200], "answer_text": "The broze medalist are just satisfied that they received any medal at all, whereas the silver medalists were more focused in the next competition.", "answer_span": [6484.0, 6514.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "investment.S73.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4752, "question_text": "How is the ESG performance rated?", "trigger_span": [4665, 4687], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S75.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4910, "question_text": "Who are some of the best ESG performers?", "trigger_span": [4884, 4908], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg1-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg1-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S77.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4981, "question_text": "How many years is ESG performance tracked?", "trigger_span": [4910, 4956], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S83.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5008, "question_text": "What more do you want?", "trigger_span": [4995, 5006], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S168.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9484, "question_text": "How does it poke fun at the issues?", "trigger_span": [9431, 9454], "answer_text": "It has a Mark Twain quote.", "answer_span": [9619.0, 9639.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S170.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9641, "question_text": "What else does it say?", "trigger_span": [9529, 9556], "answer_text": "Your future is where you'll be spending your life.", "answer_span": [9662.0, 9705.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "homeless.S14.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1414, "question_text": "Where does this group of people travel to?", "trigger_span": [1270, 1322], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S21.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1635, "question_text": "Do they ever get caught trying to hop on trains?", "trigger_span": [1522, 1545], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S125.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8749, "question_text": "What more could they do?", "trigger_span": [8703, 8732], "answer_text": "more techniques and drills", "answer_span": [8777.0, 8820.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S119.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6049, "question_text": "What is the purpose of these various tests on the 'petals?'", "trigger_span": [5952, 5983], "answer_text": "They a designing a system to take a new 'portrait of the solar system in a way which I have yet to fully understand.", "answer_span": [6301.0, 6336.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S121.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6248, "question_text": "Are these people designing another version of a space telescope? ", "trigger_span": [6139, 6179], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S123.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6464, "question_text": "What on earth is an occulter - and what is the purpose of taking this 'family portrait of the solar system?", "trigger_span": [6423, 6431], "answer_text": "I believe this device is related to the ability to track the elements needed to sustain life on other planets. ", "answer_span": [6638.0, 6673.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S48.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3388, "question_text": "What changes are these companies making?", "trigger_span": [3341, 3355], "answer_text": "move to cloud", "answer_span": [3486.0, 3503.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "AltLex:Hypophora", "AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "homeless.S27.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2370, "question_text": "Did they used to own homes?", "trigger_span": [2316, 2368], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S29.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2655, "question_text": "What types of places do they explore?", "trigger_span": [2626, 2653], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S35.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2776, "question_text": "What troubles do they face?", "trigger_span": [2723, 2774], "answer_text": "Many are drug addicts and some get killed on trains.", "answer_span": [2831.0, 2892.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "starshade.S127.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6778, "question_text": "How reliable is this technology that determines of these various plants have the properties needed to sustain life? ", "trigger_span": [6686, 6704], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S65.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4488, "question_text": "Which power tools company are these people discussing? ", "trigger_span": [4277, 4289], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S70.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4592, "question_text": "That is a pretty wide blanket statement - has this person done any research into the financial success of companies focused on sustainability?", "trigger_span": [4564, 4591], "answer_text": "This person has indeed looked into the financial sucess of companies interested in sustainability - and cites specific data to support his statement. ", "answer_span": [4637.0, 4647.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S110.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8014, "question_text": "what drives us to do more?", "trigger_span": [7775, 7804], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S117.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8255, "question_text": "what type of imperfections?", "trigger_span": [8196, 8228], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S119.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8404, "question_text": "do they come back to fix the flaw?", "trigger_span": [8291, 8306], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S121.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8479, "question_text": "Why are they masters?", "trigger_span": [8404, 8427], "answer_text": "They know there is no end", "answer_span": [8503.0, 8536.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S123.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8538, "question_text": "How do they work towards the end?", "trigger_span": [8503, 8536], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S24.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1617, "question_text": "What investment rules of today won't work tomorrow?", "trigger_span": [1561, 1586], "answer_text": "rather than just looking at financial data and metrics, investors should look at ESG performance metrics", "answer_span": [1925.0, 1964.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S26.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1826, "question_text": "What should they be looking at, if not financial data and metrics?", "trigger_span": [1699, 1735], "answer_text": "performance metrics in environment, social and governance (ESG)", "answer_span": [1925.0, 1964.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S28.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2002, "question_text": "Why should investors care about environment, social, and governance performance metrics?", "trigger_span": [1966, 2000], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S32.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2283, "question_text": "Why is human capital important?", "trigger_span": [2141, 2154], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S73.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3910, "question_text": "Is there some way to do this that won't destroy the shadow?", "trigger_span": [3854, 3884], "answer_text": "control diffraction by softening the edges then we can see the planets", "answer_span": [4003.0, 4051.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond", "EntRel:nan", "Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S75.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3974, "question_text": "What can be done so we can see the planets?", "trigger_span": [3914, 3934], "answer_text": "control diffraction by softening the edges", "answer_span": [4003.0, 4051.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond", "EntRel:nan", "Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S77.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4168, "question_text": "What kinds of solutions were discovered to accomplish this?", "trigger_span": [4115, 4151], "answer_text": "The flower petal starshade is one solution.", "answer_span": [4215.0, 4237.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S83.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4239, "question_text": "How does the flower petal starshade work?", "trigger_span": [4211, 4237], "answer_text": "control the shape of the starshade which allows researchers to control diffraction", "answer_span": [4297.0, 4344.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond", "EntRel:nan", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S105.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7505, "question_text": "Do near wins make people more determined to try again?", "trigger_span": [7348, 7397], "answer_text": "A near win made Jackie Joyner-Kersee compete harder and set a record for the heptathlon at the next Olympics.", "answer_span": [7649.0, 7677.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "investment.S36.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2415, "question_text": "What is the importance of company oversight (governance) for investors? ", "trigger_span": [2313, 2365], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S10.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1017, "question_text": "Does she have any regrets?", "trigger_span": [909, 934], "answer_text": "Her description of her work would imply that she is completely happy with her current role", "answer_span": [1324.0, 1358.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S12.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1102, "question_text": "Does she experience many difficulties with this lifestyle?", "trigger_span": [1060, 1100], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S16.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1360, "question_text": "To what extent is she a part of the community that she is photographing?", "trigger_span": [1283, 1322], "answer_text": "Her extensive knowledge of this community would imply that she had to have been a part of it for some period of time", "answer_span": [1598.0, 1633.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S20.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1514, "question_text": "Are there any negative sides to this part of America that no one else gets to see?", "trigger_span": [1367, 1412], "answer_text": "\"pet rats\" would imply that the conditions these people endure are quite unhygienic ", "answer_span": [1727.0, 1756.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S17.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1320, "question_text": "What can be done to control risk?", "trigger_span": [1275, 1318], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S22.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1497, "question_text": "Is there a way to simplify them so people understand them better?", "trigger_span": [1324, 1347], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S110.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5692, "question_text": "What are these 'petals that are being discussed? ", "trigger_span": [5522, 5528], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S117.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5893, "question_text": "What type of equipment are these individuals testing?", "trigger_span": [5791, 5807], "answer_text": "I assume they are building a rocket or some type of vehicle for launch into space. ", "answer_span": [5985.0, 6012.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S40.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2907, "question_text": "What are the CEOs doing?", "trigger_span": [2892, 2905], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S42.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3142, "question_text": "How are they incorporating sustainability?", "trigger_span": [3029, 3083], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S44.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3261, "question_text": "What makes the other 7% hesitant?", "trigger_span": [3146, 3178], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S94.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6964, "question_text": "Who or what made the gambling industry stop selling near win scratch off tickets?", "trigger_span": [6798, 6840], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S101.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7157, "question_text": "Does something that seems close seem more attainable?", "trigger_span": [6973, 7028], "answer_text": "We can imagine something that is closer more clearly.", "answer_span": [7242.0, 7269.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S103.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7305, "question_text": "Does a near win really compel people to buy more tickets just because the win seemed so close?", "trigger_span": [7275, 7303], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S20.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1619, "question_text": "Could you alleviate the pressure?", "trigger_span": [1453, 1484], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S14.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1561, "question_text": "Will someone seek to make these more tolerable?", "trigger_span": [1433, 1497], "answer_text": "They will seek to answer this", "answer_span": [1893.0, 1923.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S21.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1739, "question_text": "Can we make sockets more comfortable so people will use them?", "trigger_span": [1627, 1679], "answer_text": "Says they made them more comfortable. ", "answer_span": [2030.0, 2080.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S23.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1925, "question_text": "What steps can you take to develop a more comfortable prosthetic?", "trigger_span": [1893, 1923], "answer_text": "Used magnetic resonance imaging and finite element modeling.", "answer_span": [2137.0, 2201.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Implicit:Contingency.Purpose.Arg2-as-goal", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "investment.S52.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3532, "question_text": "how much did it save state street?", "trigger_span": [3512, 3530], "answer_text": "23 million", "answer_span": [3741.0, 3770.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "AltLex:Hypophora", "AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S107.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7733, "question_text": "So Olympians and gamblers are similar when it comes to how they deal with near wins?", "trigger_span": [7542, 7599], "answer_text": "We thrive when we still have to compete to win rather than when we've already won.", "answer_span": [7733.0, 7769.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S109.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7927, "question_text": "How could you manufacture a near win at a conference?", "trigger_span": [7890, 7925], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S115.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8014, "question_text": "Is there any research that backs this up, rather than just gut level reasoning?", "trigger_span": [7982, 8012], "answer_text": "The study of Navajo crafts people who put imperfections in their work.", "answer_span": [8190.0, 8253.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S53.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3497, "question_text": "Why does mastery take so much time?", "trigger_span": [3449, 3495], "answer_text": "Masterpieces take time to determine and opinions are often subjective", "answer_span": [3668.0, 3710.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S55.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3712, "question_text": "Why is a near win more exciting than success?", "trigger_span": [3537, 3581], "answer_text": "Flaws make works of art more interesting", "answer_span": [3712.0, 3747.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous"]}
{"id": "cities.S39.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3131, "question_text": "What kind of map?", "trigger_span": [3114, 3129], "answer_text": "a map that shows heterogeneous cities", "answer_span": [3338.0, 3355.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "cities.S41.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3326, "question_text": "How is everything mixed up in Rio?", "trigger_span": [3288, 3324], "answer_text": "The city has a heterogenous population.", "answer_span": [3326.0, 3355.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "cities.S43.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3499, "question_text": "What are the people like?", "trigger_span": [3424, 3497], "answer_text": "There is a diverse population and some are interested in music.", "answer_span": [3623.0, 3677.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S45.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3679, "question_text": "What kinds of music do they have there?", "trigger_span": [3653, 3677], "answer_text": "There is country, rap, gospel, funk and even boy bands.", "answer_span": [3731.0, 3785.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S129.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9083, "question_text": "Is this the coach of the archer team?", "trigger_span": [8663, 8674], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S134.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9190, "question_text": "Are we building a team?", "trigger_span": [9083, 9091], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S59.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4109, "question_text": "Why didn't paul revisit his paintings?", "trigger_span": [3968, 4011], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S61.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4354, "question_text": "Why did Franz Kafka not value other people's opinions", "trigger_span": [4234, 4262], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S67.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4524, "question_text": "Why did Franz Kafka's friend ignore his advice?", "trigger_span": [4420, 4455], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S97.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5212, "question_text": "Which planets will we see?", "trigger_span": [5178, 5201], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S102.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5262, "question_text": "What is it called?", "trigger_span": [5234, 5260], "answer_text": "Part of it is petals and a sub-scale star shade.", "answer_span": [5412.0, 5455.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S104.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5399, "question_text": "Was the test a success?", "trigger_span": [5334, 5359], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S68.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4929, "question_text": "Does race equal diversity?", "trigger_span": [4886, 4927], "answer_text": "no, we should change the way we think about diversity", "answer_span": [5207.0, 5250.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S46.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3314, "question_text": "Are mastery and success the same concept?", "trigger_span": [3104, 3142], "answer_text": "They are not the same. Mastery is a constant pursuit", "answer_span": [3314.0, 3342.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"]}
{"id": "starshade.S120.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6139, "question_text": "What stars will the object take pictures of?", "trigger_span": [6073, 6137], "answer_text": "Picture of the solar system", "answer_span": [6292.0, 6336.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S122.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6354, "question_text": "How much larger does the telescope need to be?", "trigger_span": [6156, 6196], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S134.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7578, "question_text": "is the author implying that institutional investors are good or bad for sustainability?", "trigger_span": [7496, 7522], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S136.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7645, "question_text": "What is the author's opinion of this amount of money created by these global markets?", "trigger_span": [7615, 7643], "answer_text": "The author believes the money should be used to solve world problems, due to the excessive amount of money involved ", "answer_span": [7771.0, 7825.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S138.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7771, "question_text": "Is the author stating that institutional investors hinder sustainability?", "trigger_span": [7731, 7769], "answer_text": "It seems the author is suggesting that they use their power to solve world problems, and are not currently doing so", "answer_span": [7883.0, 7940.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond"]}
{"id": "investment.S140.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7942, "question_text": "is this goal the author proposes attainable?", "trigger_span": [7827, 7881], "answer_text": "it seems that the author beleieves this goal to be attainable ", "answer_span": [8012.0, 8069.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S69.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4513, "question_text": "What cases might be isolated?", "trigger_span": [4457, 4487], "answer_text": "Companies that take sustainability into consideration. ", "answer_span": [4516.0, 4563.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S57.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3855, "question_text": "Why does Elizabeth not value her paintings as much as her audience?", "trigger_span": [3794, 3825], "answer_text": "She thought they were incomplete and flawed", "answer_span": [3879.0, 3918.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S131.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9040, "question_text": "how did that make you feel?", "trigger_span": [8921, 8941], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S2.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 239, "question_text": "Why did she want to run away?", "trigger_span": [97, 121], "answer_text": "She had a desire to escape her ordinary life, and experience something new ", "answer_span": [318.0, 345.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "homeless.S6.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 465, "question_text": "What is the source of her desire?", "trigger_span": [249, 274], "answer_text": "Through her career choice, it seems that her desire comes from her own personality and the desires that have resulted from it", "answer_span": [686.0, 723.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence", "Explicit:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner"]}
{"id": "homeless.S8.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 755, "question_text": "Does her current job manifest her current desires?", "trigger_span": [589, 618], "answer_text": "The way she speaks of her current job would imply that it is a current passion as well as a childhood dream", "answer_span": [759.0, 795.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "starshade.S71.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3790, "question_text": "Is there another way to do this that doesn't diffract the light waves?", "trigger_span": [3717, 3751], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Similarity"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S148.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8406, "question_text": "What is the author's rebuttal to the claim that the need for sustainability is exaggerated?", "trigger_span": [8318, 8375], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S113.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5791, "question_text": "What is JPL?", "trigger_span": [5615, 5621], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S118.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6014, "question_text": "Why do they want the object to go into space?", "trigger_span": [5985, 6013], "answer_text": "To take pictures in space", "answer_span": [6049.0, 6065.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S35.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2367, "question_text": "who has more authority over the current issue", "trigger_span": [2287, 2322], "answer_text": "there is a process for every company in authority", "answer_span": [2461.0, 2495.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S81.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5626, "question_text": "what is the reason for somebody to compose something he likes", "trigger_span": [5588, 5625], "answer_text": "he has love for it ", "answer_span": [5783.0, 5800.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S86.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5841, "question_text": "who knows who will be there by then", "trigger_span": [5818, 5840], "answer_text": "everything is unnkown", "answer_span": [5966.0, 5998.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S124.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6603, "question_text": "What is the pale blue dot?", "trigger_span": [6565, 6602], "answer_text": "Earth", "answer_span": [6603.0, 6615.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S126.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6732, "question_text": "How far away can the telescope see?", "trigger_span": [6679, 6731], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S128.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6812, "question_text": "Why is this the coolest science?", "trigger_span": [6732, 6776], "answer_text": "Because it will change the world", "answer_span": [6812.0, 6854.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "investment.S27.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1895, "question_text": "what is the market place supposed to do", "trigger_span": [1875, 1894], "answer_text": "look for perfomance metrics", "answer_span": [1925.0, 1944.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S124.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6603, "question_text": "What is that pale blue dot?", "trigger_span": [6588, 6601], "answer_text": "The pale blue dot is Earth.", "answer_span": [6603.0, 6615.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S69.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3618, "question_text": "How else could someone see the planets?", "trigger_span": [3598, 3616], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S78.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5008, "question_text": "Why was there no performance tradeoff?", "trigger_span": [4933, 4956], "answer_text": "Climate change strategy and risk management", "answer_span": [5310.0, 5338.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S85.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5239, "question_text": "What is ESG?", "trigger_span": [5051, 5059], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S88.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5999, "question_text": "how do you call a person who pretends to know more", "trigger_span": [5966, 5996], "answer_text": "it was mind teasing", "answer_span": [6443.0, 6457.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S90.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6222, "question_text": "what is the simplest way to tell a person you a damn looser?", "trigger_span": [6155, 6200], "answer_text": "play around with it", "answer_span": [6660.0, 6679.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S92.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6516, "question_text": "how easy is it to get what you don't deserve", "trigger_span": [6484, 6502], "answer_text": "it is either yes or no as it is in coins", "answer_span": [6516.0, 6537.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S96.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6855, "question_text": "what are the functions of of a laver", "trigger_span": [6789, 6815], "answer_text": "things that make life more easier", "answer_span": [6973.0, 6998.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S29.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2125, "question_text": "what about the social and governance policies", "trigger_span": [1966, 2000], "answer_text": "they both got roles to play", "answer_span": [2141.0, 2187.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S19.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1553, "question_text": "How is this data gathered?", "trigger_span": [1395, 1434], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S129.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7496, "question_text": "What role do investors play in sustainability?", "trigger_span": [7349, 7393], "answer_text": "One can assume that based on this context, they provide the funding for sustainable efforts", "answer_span": [7551.0, 7576.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "cities.S1.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 241, "question_text": "What is it that we do not think about in regards to mapping cities?", "trigger_span": [128, 150], "answer_text": "The author seems to be implying that we do not think about deeper meanings behind maps ", "answer_span": [584.0, 612.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Disjunction", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Disjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S5.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 431, "question_text": "What is this new kind of map?", "trigger_span": [414, 429], "answer_text": "This is a map of relationships ", "answer_span": [461.0, 495.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "cities.S7.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 614, "question_text": "In what way does each dot represent a person?", "trigger_span": [554, 575], "answer_text": "It is clear that the authors version of a map is a means of social representation ", "answer_span": [624.0, 670.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S9.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 846, "question_text": "Why is this version of a map necessary?", "trigger_span": [700, 728], "answer_text": "It creates a map of people, rather than a map of places ", "answer_span": [1303.0, 1337.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S100.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7048, "question_text": "better off", "trigger_span": [6918, 6926], "answer_text": "what is it good abuot it", "answer_span": [7116.0, 7130.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S62.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3524, "question_text": "Was Spitzer's suggestion doable?", "trigger_span": [3279, 3299], "answer_text": "It didn't work.", "answer_span": [3640.0, 3674.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S136.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9424, "question_text": "Is Elizabeth Murray a painter?", "trigger_span": [9357, 9397], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S138.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9553, "question_text": "What would a utopia look like?", "trigger_span": [9429, 9450], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S2.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 332, "question_text": "Where are you now?", "trigger_span": [67, 88], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S6.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 635, "question_text": "So how did you get out?", "trigger_span": [524, 545], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S8.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 938, "question_text": "Why wouldn't they use their prostheses?", "trigger_span": [906, 936], "answer_text": "They didn't fit god enough", "answer_span": [1031.0, 1052.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "investment.S144.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8234, "question_text": "How substantial would this impact be?", "trigger_span": [8188, 8233], "answer_text": "The author is implying the impact would have dire consequences ", "answer_span": [8234.0, 8287.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S11.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1147, "question_text": "Can this map version up to interpretation?", "trigger_span": [1034, 1061], "answer_text": "It seems that maps like these would be primarily for the use of the people it represents ", "answer_span": [1257.0, 1298.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "cities.S13.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1339, "question_text": "Does this map also represent socio-economic status?", "trigger_span": [1209, 1245], "answer_text": "It seems to strictly measure behavioral patterns and interests ", "answer_span": [1593.0, 1645.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "starshade.S106.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5457, "question_text": "What does the star shade do?", "trigger_span": [5425, 5455], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S108.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5537, "question_text": "How are the petals operated? ", "trigger_span": [5507, 5535], "answer_text": "They rotate into place.", "answer_span": [5673.0, 5690.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan", "AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan", "AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S112.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5652, "question_text": "What does JPL stand for?", "trigger_span": [5597, 5621], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S116.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5791, "question_text": "What happens if they miss their place?", "trigger_span": [5717, 5755], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S62.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4424, "question_text": "What did they produce?", "trigger_span": [4277, 4310], "answer_text": "Sustainable products.", "answer_span": [4516.0, 4563.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S104.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6232, "question_text": "Whats the first largest in the US?", "trigger_span": [6156, 6194], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S106.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6356, "question_text": "What entails a 100% sustainable investment?", "trigger_span": [6259, 6293], "answer_text": "long term value creation", "answer_span": [6445.0, 6470.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Q/A"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Q/A"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S108.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6532, "question_text": "What are the three forms of capital?", "trigger_span": [6508, 6531], "answer_text": "financial, human, physical", "answer_span": [6532.0, 6562.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "starshade.S29.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1846, "question_text": "Will the sun affect what you can see in space?", "trigger_span": [1776, 1811], "answer_text": "yes, it's very bright like the other stars", "answer_span": [1989.0, 2006.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S35.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1965, "question_text": "Is the planet too far away to see at this point?", "trigger_span": [1945, 1963], "answer_text": "It's hard to see due to the brightness of nearby stars", "answer_span": [2014.0, 2068.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S2.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 386, "question_text": "How are cities mapped out?", "trigger_span": [316, 356], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S6.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 461, "question_text": "What kind of map is it?", "trigger_span": [393, 429], "answer_text": "It is a relationship map.", "answer_span": [461.0, 495.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "cities.S8.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 730, "question_text": "How diverse is this network?", "trigger_span": [676, 728], "answer_text": "They are both african americans and latinos.", "answer_span": [900.0, 950.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "investment.S71.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4633, "question_text": "What are some examples of companies making sustainable products?", "trigger_span": [4628, 4631], "answer_text": "The MSCI World", "answer_span": [4729.0, 4750.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S161.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9365, "question_text": "How do we invest sustainably?", "trigger_span": [9078, 9102], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S166.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9399, "question_text": "What do you like?", "trigger_span": [9384, 9397], "answer_text": "They like the comic that makes fun of both sides of the issue.", "answer_span": [9428.0, 9454.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "cities.S54.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4072, "question_text": "Are sports and music fans similar?", "trigger_span": [3984, 4024], "answer_text": "No, they are very diverse", "answer_span": [4141.0, 4183.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"]}
{"id": "cities.S10.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1034, "question_text": "What are the geeks concerned about?", "trigger_span": [972, 1032], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S12.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1209, "question_text": "Are you part of any other networks?", "trigger_span": [1114, 1145], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief", "Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S16.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1509, "question_text": "What is the name of this network?", "trigger_span": [1346, 1370], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S20.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1666, "question_text": "What sports do they enjoy?", "trigger_span": [1608, 1664], "answer_text": "They have a baseball and a football team.", "answer_span": [1669.0, 1731.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S1.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 177, "question_text": "What did her retrospective consist of?", "trigger_span": [134, 175], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S5.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 344, "question_text": "What type of things did she paint?", "trigger_span": [295, 342], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S7.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 485, "question_text": "What was her opinion on her early works?", "trigger_span": [435, 483], "answer_text": "She thought they were below her standards.", "answer_span": [595.0, 632.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S126.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6732, "question_text": "How far will this telescope see?", "trigger_span": [6638, 6673], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S128.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6812, "question_text": "What if the telescope does find life?", "trigger_span": [6752, 6776], "answer_text": "Everything will change.", "answer_span": [6856.0, 6883.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S78.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5008, "question_text": "What do you want more of?", "trigger_span": [4981, 4993], "answer_text": "A good investment.", "answer_span": [5313.0, 5337.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S85.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5239, "question_text": "Should you invest in environmentally conscious companies?", "trigger_span": [5177, 5208], "answer_text": "Investing in environmentally conscious companies will payoff because they have outperformed over the last eight years.", "answer_span": [5268.0, 5308.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "starshade.S113.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5791, "question_text": "What do teh petals do?", "trigger_span": [5543, 5588], "answer_text": "It might be able to take images of Earth's neighboring stars.", "answer_span": [6073.0, 6099.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S118.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6014, "question_text": "What technology are you trying to get into space?", "trigger_span": [5962, 5983], "answer_text": "We could get images of neighboring stars.", "answer_span": [6014.0, 6047.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "starshade.S120.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6139, "question_text": "Will this technology allow us to take pictures of planets and stars?", "trigger_span": [6058, 6065], "answer_text": "Yes, it will allow us to get images of our solar system.", "answer_span": [6149.0, 6179.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond", "EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S122.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6354, "question_text": "What else might we see with this technology?", "trigger_span": [6253, 6288], "answer_text": "We might be able to see a different solar system from our own.", "answer_span": [6376.0, 6403.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "investment.S87.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5339, "question_text": "Will the trend continue?", "trigger_span": [5248, 5266], "answer_text": "Yes, focusing on the environment yields good results.", "answer_span": [5387.0, 5443.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg1-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S107.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7733, "question_text": "Do most people get these kinds of results from addressing their mountains?", "trigger_span": [7610, 7644], "answer_text": "It is at least implied that people achieve greater results through the mentality of near-wins.", "answer_span": [7931.0, 7961.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S109.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7927, "question_text": "How can we reproduce these results?", "trigger_span": [7876, 7925], "answer_text": "We listen to our guts.", "answer_span": [7979.0, 8012.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S115.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8014, "question_text": "How can my life play this out?", "trigger_span": [7931, 7961], "answer_text": "My life can play it out by accomplishing things in a near-complete way, giving me something higher and higher to aim toward.", "answer_span": [8027.0, 8073.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S94.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6964, "question_text": "How does it change our view of the landscape?", "trigger_span": [6907, 6943], "answer_text": "Our goals seem closer to us through near-wins.", "answer_span": [7000.0, 7046.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S101.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7157, "question_text": "What are these more general terms?", "trigger_span": [7112, 7155], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S103.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7305, "question_text": "What are the downsides to the near-win mentality?", "trigger_span": [7271, 7303], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S105.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7505, "question_text": "Is the addressing positive overall or negative?", "trigger_span": [7348, 7383], "answer_text": "It implies that the addressing of the mountain is positive, but we also know that there were abuses of near-wins.", "answer_span": [7610.0, 7626.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "starshade.S64.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3435, "question_text": "what can you use to travel to space with a big screen?", "trigger_span": [3328, 3366], "answer_text": "all this failed ", "answer_span": [3643.0, 3675.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "starshade.S68.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3566, "question_text": "we are going to use a space ship or a rocket", "trigger_span": [3435, 3459], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S14.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1246, "question_text": "Are all these humans contributing to the current climate change", "trigger_span": [1110, 1147], "answer_text": "they are not part of it ", "answer_span": [1246.0, 1307.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "investment.S21.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1472, "question_text": "are all gonna die ", "trigger_span": [1421, 1447], "answer_text": "the most important thing is life", "answer_span": [1497.0, 1519.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast", "Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast", "Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "starshade.S49.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2788, "question_text": "how is that possible?", "trigger_span": [2576, 2610], "answer_text": "the moon moved toward the sun to get that corona ", "answer_span": [2792.0, 2826.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "starshade.S54.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2901, "question_text": "is the moon going to crush the sun", "trigger_span": [2788, 2826], "answer_text": "that will never happen", "answer_span": [2917.0, 2945.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "starshade.S56.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3039, "question_text": "is there a different if you turn around and look", "trigger_span": [3008, 3037], "answer_text": "that makes a difference ", "answer_span": [3039.0, 3061.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S58.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3115, "question_text": "what happens to the sun when the moon blocks its light from reaching where it was supposed ", "trigger_span": [3067, 3113], "answer_text": "we use use a camera telescope to see that", "answer_span": [3124.0, 3160.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S102.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6050, "question_text": "What is CalPERs?", "trigger_span": [6022, 6048], "answer_text": "a pension fund for public employees in california ", "answer_span": [6050.0, 6112.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S23.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1520, "question_text": "is the changes caused by climate change reverseble", "trigger_span": [1472, 1495], "answer_text": "they call it market complexion ", "answer_span": [1830.0, 1858.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S25.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1728, "question_text": "what if they fail to invest in a more appropriate bank account", "trigger_span": [1699, 1727], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S89.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5445, "question_text": "Should we invest more in these companies?", "trigger_span": [5426, 5443], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S91.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5600, "question_text": "Do people want to invest in companies that care about the environment?", "trigger_span": [5494, 5509], "answer_text": "Some institutions are interested in investing in environmentally conscious companies.", "answer_span": [5606.0, 5614.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora"]}
{"id": "investment.S93.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5661, "question_text": "How can we gather more interest?", "trigger_span": [5620, 5629], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S99.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5967, "question_text": "So, Hesta would be a good investment?", "trigger_span": [5761, 5781], "answer_text": "Australians care about their fund members.", "answer_span": [5967.0, 5985.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S60.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3279, "question_text": "how does the moon being in front of the sun affect the sun ", "trigger_span": [3165, 3185], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S112.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6604, "question_text": "Why are they concerned with ESG?", "trigger_span": [6572, 6603], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S116.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6845, "question_text": "Why don't they want to use the portfolio to make policy statements?", "trigger_span": [6785, 6842], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S87.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5339, "question_text": "What does outperforming entail?", "trigger_span": [5268, 5308], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg1-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S89.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5445, "question_text": "Why is it not causation?", "trigger_span": [5339, 5357], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S91.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5600, "question_text": "Why wouldn't the investors be engaged?", "trigger_span": [5538, 5599], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S93.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5661, "question_text": "Who are Hesta?", "trigger_span": [5654, 5659], "answer_text": "Retirement fund for health and community services employees in Australia", "answer_span": [5672.0, 5744.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "investment.S99.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5967, "question_text": "Why do they believe ESG has the potential to impact risks and returns?", "trigger_span": [5801, 5850], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S97.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5987, "question_text": "What is ESG?", "trigger_span": [5801, 5804], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S49.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3882, "question_text": "Are different kids of people into music?", "trigger_span": [3594, 3649], "answer_text": "yes, from country to Justin bieber", "answer_span": [4030.0, 4070.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "investment.S112.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6604, "question_text": "What are the negative impacts of ESG?", "trigger_span": [6576, 6601], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S116.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6845, "question_text": "Do a lot of investors use ESG?", "trigger_span": [6611, 6641], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S1.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 142, "question_text": "How many planets are there?", "trigger_span": [120, 140], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S83.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4239, "question_text": "What is the flower petal starshade like?", "trigger_span": [4215, 4237], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S17.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1320, "question_text": "How are they economic issues?", "trigger_span": [1254, 1269], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S22.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1497, "question_text": "How do we resist this?", "trigger_span": [1472, 1495], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S24.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1617, "question_text": "What do you mean by 'purpose'?", "trigger_span": [1599, 1606], "answer_text": "The response pertains to financial purposes.", "answer_span": [1712.0, 1726.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "investment.S151.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8675, "question_text": "How do we choose better actions?", "trigger_span": [8622, 8673], "answer_text": "We need to prepare ourselves for worries.", "answer_span": [8992.0, 9038.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S153.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8918, "question_text": "What is based on scientific consensus?", "trigger_span": [8741, 8789], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Exception.Arg2-as-excpt"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S56.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4211, "question_text": "Is rio a fun city?", "trigger_span": [4126, 4129], "answer_text": "it's fun and diverse with lots of data on it.", "answer_span": [4219.0, 4246.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "cities.S58.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4369, "question_text": "Can rio be compared to other cities?", "trigger_span": [4289, 4340], "answer_text": "yes, they have a lot of data to do so.", "answer_span": [4477.0, 4507.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "cities.S60.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4578, "question_text": "Why are they segregated?", "trigger_span": [4437, 4470], "answer_text": "People choose to segregate themselves", "answer_span": [4711.0, 4770.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S64.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4772, "question_text": "Is social life like a high school?", "trigger_span": [4678, 4705], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S9.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 645, "question_text": "What were her favorite works of her's?", "trigger_span": [582, 612], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S11.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 801, "question_text": "How much was the painting worth?", "trigger_span": [752, 799], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S157.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9127, "question_text": "What two things does sustainable investing do?", "trigger_span": [9081, 9125], "answer_text": "Sacrificing performance but reducing the damage to the planet.", "answer_span": [9153.0, 9184.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S163.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9281, "question_text": "How do we keep the economy safe?", "trigger_span": [9166, 9203], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S2.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 296, "question_text": "What is the instrument that can be able to image on earth?", "trigger_span": [190, 233], "answer_text": "Space telescope can be used ?", "answer_span": [477.0, 514.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S6.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 625, "question_text": "Does every star in the galaxy has planet ?", "trigger_span": [550, 589], "answer_text": "Yes they have ", "answer_span": [658.0, 693.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S13.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 958, "question_text": "How did this change how you went about being creative?", "trigger_span": [817, 858], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S19.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1070, "question_text": "How do we turn success in to mastery?", "trigger_span": [981, 1026], "answer_text": "It is when we get close to accomplishing something that we begin to try harder.", "answer_span": [1095.0, 1132.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S142.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8288, "question_text": "What should we do to better plan for retirement?", "trigger_span": [8160, 8201], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S149.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8460, "question_text": "What sustainability risks can we avoid?", "trigger_span": [8326, 8360], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S5.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 448, "question_text": "How long will this take?", "trigger_span": [427, 446], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S7.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 658, "question_text": "How did astronomers come to the conclusion that up to 1/5 of stars have an Earth-like planet?", "trigger_span": [540, 589], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S26.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1826, "question_text": "What does the financial data look like in terms of hard stats?", "trigger_span": [1712, 1726], "answer_text": "The data is outlined in terms of the ESG concepts, such as the environmental and social factors.", "answer_span": [2125.0, 2154.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S28.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2002, "question_text": "How do we evaluate ESG?", "trigger_span": [1917, 1964], "answer_text": "Environment pertains to how we use resources, social pertains to human capital, and governance has not yet been addressed.", "answer_span": [2002.0, 2041.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S32.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2283, "question_text": "How does this benefit humans in terms of their basic human rights?", "trigger_span": [2224, 2281], "answer_text": "It benefits them in terms of protecting their health as well as that of the planet.", "answer_span": [2593.0, 2629.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence", "Explicit:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner"]}
{"id": "investment.S36.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2415, "question_text": "How should boards and investors handle the oversight?", "trigger_span": [2313, 2335], "answer_text": "They should handle it in a way that protects people and the planet.", "answer_span": [2569.0, 2629.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence", "Explicit:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner"]}
{"id": "starshade.S14.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1226, "question_text": "Why can't they see as far as the want ot with the telescope?", "trigger_span": [1186, 1224], "answer_text": "The telescope is too small and out of orbit", "answer_span": [1240.0, 1281.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "investment.S155.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9068, "question_text": "What is the best insurance to get?", "trigger_span": [8992, 9026], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S11.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 986, "question_text": "Where is Voyager now?", "trigger_span": [767, 793], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S13.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1030, "question_text": "What are the issues around what the author wants done?", "trigger_span": [1012, 1029], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S19.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1226, "question_text": "How can we improve our imaging?", "trigger_span": [1188, 1224], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S33.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2880, "question_text": "Why are communities not getting along in San Francisco?", "trigger_span": [2779, 2803], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S38.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3043, "question_text": "What IS happening on the ground in San Francisco?", "trigger_span": [2993, 3041], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S40.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3168, "question_text": "What's the similarities between San Francisco and Rio de Janeiro?", "trigger_span": [3131, 3166], "answer_text": "It's a mixed city with varied cultures and peoples.", "answer_span": [3326.0, 3355.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S31.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2882, "question_text": "did they enjoy helping this person? ", "trigger_span": [2857, 2863], "answer_text": "they are healing the people", "answer_span": [3065.0, 3082.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S113.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6845, "question_text": "so what do they do there?", "trigger_span": [6756, 6774], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S75.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3974, "question_text": "What is the answer?", "trigger_span": [3940, 3972], "answer_text": "The answer is to feather and soften the edges.", "answer_span": [3984.0, 4021.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond", "EntRel:nan", "Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "cities.S42.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3405, "question_text": "How does Rio de Janeiro illustrate the point about San Francisco?", "trigger_span": [3168, 3219], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S44.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3571, "question_text": "What is TEDxRio?", "trigger_span": [3499, 3506], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S118.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6983, "question_text": "why does this person let it get under their skin?", "trigger_span": [6875, 6888], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S120.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7061, "question_text": "what does he want to clarify?", "trigger_span": [7031, 7048], "answer_text": "he thinks others think that he can do more than he actually can.", "answer_span": [7124.0, 7142.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S122.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7270, "question_text": "why doesnt he just change his job if he doesnt like it so much?", "trigger_span": [7061, 7115], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S124.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7331, "question_text": "what is he talking about?", "trigger_span": [7293, 7329], "answer_text": "insitutional investors hold the key", "answer_span": [7349.0, 7375.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "starshade.S9.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 747, "question_text": "How have we detected these planets indirectly?", "trigger_span": [658, 693], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S30.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2285, "question_text": "How would he coach offer support?", "trigger_span": [1985, 2020], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S37.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2486, "question_text": "How many times did she go after it?", "trigger_span": [2451, 2484], "answer_text": "She kept at it for three hours.", "answer_span": [2486.0, 2501.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S128.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7421, "question_text": "what does he think should change?", "trigger_span": [7395, 7420], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Q/A"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Q/A"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S132.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7496, "question_text": "can it be changed?", "trigger_span": [7425, 7445], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S62.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3524, "question_text": "Why do they want to see the planets?", "trigger_span": [3501, 3522], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S69.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3618, "question_text": "Why aren't there planets yet?", "trigger_span": [3598, 3616], "answer_text": "The plan didn't work well.", "answer_span": [3626.0, 3674.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "starshade.S71.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3790, "question_text": "Is there going to be a new plan?", "trigger_span": [3723, 3764], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Similarity"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S73.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3910, "question_text": "Why is the shadow so terrible?", "trigger_span": [3886, 3908], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S97.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5987, "question_text": "Do a lot of Australians invest in Hesta?", "trigger_span": [5703, 5744], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S102.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6050, "question_text": "What is CalPERS?", "trigger_span": [6022, 6029], "answer_text": "CalPERS is a large pension fund for public employees in California.", "answer_span": [6082.0, 6112.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S104.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6232, "question_text": "Are there any more examples?", "trigger_span": [6050, 6057], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S106.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6356, "question_text": "How are they integrating ESG?", "trigger_span": [6297, 6326], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Q/A"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Q/A"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S108.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6532, "question_text": "What are the three forms of capital?", "trigger_span": [6508, 6530], "answer_text": "The three forms of capital have to do with financial, human and physical interests.", "answer_span": [6532.0, 6562.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "starshade.S77.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4168, "question_text": "What are those solutions?", "trigger_span": [4134, 4166], "answer_text": "The flower petal starshade is at least one solution.", "answer_span": [4215.0, 4237.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "cities.S48.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3725, "question_text": "How does the diversity of people affect Rio?", "trigger_span": [3594, 3629], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S52.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3882, "question_text": "What are the sections that are being talked about?", "trigger_span": [3826, 3839], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S77.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4981, "question_text": "Will it continue?", "trigger_span": [4910, 4931], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S83.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5008, "question_text": "What will you do?", "trigger_span": [4995, 5006], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S129.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9083, "question_text": "Will he continue?", "trigger_span": [9061, 9081], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S134.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9190, "question_text": "Will he succeed?", "trigger_span": [9086, 9095], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S136.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9424, "question_text": "Will he get what he wanted?", "trigger_span": [9206, 9233], "answer_text": "he still has the incomplete", "answer_span": [9477.0, 9496.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S138.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9553, "question_text": "How long will it go on?", "trigger_span": [9544, 9551], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S29.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2691, "question_text": "did they like the new prosthesis?", "trigger_span": [2657, 2689], "answer_text": "they said it was sexy and like walking on pillows", "answer_span": [2750.0, 2768.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S7.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 658, "question_text": "will we be able to see the earth-like planets anytime soon?", "trigger_span": [629, 656], "answer_text": "only can see them indirectly", "answer_span": [658.0, 694.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S25.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1703, "question_text": "Are you suggesting that it's because they were relaxed that they were successful? Or are they relaxed because they're masters? ", "trigger_span": [1585, 1606], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S27.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1923, "question_text": "And did this give you a better idea of why they are successful?", "trigger_span": [1868, 1921], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S29.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2107, "question_text": "And were they all successful in hitting the ten ring?", "trigger_span": [2072, 2105], "answer_text": "At least one archer was successful.", "answer_span": [2337.0, 2354.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S35.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2285, "question_text": "What is the definition of draw weight?", "trigger_span": [2249, 2270], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S21.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1330, "question_text": "How blurry will earth look after the telescope was adjusted?", "trigger_span": [1291, 1328], "answer_text": "It looks smaller", "answer_span": [1366.0, 1421.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S23.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1423, "question_text": "Can you see uranus with telescope?", "trigger_span": [1349, 1364], "answer_text": "They can see moons around uranus orbit", "answer_span": [1426.0, 1455.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "starshade.S25.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1569, "question_text": "Can you see the edge of the solar system with a telescope?", "trigger_span": [1515, 1543], "answer_text": "No, it's dot like at this distance", "answer_span": [1599.0, 1638.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Synchronous"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Synchronous"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "starshade.S27.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1640, "question_text": "Can the telescope be adjusted at this distance?", "trigger_span": [1582, 1597], "answer_text": "Yes, you can move further away or up closer.", "answer_span": [1640.0, 1687.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S116.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5791, "question_text": "What happens if they get misplaced?", "trigger_span": [5759, 5789], "answer_text": "Failure won't happen", "answer_span": [5822.0, 5864.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S158.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9281, "question_text": "Performance of what?", "trigger_span": [9252, 9279], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S165.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9384, "question_text": "Like what?", "trigger_span": [9371, 9382], "answer_text": "It elaborates that whatever they're looking at pokes fun at climate change issues.", "answer_span": [9458.0, 9482.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "investment.S167.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9420, "question_text": "What do you like?", "trigger_span": [9384, 9419], "answer_text": "I guess they're laughing at the joke in some climate change-related comic strip they're reading.", "answer_span": [9428.0, 9469.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "investment.S169.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9525, "question_text": "What side are you on?", "trigger_span": [9500, 9523], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S171.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9708, "question_text": "So you must believe in climate change.", "trigger_span": [9619, 9639], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S21.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1263, "question_text": "What was so special about what these archers did?", "trigger_span": [1095, 1132], "answer_text": "It seems that part of it is that you don't always aim directly at your target if you want to shoot for success.", "answer_span": [1447.0, 1485.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S23.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1487, "question_text": "What does this have to do with converting success into mastery?", "trigger_span": [1358, 1381], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S9.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 747, "question_text": "Will NASA have the budget to keep looking for more blue dots?", "trigger_span": [703, 745], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S11.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 986, "question_text": "How close is the nearest earth-like planet?", "trigger_span": [882, 920], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S13.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1030, "question_text": "Why haven't we seen more earth-like planets?", "trigger_span": [986, 1011], "answer_text": "we haven't moved the Hubble Space Telescope so we can see more", "answer_span": [1060.0, 1113.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "AltLex:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S14.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1561, "question_text": "why hasnt there been a streamlined way of helping people deal with this problem?", "trigger_span": [1541, 1559], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S21.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1739, "question_text": "how old are they? or do they mean like age of mankind?", "trigger_span": [1714, 1737], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S23.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1925, "question_text": "how is the person going to help them?", "trigger_span": [1909, 1922], "answer_text": "they made a whole new process of making prosteses.", "answer_span": [1970.0, 2004.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S25.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2276, "question_text": "did it work? were they fitting better and not hurting people as much?", "trigger_span": [2034, 2079], "answer_text": "it relieves pressure so yes", "answer_span": [2400.0, 2417.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Implicit:Contingency.Purpose.Arg2-as-goal"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S27.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2462, "question_text": "how happy was this person to help the peopel in need?", "trigger_span": [2449, 2460], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg1-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg1-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S30.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2285, "question_text": "did the archer hit the ten ring target?", "trigger_span": [2080, 2105], "answer_text": "she hit the 7 ring on the target", "answer_span": [2285.0, 2306.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S37.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2486, "question_text": "how did she do overall?", "trigger_span": [2451, 2484], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S19.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1226, "question_text": "Is NASA going to move the Hubble to orbit Mars?", "trigger_span": [1118, 1153], "answer_text": "there is a small telescope orbiting Mars", "answer_span": [1255.0, 1289.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "cities.S33.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2880, "question_text": "Why isn't the LGBT community getting along with the geek community?", "trigger_span": [2790, 2827], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S38.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3043, "question_text": "What exactly does the photo show?", "trigger_span": [2984, 3024], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S40.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3168, "question_text": "What does the map show about Rio de Janeiro?", "trigger_span": [3131, 3166], "answer_text": "the map shows that the city is very heterogeneous", "answer_span": [3288.0, 3324.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"]}
{"id": "cities.S42.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3405, "question_text": "What exactly is a heterogeneous city?", "trigger_span": [3338, 3355], "answer_text": "there is a diversity of people in Rio de Janeiro", "answer_span": [3599.0, 3629.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S89.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5445, "question_text": "What's the next step for environmentally conscious companies?", "trigger_span": [5387, 5411], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S39.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2626, "question_text": "how did they practice?", "trigger_span": [2516, 2542], "answer_text": "they practiced for three hours", "answer_span": [2941.0, 2977.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Contingency.Purpose.Arg2-as-goal"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S41.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2739, "question_text": "was she a fan of T.S. Eliot?", "trigger_span": [2678, 2688], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S43.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3023, "question_text": "Why is it so rare in American culture to practice so hard?", "trigger_span": [2744, 2771], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S45.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3144, "question_text": "why is it so rare to see that difference between success and mastery?", "trigger_span": [3099, 3142], "answer_text": "mastery is doing it over and over again - success can be just doing it once", "answer_span": [3147.0, 3179.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S51.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3314, "question_text": "why is mastery not the same as excellence?", "trigger_span": [3262, 3304], "answer_text": "Mastery is a serious pursuit and not a one time thing", "answer_span": [3432.0, 3469.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S44.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3571, "question_text": "What is TEDxRio?", "trigger_span": [3499, 3506], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S48.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3725, "question_text": "What other diversities are there besides music?", "trigger_span": [3653, 3677], "answer_text": "other diversity is comedy", "answer_span": [3790.0, 3805.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S52.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3882, "question_text": "Why is it cool?", "trigger_span": [3864, 3881], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S51.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3314, "question_text": "Why is mastery not the same as excellence?", "trigger_span": [3262, 3304], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S1.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 142, "question_text": "what else is the universe teaming with?", "trigger_span": [108, 132], "answer_text": "what else do astronomers think is out there?", "answer_span": [472.0, 514.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S5.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 448, "question_text": "What is the technology going to entail?", "trigger_span": [382, 392], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S113.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5791, "question_text": "What are the petals' purpose?", "trigger_span": [5543, 5565], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S118.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6014, "question_text": "What are they sending to space?", "trigger_span": [5985, 6012], "answer_text": "Something to do with taking pictures in space", "answer_span": [6058.0, 6099.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S120.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6139, "question_text": "Are we doing something with the Hubble?", "trigger_span": [6115, 6137], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S122.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6354, "question_text": "What's an occulter?", "trigger_span": [6216, 6231], "answer_text": "Some sort of shade for telescopes", "answer_span": [6433.0, 6462.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "starshade.S124.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6603, "question_text": "What's the blue dot?", "trigger_span": [6588, 6601], "answer_text": "It's Earth", "answer_span": [6610.0, 6615.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S10.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1054, "question_text": "did anyone help them get new prostesis?", "trigger_span": [1036, 1047], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S12.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1302, "question_text": "did they continue to try and find more prostesis for them that would actually fit?", "trigger_span": [1282, 1300], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession+SpeechAct.Arg2-as-denier+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession+SpeechAct.Arg2-as-denier+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S16.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1428, "question_text": "has anyone helped them get a new conventional method prosthetists? ", "trigger_span": [1334, 1346], "answer_text": "they were asked to help solve the problem!", "answer_span": [1847.0, 1865.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S20.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1619, "question_text": "is there anything that will help with that pain?", "trigger_span": [1541, 1559], "answer_text": "they are being asked to help solve the problem!", "answer_span": [1847.0, 1865.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S39.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2626, "question_text": "What does star-fished mean?", "trigger_span": [2613, 2624], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S41.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2739, "question_text": "What did TS Eliot mean by that still point of the turning world?", "trigger_span": [2700, 2737], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S43.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3023, "question_text": "Why is it so rare in American culture?", "trigger_span": [2744, 2771], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S45.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3144, "question_text": "What is the difference between success and mastery?", "trigger_span": [3099, 3142], "answer_text": "Success is achieving something, mastery is being able to achieve it time after time.", "answer_span": [3239.0, 3260.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast", "Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond"]}
{"id": "starshade.S102.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5262, "question_text": "Has this been published?", "trigger_span": [5241, 5260], "answer_text": "What will you do now?", "answer_span": [5297.0, 5320.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S104.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5399, "question_text": "What will you do next?", "trigger_span": [5297, 5319], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S106.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5457, "question_text": "Are there others?", "trigger_span": [5412, 5423], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S108.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5537, "question_text": "Are there others?", "trigger_span": [5489, 5505], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan", "AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S112.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5652, "question_text": "Are there other petals?", "trigger_span": [5560, 5614], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S87.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5339, "question_text": "Correlation to what?", "trigger_span": [5318, 5337], "answer_text": "Companies that worry about climate change are doing well financially.", "answer_span": [5387.0, 5443.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg1-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg1-as-subst"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "investment.S122.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7270, "question_text": "Why are companies and investors not responsible?", "trigger_span": [7061, 7115], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S124.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7331, "question_text": "How are they compatible?", "trigger_span": [7270, 7288], "answer_text": "institutional investors are the x-factor in sustainability", "answer_span": [7335.0, 7393.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "starshade.S12.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1012, "question_text": "Can a earth -like planet be taken for another star?", "trigger_span": [948, 984], "answer_text": "Yes it can ", "answer_span": [1114.0, 1153.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "AltLex:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "starshade.S16.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1155, "question_text": "Hubble space telescope can be used for what ?", "trigger_span": [1069, 1113], "answer_text": "It can be turned around and move around the orbit of Mars ", "answer_span": [1186.0, 1224.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "investment.S62.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4424, "question_text": "What are their plans?", "trigger_span": [4294, 4310], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S69.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4513, "question_text": "What is your evidence for more?", "trigger_span": [4472, 4487], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S71.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4633, "question_text": "How much better financially?", "trigger_span": [4564, 4591], "answer_text": "stocks are similar", "answer_span": [4653.0, 4708.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S73.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4752, "question_text": "What are some other indicators?", "trigger_span": [4720, 4727], "answer_text": "other indices and gold", "answer_span": [4757.0, 4784.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S75.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4910, "question_text": "Are there more indicators?", "trigger_span": [4868, 4873], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg1-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg1-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S97.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5212, "question_text": "Is this for an exhibition?", "trigger_span": [5144, 5151], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S85.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5239, "question_text": "What are the best climate change companies?", "trigger_span": [5177, 5208], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S67.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4837, "question_text": "What can you look at seeing how everybody arranged themselves ", "trigger_span": [4772, 4804], "answer_text": "Maps", "answer_span": [4977.0, 5018.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "starshade.S20.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1291, "question_text": "Why is a slightly blurry picture of the earth ?", "trigger_span": [1242, 1254], "answer_text": "It is because we are a fairly small telescope out at the orbit of Mars", "answer_span": [1342.0, 1364.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "cities.S46.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3864, "question_text": "Why did you have a tremendous diversity of people", "trigger_span": [3639, 3677], "answer_text": "Because they are interested in different types of music ", "answer_span": [3882.0, 3912.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S53.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3944, "question_text": "Was the Flamengo football football team represented there ?", "trigger_span": [3913, 3942], "answer_text": "Yes they were ", "answer_span": [4076.0, 4099.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"]}
{"id": "cities.S55.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4185, "question_text": "Are you fit to understanding Rio as being a very multicultural?", "trigger_span": [4100, 4159], "answer_text": "Yes i am .", "answer_span": [4185.0, 4209.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S8.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 695, "question_text": "Did all the Earth-like planet has speculate ?", "trigger_span": [658, 693], "answer_text": "About one fifth of them have an Earth-like planet ", "answer_span": [775.0, 793.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S10.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 922, "question_text": "When was Voyager spacecraft taken ?", "trigger_span": [786, 793], "answer_text": "It was taken in 1990", "answer_span": [948.0, 984.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"]}
{"id": "investment.S91.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5600, "question_text": "Are investors not working on/with these environmentally conscious companies?", "trigger_span": [5580, 5599], "answer_text": "Some are, especially one called \"Hesta.\"", "answer_span": [5600.0, 5614.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora"]}
{"id": "investment.S93.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5661, "question_text": "What is Hesta doing?", "trigger_span": [5654, 5659], "answer_text": "They're working on/with ESG to give members good returns.", "answer_span": [5903.0, 5921.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "investment.S99.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5967, "question_text": "What is ESG?", "trigger_span": [5801, 5838], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S97.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5987, "question_text": "What is ESG doing?", "trigger_span": [5801, 5832], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S6.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 635, "question_text": "do they like where they live now?", "trigger_span": [446, 460], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S8.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 938, "question_text": "why wouldnt they use their prostesis?", "trigger_span": [906, 936], "answer_text": "they didnt fit well.", "answer_span": [1036.0, 1047.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "starshade.S128.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6812, "question_text": "What's the science field?", "trigger_span": [6748, 6776], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S78.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5008, "question_text": "Want more what?", "trigger_span": [4981, 5006], "answer_text": "Performance of top companies", "answer_span": [5081.0, 5128.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S14.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1561, "question_text": "Is there a way to relieve the pressure?", "trigger_span": [1476, 1497], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S21.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1739, "question_text": "Can they be shone the benfits out way the pain involved?", "trigger_span": [1627, 1661], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S102.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6050, "question_text": "CalPERS is an example of what?", "trigger_span": [6022, 6048], "answer_text": "It's a pension fund that invests for Californians.", "answer_span": [6065.0, 6112.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S104.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6232, "question_text": "What is CalPERS doing?", "trigger_span": [6050, 6057], "answer_text": "Working on climate conscious investments.", "answer_span": [6259.0, 6293.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S106.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6356, "question_text": "What is ESG?", "trigger_span": [6297, 6326], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Q/A"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Q/A"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S108.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6532, "question_text": "What are the three forms of capital?", "trigger_span": [6508, 6530], "answer_text": "money, people and things", "answer_span": [6532.0, 6562.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S6.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 635, "question_text": "Do you feel safe now for yourself and your children?", "trigger_span": [446, 460], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S8.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 938, "question_text": "Why do they not use their prostheses?", "trigger_span": [906, 936], "answer_text": "painful because they did not fit well", "answer_span": [1015.0, 1052.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S25.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2276, "question_text": "what is magnetic resonance imaging?", "trigger_span": [2088, 2114], "answer_text": "3d printer that images", "answer_span": [2338.0, 2348.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S27.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2462, "question_text": "So this makes it more comfortable by fitting better?", "trigger_span": [2400, 2430], "answer_text": "walking on pillows", "answer_span": [2750.0, 2768.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg1-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg1-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S29.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2691, "question_text": "How quickly and cheaply can they be made comparatively? ", "trigger_span": [2511, 2530], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S112.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6604, "question_text": "How is ESG concerning?", "trigger_span": [6583, 6601], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S10.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1054, "question_text": "Can they get new prostheses to fit better?", "trigger_span": [1040, 1052], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S12.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1302, "question_text": "Can they be taught this lesson that it takes time to get comfortable.", "trigger_span": [1282, 1300], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession+SpeechAct.Arg2-as-denier+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession+SpeechAct.Arg2-as-denier+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S16.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1428, "question_text": "Is their a new process that can be used to adjust the time it takes to get used to it?", "trigger_span": [1334, 1356], "answer_text": "solve this problem", "answer_span": [1847.0, 1865.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S20.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1619, "question_text": "Is there a way to relieve the pressure?", "trigger_span": [1453, 1484], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S116.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6845, "question_text": "Why shouldn't portfolios make statements?", "trigger_span": [6807, 6843], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S78.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4239, "question_text": "What optimal solutions are there", "trigger_span": [4115, 4151], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S85.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4378, "question_text": "What is the shadow for?", "trigger_span": [4357, 4376], "answer_text": "make planets easier to see", "answer_span": [4437.0, 4459.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S87.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4534, "question_text": "why does it have to be bigger than a thumb?", "trigger_span": [4502, 4532], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S89.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4728, "question_text": "How expensive is the telescope?", "trigger_span": [4642, 4651], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S91.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4910, "question_text": "what is JPL?", "trigger_span": [4796, 4802], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S93.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5004, "question_text": "What separates from the telescope", "trigger_span": [4910, 4922], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S23.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1925, "question_text": "How to solve this problem?", "trigger_span": [1840, 1852], "answer_text": "designed custom prosethetic sockets", "answer_span": [1970.0, 2004.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "investment.S128.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7421, "question_text": "Why are they xfactor?", "trigger_span": [7367, 7375], "answer_text": "they have the money", "answer_span": [7451.0, 7494.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Q/A"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Q/A", "EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S132.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7496, "question_text": "But why should they give their money?", "trigger_span": [7451, 7494], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S2.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 332, "question_text": "do they still live there?", "trigger_span": [73, 88], "answer_text": "they said they ran for safety, so i assume they left for good. ", "answer_span": [446.0, 460.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S126.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6732, "question_text": "How good are the chances of finding an Earth-like planet?", "trigger_span": [6642, 6673], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S31.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2882, "question_text": "How does this give meaning to your life?", "trigger_span": [2857, 2874], "answer_text": "healing the souls", "answer_span": [3065.0, 3082.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S113.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6845, "question_text": "Why did they not see your point?", "trigger_span": [6665, 6696], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S118.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6983, "question_text": "Why does it get under your skin?", "trigger_span": [6870, 6888], "answer_text": "indefinite social obligations and prudent investing and finance theory", "answer_span": [7160.0, 7231.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S120.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7061, "question_text": "Why are their eyes rolling when you speak to them?", "trigger_span": [6988, 7014], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S59.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4472, "question_text": "How can we understand that it is segregation is a social construct ?", "trigger_span": [4404, 4428], "answer_text": "We can  try to understand it ", "answer_span": [4605.0, 4647.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S61.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4707, "question_text": "What is data trying to do?", "trigger_span": [4605, 4637], "answer_text": "The data is aiming a space telescope ", "answer_span": [4722.0, 4770.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S10.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 802, "question_text": "What are some better-performing could be suggested?", "trigger_span": [766, 800], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S12.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 882, "question_text": "What we already know?", "trigger_span": [849, 880], "answer_text": "Population is growing, and everybody already aware of that", "answer_span": [882.0, 932.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S16.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1170, "question_text": "How true climate change just keep increasing?", "trigger_span": [1133, 1168], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S20.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1320, "question_text": "How is that risky?", "trigger_span": [1291, 1318], "answer_text": "Complicated to explain the risk and return", "answer_span": [1324.0, 1347.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S78.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5588, "question_text": "What was his favorite song?", "trigger_span": [5523, 5540], "answer_text": "His favorite song always had yet not compose.", "answer_span": [5603.0, 5624.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S99.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5172, "question_text": "How long does this take?", "trigger_span": [5088, 5127], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S122.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8495, "question_text": "What contrasts with a conceptual end?", "trigger_span": [8441, 8477], "answer_text": "there is no conceptual end", "answer_span": [8503.0, 8536.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S124.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8645, "question_text": "What did the archery coach say?", "trigger_span": [8594, 8615], "answer_text": "they can't do enough", "answer_span": [8703.0, 8747.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S128.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8869, "question_text": "Why do they coach?", "trigger_span": [8703, 8732], "answer_text": "eternal struggle", "answer_span": [9029.0, 9081.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Implicit:Contingency.Purpose.Arg2-as-goal"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S33.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2408, "question_text": "How  many rings is going to hit the ten rings?", "trigger_span": [2063, 2075], "answer_text": "Every one ", "answer_span": [2469.0, 2484.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S38.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2516, "question_text": "For how many hours do you see her tenacity ", "trigger_span": [2486, 2514], "answer_text": "Three hours", "answer_span": [2630.0, 2656.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S40.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2683, "question_text": "Why is he looking up the sky?", "trigger_span": [2658, 2681], "answer_text": "Try to find the T.S", "answer_span": [2739.0, 2771.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S14.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1070, "question_text": "What exactly caused you to change your view?", "trigger_span": [817, 858], "answer_text": "The moment happened when they watched a team of all-female archers.", "answer_span": [1198.0, 1239.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous"]}
{"id": "cities.S57.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4342, "question_text": "How was the data you have ?", "trigger_span": [4211, 4246], "answer_text": "It was an incredible set of data", "answer_span": [4404.0, 4428.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S89.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6071, "question_text": "Is success really gives us ongoing quest?", "trigger_span": [6040, 6069], "answer_text": "Comparing Olympic silver medalists and bronze medalists is a success to motivate an ongoing quest.", "answer_span": [6155.0, 6220.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S91.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6361, "question_text": "How frustrated?", "trigger_span": [6292, 6359], "answer_text": "A little bit of happiness after the competition.", "answer_span": [6361.0, 6395.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "cities.S22.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1916, "question_text": "Is this a sports media network?", "trigger_span": [1891, 1914], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S132.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9083, "question_text": "Is it good to always require more?", "trigger_span": [9061, 9081], "answer_text": "that's what mastery is about", "answer_span": [9158.0, 9188.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "homeless.S30.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2776, "question_text": "What are some aspects of homelessness that are not so great?", "trigger_span": [2728, 2774], "answer_text": "The homeless suffer from addiction, life out in the elements, and getting hit by trains.", "answer_span": [2831.0, 2892.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "homeless.S37.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3022, "question_text": "What are some laws which the homeless commonly encounter?", "trigger_span": [2972, 2984], "answer_text": "It's illegal for them to sit on the sidewalk, to be wrapped in a blanket, to sleep in a car, and to be given food from a stranger.", "answer_span": [3088.0, 3139.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "homeless.S39.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3209, "question_text": "Which are some cities who have these laws?", "trigger_span": [3042, 3056], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S120.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8428, "question_text": "Why are masters not experts?", "trigger_span": [8404, 8427], "answer_text": "they realize there is no conceptual end", "answer_span": [8503.0, 8536.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S93.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6780, "question_text": "What motivate them to buy more tickets?", "trigger_span": [6725, 6778], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S99.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6964, "question_text": "How does that relevant putting goals and change our view altogether?", "trigger_span": [6910, 6962], "answer_text": "We tend to separate them at distance.", "answer_span": [6964.0, 6998.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S2.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 332, "question_text": "Have the villages come back since the war?", "trigger_span": [306, 330], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S40.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2907, "question_text": "Is sustainability attainable?", "trigger_span": [2736, 2750], "answer_text": "yes", "answer_span": [3033.0, 3069.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner"]}
{"id": "investment.S42.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3142, "question_text": "Why is it the root of growth", "trigger_span": [3055, 3069], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S44.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3261, "question_text": "Why is ESG the future?", "trigger_span": [3161, 3178], "answer_text": "lots of opportunities", "answer_span": [3261.0, 3309.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S85.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5802, "question_text": "What examples we don't know of?", "trigger_span": [5760, 5800], "answer_text": "It's Dunning-Kruger effect.", "answer_span": [5802.0, 5840.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S87.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5953, "question_text": "How can we do with knowledge?", "trigger_span": [5907, 5951], "answer_text": "Gotta learn just a bit ", "answer_span": [5966.0, 5998.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S26.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2260, "question_text": "What network?", "trigger_span": [2239, 2258], "answer_text": "It's a hip-hop network and culture spanning the east and west coast and across America.", "answer_span": [2443.0, 2459.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "cities.S28.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2461, "question_text": "Why is the Twitter segment delineated in the hip-hop network?", "trigger_span": [2314, 2358], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S32.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2745, "question_text": "How have the tensions been expressed?", "trigger_span": [2494, 2542], "answer_text": "Communities are at odds with each other, from the LGBT community, the arts, the geeks, and music.", "answer_span": [2761.0, 2817.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "cities.S36.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2880, "question_text": "Why do you think these communities are at odds with each other?", "trigger_span": [2779, 2803], "answer_text": "It shows that certain segments of the network are up in arms about certain other segments. The tech sector is blamed for gentrification.", "answer_span": [2917.0, 2932.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S41.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3370, "question_text": "Were they fined a certain dollar amount?", "trigger_span": [3321, 3330], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S43.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3574, "question_text": "What are some reasons the homeless might give for living like they do?", "trigger_span": [3401, 3441], "answer_text": "Freedom was the only reason listed in the text.", "answer_span": [3702.0, 3709.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "homeless.S45.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3711, "question_text": "What are some other reasons?", "trigger_span": [3607, 3652], "answer_text": "They also seek liberation and some are doing it as a form of rebellion.", "answer_span": [3941.0, 3980.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "homeless.S47.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3938, "question_text": "Do they find the escape they're looking for?", "trigger_span": [3921, 3936], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S88.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4693, "question_text": "How do you make the starshade fly?", "trigger_span": [4596, 4651], "answer_text": "good design", "answer_span": [4804.0, 4834.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "starshade.S90.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4878, "question_text": "It looks like what?", "trigger_span": [4858, 4876], "answer_text": "wrapped and separated later", "answer_span": [4888.0, 4941.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "starshade.S92.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4943, "question_text": "What happens after separation?", "trigger_span": [4910, 4941], "answer_text": "petals unfurl and open", "answer_span": [4943.0, 4974.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence", "Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S22.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1867, "question_text": "How can the problem be solved?", "trigger_span": [1830, 1865], "answer_text": "He models the prosthetic specifically for the patient.", "answer_span": [2178.0, 2201.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S24.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2081, "question_text": "What is different about the custom prosthetic sockets from conventional ones?", "trigger_span": [2034, 2079], "answer_text": "He uses MRIs to design a prosthetic specifically for a patient, based on that patient's anatomy.", "answer_span": [2118.0, 2167.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Implicit:Contingency.Purpose.Arg2-as-goal"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S128.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8869, "question_text": "Does anybody become an expert and overcome the feeling of not being 100% great in what they do?", "trigger_span": [8703, 8732], "answer_text": "Apparently experts do not exist as you can always become better at what you do so being a master is the ultimate. ", "answer_span": [9040.0, 9081.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Implicit:Contingency.Purpose.Arg2-as-goal"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S132.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9083, "question_text": "Does the writer of this paragraph feel more confident and like a master now?", "trigger_span": [8971, 8983], "answer_text": "The write insinuates that they do in fact see their self as a master.", "answer_span": [9158.0, 9188.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "cities.S24.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2021, "question_text": "What's happening in San Francisco?", "trigger_span": [1983, 2019], "answer_text": "Aside from sports, politics, and news, SF has more of a geek and techie influence.", "answer_span": [2184.0, 2201.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S44.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3571, "question_text": "What do you find so unique about that?", "trigger_span": [3499, 3545], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S5.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 448, "question_text": "How will this technology work?", "trigger_span": [382, 426], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S7.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 658, "question_text": "Why aren't we able to detect them?", "trigger_span": [625, 656], "answer_text": "We can detect them, but indirectly.", "answer_span": [658.0, 693.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "starshade.S9.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 747, "question_text": "What is the pale blue dot?", "trigger_span": [695, 745], "answer_text": "The pale blue dot is how the Earth looks from the furthest bounds of the solar system.", "answer_span": [865.0, 920.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous"]}
{"id": "starshade.S11.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 986, "question_text": "How will that be possible?", "trigger_span": [945, 984], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S13.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1030, "question_text": "Yes, what exactly are the challenges in accomplishing such a feat?", "trigger_span": [1012, 1029], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S81.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4346, "question_text": "How do you control petals?", "trigger_span": [4242, 4289], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S86.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4485, "question_text": "Which planets can you see?", "trigger_span": [4437, 4459], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S33.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2415, "question_text": "What is the overall meaning?", "trigger_span": [2372, 2413], "answer_text": "ESG", "answer_span": [2419.0, 2422.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "investment.S38.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2730, "question_text": "how successful is esg", "trigger_span": [2569, 2589], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S6.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 431, "question_text": "Why it's reckless to ignore them?", "trigger_span": [398, 429], "answer_text": "risking a future long-term", "answer_span": [452.0, 487.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief"]}
{"id": "investment.S8.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 625, "question_text": "How big the power to influence the institutional investors?", "trigger_span": [533, 553], "answer_text": "pension funds, foundation and endowments show a big power play", "answer_span": [625.0, 691.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S33.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2880, "question_text": "Since when? That isn't my experience.", "trigger_span": [2761, 2817], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S38.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3043, "question_text": "What exactly is happening?", "trigger_span": [2984, 3024], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S40.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3168, "question_text": "What's the sudden relevance of Rio here? We were just talking about San Francisco.", "trigger_span": [3131, 3166], "answer_text": "Rio is very diverse compared to the other two cities mentioned, Baltimore and San Francisco.", "answer_span": [3326.0, 3369.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence", "Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "cities.S42.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3405, "question_text": "Why do you think that Rio is heterogeneous and the other two cities are not?", "trigger_span": [3356, 3403], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S57.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3062, "question_text": "What happened next?", "trigger_span": [3045, 3061], "answer_text": "After telescope in the shadow, the light's has been removed", "answer_span": [3191.0, 3223.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg1-as-cond"]}
{"id": "starshade.S59.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3249, "question_text": "How dim?", "trigger_span": [3228, 3247], "answer_text": "Fine structure implied how dim", "answer_span": [3249.0, 3277.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S61.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3325, "question_text": "How can we do this in space?", "trigger_span": [3289, 3323], "answer_text": "block the light and we get to see planets ", "answer_span": [3403.0, 3433.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "starshade.S67.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3524, "question_text": "How far we can see the planets?", "trigger_span": [3501, 3522], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S90.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6222, "question_text": "What is the difference between a silver and bronze medalist after a competition?", "trigger_span": [6132, 6200], "answer_text": "Bronze medalists are just happy to have won a medal at all, while silver medalists think more about the next competition.", "answer_span": [6465.0, 6514.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S92.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6516, "question_text": "Do more silver medalists go on to win gold than bronze medalists?", "trigger_span": [6465, 6514], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S96.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6855, "question_text": "Does the gambling industry still do this?", "trigger_span": [6538, 6594], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S100.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7048, "question_text": "Do near winners go on to win more often than non-near winners?", "trigger_span": [6870, 6895], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S1.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 142, "question_text": "What is the likelihood one holds advanced lifeforms?", "trigger_span": [120, 140], "answer_text": "a new telescope that's capable of seeing further distances to find another Earth-life planet", "answer_span": [184.0, 233.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S5.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 448, "question_text": "What other projects are being worked on?", "trigger_span": [367, 392], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S2.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 267, "question_text": "What sustainability we are talking about?", "trigger_span": [251, 265], "answer_text": "environmental and social issues are the main concern in sustainability.", "answer_span": [327.0, 383.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "cities.S48.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3725, "question_text": "How do you think Rio came to be this way?", "trigger_span": [3571, 3629], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S52.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3882, "question_text": "Is BTS included in that category?", "trigger_span": [3725, 3740], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S30.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2285, "question_text": "How long has she been doing archery to have that amount of strength? She sounds very proficient.", "trigger_span": [2232, 2283], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S37.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2486, "question_text": "How long did she keep at it?", "trigger_span": [2451, 2484], "answer_text": "She kept at it for three hours.", "answer_span": [2486.0, 2515.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S39.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2626, "question_text": "She must've put in a lot of effort, huh?", "trigger_span": [2581, 2624], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S48.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3388, "question_text": "How is ESG driving hard results?", "trigger_span": [3352, 3387], "answer_text": "more mobile workplace", "answer_span": [3660.0, 3681.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "AltLex:Hypophora", "AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "investment.S52.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3532, "question_text": "what is the cloud enviroment?", "trigger_span": [3466, 3503], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S110.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8014, "question_text": "What type of win?", "trigger_span": [7904, 7912], "answer_text": "leading edge", "answer_span": [8057.0, 8073.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S117.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8255, "question_text": "why would they put imperfections in textiles?", "trigger_span": [8216, 8253], "answer_text": "called a spirit line", "answer_span": [8276.0, 8287.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S41.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2739, "question_text": "What kind of books did they write?", "trigger_span": [2658, 2699], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S43.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3023, "question_text": "Why do you think that is?", "trigger_span": [2773, 2825], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S45.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3144, "question_text": "Did it move you in a meaningful way?", "trigger_span": [3023, 3071], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S51.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3314, "question_text": "What is the subtle difference?", "trigger_span": [3262, 3304], "answer_text": "Mastery is not a commitment to a goal, but a constant pursuit.", "answer_span": [3443.0, 3469.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S17.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1666, "question_text": "What network are you referring to?", "trigger_span": [1352, 1370], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S19.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1226, "question_text": "How far away is that from Earth?", "trigger_span": [1118, 1153], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S119.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8404, "question_text": "is weaving a bad job?", "trigger_span": [8334, 8340], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S121.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8479, "question_text": "what is a conceptual end?", "trigger_span": [8463, 8477], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S123.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8538, "question_text": "What is a master?", "trigger_span": [8487, 8494], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S125.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8749, "question_text": "Why tell them out of earshot?", "trigger_span": [8645, 8674], "answer_text": "not enouigh techniques", "answer_span": [8749.0, 8801.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S131.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9040, "question_text": "He is giving himself to what?", "trigger_span": [9004, 9026], "answer_text": "unfinished path", "answer_span": [9040.0, 9081.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Implicit:Contingency.Purpose.Arg2-as-goal"]}
{"id": "starshade.S1.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 142, "question_text": "How many planets are there in the universe?", "trigger_span": [104, 140], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S64.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3435, "question_text": "What is the purpose of doing this in space?", "trigger_span": [3279, 3323], "answer_text": "We could see planets by doing this in space.", "answer_span": [3501.0, 3522.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S68.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3566, "question_text": "Did this suggestion actually take place?", "trigger_span": [3534, 3564], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S14.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1246, "question_text": "What other issues are they besides environmental and social?", "trigger_span": [1193, 1244], "answer_text": "They are economic issues.", "answer_span": [1246.0, 1269.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "homeless.S6.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 465, "question_text": "What borders would you dream of crossing?", "trigger_span": [436, 443], "answer_text": "Worlds other than their own", "answer_span": [659.0, 665.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S8.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 755, "question_text": "Where have you been as a documentary photographer?", "trigger_span": [741, 753], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S10.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1017, "question_text": "Have youe ever travelled as a hitchhiker?", "trigger_span": [1004, 1015], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S23.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1952, "question_text": "Anywhere else other than San Francisco?", "trigger_span": [1937, 1950], "answer_text": "Baltimore and other cities", "answer_span": [2107.0, 2133.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "cities.S25.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2135, "question_text": "What other subjects are happening?", "trigger_span": [2038, 2078], "answer_text": "geeks and techs are also taking over", "answer_span": [2184.0, 2201.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S13.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1030, "question_text": "When will create a fuel source to power a ship for that length of travel?", "trigger_span": [986, 1011], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S21.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1472, "question_text": "What can we do instead of ignoring the issues?", "trigger_span": [1452, 1470], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast", "Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast", "Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S23.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1520, "question_text": "What should I do instead?", "trigger_span": [1497, 1518], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S25.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1728, "question_text": "Do investors look at anything other than financial data?", "trigger_span": [1673, 1726], "answer_text": "They should look at environmental, social, and governance issues.", "answer_span": [1912.0, 1964.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S27.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1895, "question_text": "What else should investors be looking at?", "trigger_span": [1871, 1893], "answer_text": "They should also look at environmental, social, and governance factors.", "answer_span": [1912.0, 1964.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S29.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2125, "question_text": "What is involved with governance?", "trigger_span": [1990, 2000], "answer_text": "Governance includes the company's boards, investors, and general oversight.", "answer_span": [2287.0, 2335.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S7.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 658, "question_text": "Are any advances being made in regards to longer space travel?", "trigger_span": [546, 589], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S60.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3279, "question_text": "How is the corona involved with Spitzer's suggestion?", "trigger_span": [3231, 3277], "answer_text": "Spitzer suggested that we do this same thing, but in space.", "answer_span": [3279.0, 3323.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "cities.S44.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3571, "question_text": "They are all getting along?", "trigger_span": [3424, 3452], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S48.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3725, "question_text": "What other groups are in the vicinity?", "trigger_span": [3599, 3619], "answer_text": "other groups include those interested in funk, rap and stand-up comedy", "answer_span": [3773.0, 3805.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S35.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2367, "question_text": "Why is it important that investors look at ESG?", "trigger_span": [2125, 2154], "answer_text": "Looking at the ESG makes investing more sustainable.", "answer_span": [2461.0, 2522.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S81.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5626, "question_text": "How can we stay at our own leading edge?", "trigger_span": [5427, 5463], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S86.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5841, "question_text": "How does the Dunning-Kruger effect help?", "trigger_span": [5818, 5839], "answer_text": "It can lead you to learn/do/know more.", "answer_span": [6027.0, 6069.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S88.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5999, "question_text": "How does learning that you don't know much help you?", "trigger_span": [5966, 5996], "answer_text": "A near win, or not knowing everything you thought you did, can make you want to know/learn more.", "answer_span": [6027.0, 6069.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "starshade.S9.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 747, "question_text": "How many pale blue dots could there be in our galaxy alone?", "trigger_span": [732, 745], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S11.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 986, "question_text": "Are scientists any closer to having astronauts travel further than the Moon?", "trigger_span": [922, 941], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S46.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2764, "question_text": "What exactly Lyman Spitzer did to earn the title father of the space telescope?", "trigger_span": [2638, 2651], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S53.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2828, "question_text": "When was that?", "trigger_span": [2788, 2826], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S55.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3008, "question_text": "What happened next after the moon blocks the sun?", "trigger_span": [2828, 2859], "answer_text": "Almost like I can see something at the back", "answer_span": [3008.0, 3037.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S19.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1226, "question_text": "Why would we care to see Earth again?", "trigger_span": [1197, 1224], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S33.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2880, "question_text": "How are they not getting along?", "trigger_span": [2710, 2743], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S38.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3043, "question_text": "What does that mean?", "trigger_span": [2917, 2932], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S40.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3168, "question_text": "How are they coping with gentrification?", "trigger_span": [3137, 3166], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S42.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3405, "question_text": "So they aren't dealing with gentrification at all?", "trigger_span": [3326, 3355], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S46.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3432, "question_text": "What is an example of leveraging ESG?", "trigger_span": [3314, 3355], "answer_text": "use the cloud", "answer_span": [3454.0, 3503.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "AltLex:Hypophora", "AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "investment.S53.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3629, "question_text": "Did State Street do anything else to drive results?", "trigger_span": [3586, 3627], "answer_text": "lower costs and emissions", "answer_span": [3804.0, 3858.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S55.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3860, "question_text": "Are there other environmental benefits?", "trigger_span": [3852, 3858], "answer_text": "like taking cars off the road", "answer_span": [3871.0, 3916.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation", "AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "homeless.S2.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 239, "question_text": "What made you want to run away?", "trigger_span": [117, 121], "answer_text": "They dreamed of traveling accross borders.", "answer_span": [591.0, 601.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "starshade.S49.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2788, "question_text": "What was first suggested by Lyman Spitzer?", "trigger_span": [2612, 2651], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S54.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2901, "question_text": "What does the corona have to do with Spitzer's suggestion?", "trigger_span": [2863, 2889], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S56.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3039, "question_text": "What does this have to do with Spitzer's suggestion?", "trigger_span": [2913, 2927], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S58.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3115, "question_text": "What does a shadow have to do with Spitzer's suggestion?", "trigger_span": [3067, 3095], "answer_text": "If a camera is placed in the shadow, you can see the corona.", "answer_span": [3139.0, 3160.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S57.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3937, "question_text": "Are there social benefits involved?", "trigger_span": [3921, 3936], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S59.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4125, "question_text": "What did the water business do?", "trigger_span": [4109, 4123], "answer_text": "met global demand", "answer_span": [4357.0, 4422.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S61.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4172, "question_text": "Did Pentair profit?", "trigger_span": [4134, 4148], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S67.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4424, "question_text": "Was Pentair socially responsible?", "trigger_span": [4236, 4251], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S113.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8146, "question_text": "What creation myth has the deliberate incomplete?", "trigger_span": [8088, 8144], "answer_text": "Navajo spirit line", "answer_span": [8274.0, 8306.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S118.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8361, "question_text": "Why do the creators want a way out?", "trigger_span": [8325, 8359], "answer_text": "to keep working", "answer_span": [8370.0, 8402.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S96.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5088, "question_text": "How does it fly out?", "trigger_span": [5020, 5039], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S100.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5212, "question_text": "How many planets orbiting?", "trigger_span": [5178, 5201], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S42.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2896, "question_text": "Why culture is there little thats vocation about any more ", "trigger_span": [2827, 2859], "answer_text": "American culture ", "answer_span": [2919.0, 2952.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S44.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3036, "question_text": "Why do you have to align you body for three hours ", "trigger_span": [2990, 3021], "answer_text": "I did that in order to hit the target ", "answer_span": [3181.0, 3225.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S48.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3262, "question_text": "How many rings is success hitting ?", "trigger_span": [3144, 3179], "answer_text": "Its hitting ten rings ", "answer_span": [3262.0, 3304.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S61.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4172, "question_text": "Why is it a really big bet?", "trigger_span": [4125, 4148], "answer_text": "There's more growth in water than in power tools.", "answer_span": [4223.0, 4271.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "investment.S67.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4424, "question_text": "When did the New World become the New World?", "trigger_span": [4314, 4347], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S113.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8146, "question_text": "What room are you in, or what do you mean?", "trigger_span": [7902, 7925], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S118.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8361, "question_text": "Do the Navajo think that the passion they put into creating things gets that creative energy stuck in what they create and may cause issues losing that creativity in their work if they DON'T make a spirit line?", "trigger_span": [8322, 8359], "answer_text": "A spirit line is made so that they have a reson to continue making work so I was right in thinking that this is why a spirit line is made.", "answer_span": [8370.0, 8402.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S120.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8428, "question_text": "What makes someone an expert then?", "trigger_span": [8404, 8427], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S37.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2486, "question_text": "Did she finally hit the target?", "trigger_span": [2451, 2484], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S39.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2626, "question_text": "Are they practicing again tomorrow?", "trigger_span": [2516, 2542], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S41.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2739, "question_text": "How were the other archers?", "trigger_span": [2626, 2656], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S43.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3023, "question_text": "What is good about American culture?", "trigger_span": [2739, 2771], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S45.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3144, "question_text": "Did you try your hand at archery?", "trigger_span": [3055, 3097], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S51.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3314, "question_text": "What is mastery?", "trigger_span": [3262, 3312], "answer_text": "mastery is constantly pursuing a goal or success", "answer_span": [3479.0, 3495.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S122.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8495, "question_text": "Is being a master at something better than being an expert?", "trigger_span": [8479, 8494], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S124.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8645, "question_text": "Does the archery coach consider their self a master?", "trigger_span": [8586, 8615], "answer_text": "the coach believes a path is always unfinished and requires more to be even better considering themselves a master at archery.", "answer_span": [9040.0, 9081.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Implicit:Contingency.Purpose.Arg2-as-goal"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S16.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1027, "question_text": "What converts success into mastery?", "trigger_span": [981, 1026], "answer_text": "Almost being successful turns it into mastery", "answer_span": [1092.0, 1132.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S20.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1134, "question_text": "anything else?", "trigger_span": [1092, 1132], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S12.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1102, "question_text": "Why is the vagabond a creature from the past?", "trigger_span": [1096, 1100], "answer_text": "It creates images of hobos travelling.", "answer_span": [1454.0, 1460.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S16.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1360, "question_text": "Why would a hobo be covered in coal?", "trigger_span": [1193, 1197], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S27.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2379, "question_text": "Any other employees?", "trigger_span": [2341, 2358], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S29.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2698, "question_text": "How much wealth?", "trigger_span": [2603, 2658], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S35.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2859, "question_text": "Why arent they getting along?", "trigger_span": [2761, 2817], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S2.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 205, "question_text": "What did you learn exactly?", "trigger_span": [177, 203], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S20.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1514, "question_text": "What is a steel arterie?", "trigger_span": [1483, 1491], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S1.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 241, "question_text": "What city are you speaking of?", "trigger_span": [120, 126], "answer_text": "Baltimore", "answer_span": [529.0, 538.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Disjunction", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "cities.S5.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 431, "question_text": "What kind of map are we talking about?", "trigger_span": [426, 429], "answer_text": "A map showing the relationship of people in Baltimore.", "answer_span": [529.0, 538.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "cities.S7.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 614, "question_text": "How many people are in Baltimore?", "trigger_span": [529, 538], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S9.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 846, "question_text": "What is TEDx?", "trigger_span": [810, 814], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S11.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1147, "question_text": "Why are African Americans and Latinos worries different than geeks?", "trigger_span": [1023, 1028], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S10.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 774, "question_text": "The neighbor stole it?", "trigger_span": [748, 773], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S12.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 860, "question_text": "How much was it?", "trigger_span": [774, 799], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S164.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9365, "question_text": "Is it a big hoax or is it real?", "trigger_span": [9305, 9320], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S13.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1339, "question_text": "Why do people not travel more?", "trigger_span": [1289, 1298], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S19.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1553, "question_text": "What makes peopel identify with a certain area more than another?", "trigger_span": [1449, 1457], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S129.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7496, "question_text": "What do institutional investors do for money?", "trigger_span": [7335, 7348], "answer_text": "They invest in the stock market and bond market", "answer_span": [7594.0, 7600.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S124.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8645, "question_text": "What do you mean?", "trigger_span": [8613, 8643], "answer_text": "ways to win", "answer_span": [8777.0, 8801.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S128.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8869, "question_text": "How does that apply in practical terms here?", "trigger_span": [8834, 8867], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S132.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9083, "question_text": "What is your unfinished path?", "trigger_span": [9040, 9055], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S17.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1514, "question_text": "Where do they travel at specifically?", "trigger_span": [1454, 1491], "answer_text": "They just travel without going anywhere specfic", "answer_span": [1575.0, 1592.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S52.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3882, "question_text": "Are there any conflicts?", "trigger_span": [3847, 3862], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S30.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2285, "question_text": "Did she make the shot?", "trigger_span": [2026, 2037], "answer_text": "She made several bad hits.", "answer_span": [2285.0, 2306.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S145.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8406, "question_text": "Is it exaggerated or overstated?", "trigger_span": [8335, 8387], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S150.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8591, "question_text": "What kinds of risks?", "trigger_span": [8540, 8589], "answer_text": "Not very urgent risks", "answer_span": [8604.0, 8638.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "investment.S152.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8791, "question_text": "what type of scientific consensus?", "trigger_span": [8769, 8789], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S154.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8957, "question_text": "Where at then?", "trigger_span": [8918, 8955], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S156.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9075, "question_text": "Does insurance protect you?", "trigger_span": [8992, 9038], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S160.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9246, "question_text": "How are we reducing risks to our planet?", "trigger_span": [9153, 9184], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S9.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 909, "question_text": "What kinds of wanderers are there in the US?", "trigger_span": [853, 907], "answer_text": "basically people with no settled place to live in, hobos, hitchhikes, tramps, travelers, etc.", "answer_span": [980.0, 1036.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "homeless.S11.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1038, "question_text": "Are there still people who do this because they choose to do it?", "trigger_span": [921, 934], "answer_text": "There is a community of creative people across the country that are vagabonds.", "answer_span": [1285.0, 1358.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S13.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1230, "question_text": "So, hobos still exist?", "trigger_span": [1064, 1100], "answer_text": "There are communities of vagabonds in the US.", "answer_span": [1285.0, 1358.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S19.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1414, "question_text": "What do they see that other Americans don't?", "trigger_span": [1360, 1400], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S17.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1619, "question_text": "Is there a different way to make prosthetics so that they are more comfortable to wear??", "trigger_span": [1453, 1497], "answer_text": "For his PhD project, he designed prosthetics that are more comfortable than conventional ones.", "answer_span": [1968.0, 2004.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S52.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3432, "question_text": "What is as same as excellence ?", "trigger_span": [3314, 3342], "answer_text": "Mastery", "answer_span": [3432.0, 3469.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S1.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 123, "question_text": "Where would you go if you ran away?", "trigger_span": [113, 121], "answer_text": "She would go to foreign countries.", "answer_span": [416.0, 443.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "homeless.S5.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 347, "question_text": "Where were you thinking of doing that wouldn't be routine or boring?", "trigger_span": [326, 345], "answer_text": "She would meet unusual people that didn't live routine lives", "answer_span": [469.0, 501.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S26.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2329, "question_text": "Who manufactures the prosthetic?", "trigger_span": [2285, 2327], "answer_text": "They use a 3D printer to 'print' the socket.", "answer_span": [2338.0, 2393.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Implicit:Contingency.Purpose.Arg2-as-goal"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S28.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2532, "question_text": "Is there anything else you can do with the data to help the patient?", "trigger_span": [2472, 2488], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S30.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2793, "question_text": "Are most of your patients military veterans?", "trigger_span": [2610, 2622], "answer_text": "Some of people helped were injured in a war.", "answer_span": [3086.0, 3119.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S32.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 3040, "question_text": "Are you sharing your research and processes with other doctors?", "trigger_span": [2913, 2932], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S88.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4693, "question_text": "How is it held right in the telescopes shadow?", "trigger_span": [4657, 4691], "answer_text": "It is wrapped around the hub and it separates from the telescope.", "answer_span": [4888.0, 4941.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "starshade.S90.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4878, "question_text": "What exactly is the design that you have come up with?", "trigger_span": [4804, 4834], "answer_text": "The starshade is an object that is wrapped around a hub and separates from the telescope.", "answer_span": [4888.0, 4941.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "starshade.S92.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4943, "question_text": "How far does it separate from the telescope?", "trigger_span": [4910, 4941], "answer_text": "It separates and flies out 50,000 kilometers away from the telescope.", "answer_span": [5045.0, 5067.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "starshade.S96.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5088, "question_text": "How many petals are part of this starshade?", "trigger_span": [4943, 4960], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S144.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8234, "question_text": "What would cause the world to become less secure?", "trigger_span": [8206, 8210], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S148.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8406, "question_text": "Why would this risk be exaggerated?", "trigger_span": [8364, 8375], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S113.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5791, "question_text": "What happens if they don't go to the same place?", "trigger_span": [5710, 5744], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S118.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6014, "question_text": "What's the next step?", "trigger_span": [5988, 6012], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S120.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6139, "question_text": "How many more tests do you have to do?", "trigger_span": [6014, 6047], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S122.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6354, "question_text": "How do you plan to do this?", "trigger_span": [6198, 6231], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S13.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 958, "question_text": "Why is success just a 'moment'?", "trigger_span": [876, 895], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S100.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5212, "question_text": "Will a starshade be made all one size or will a starshade vary in size depending on what star to shadow?", "trigger_span": [5093, 5127], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S6.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 424, "question_text": "What type of elements?", "trigger_span": [360, 379], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S8.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 559, "question_text": "What did she think about her early works?", "trigger_span": [435, 483], "answer_text": "She didn't think too highly of it", "answer_span": [578.0, 612.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S100.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5212, "question_text": "How long does it last?", "trigger_span": [5144, 5170], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S46.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3432, "question_text": "What's the example?", "trigger_span": [3388, 3430], "answer_text": "in 2012, state street migration", "answer_span": [3435.0, 3478.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "AltLex:Hypophora", "AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "investment.S53.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3629, "question_text": "What are some other automation projects?", "trigger_span": [3599, 3627], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S55.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3860, "question_text": "What else are you doing for sustainability?", "trigger_span": [3804, 3858], "answer_text": "sold business to reinvest in sustainability", "answer_span": [4078.0, 4123.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Succession", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "investment.S57.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3937, "question_text": "What else are you doing for sustainability?", "trigger_span": [3860, 3916], "answer_text": "pentair sale used to fund sustainable business", "answer_span": [4078.0, 4123.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Succession", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "investment.S140.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7942, "question_text": "What does ESG stand for?", "trigger_span": [7921, 7924], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S81.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4346, "question_text": "Is it expensive?", "trigger_span": [4198, 4237], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S86.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4485, "question_text": "Is it clear?", "trigger_span": [4364, 4376], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S88.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4693, "question_text": "Is it modifiable? ", "trigger_span": [4562, 4591], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S113.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8146, "question_text": "What different ways?", "trigger_span": [7856, 7884], "answer_text": "Intentionally leave an imperfection", "answer_span": [8291.0, 8306.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S118.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8361, "question_text": "A way out to what?", "trigger_span": [8334, 8359], "answer_text": "Continue making work", "answer_span": [8382.0, 8402.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S120.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8428, "question_text": "What else do masters do?", "trigger_span": [8404, 8427], "answer_text": "Finish what they started", "answer_span": [8441.0, 8477.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S122.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8495, "question_text": "What else makes them masters?", "trigger_span": [8479, 8494], "answer_text": "They realize there are no endings", "answer_span": [8503.0, 8536.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "investment.S59.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4125, "question_text": "Any other examples?", "trigger_span": [3937, 3952], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S126.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6732, "question_text": "Do you expect to find an environment similar to Earth?", "trigger_span": [6697, 6730], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S128.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6812, "question_text": "What if it doesn't work?", "trigger_span": [6778, 6810], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S78.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5008, "question_text": "More of what?", "trigger_span": [4981, 5006], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S85.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5239, "question_text": "Who determines these best practices?", "trigger_span": [5162, 5190], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S87.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5339, "question_text": "Outperformed in general or their individual history?", "trigger_span": [5268, 5308], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg1-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S124.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8645, "question_text": "Told you what?", "trigger_span": [8586, 8615], "answer_text": "They can't do enough", "answer_span": [8703.0, 8732.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S128.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8869, "question_text": "How to overcome this feeling?", "trigger_span": [8749, 8776], "answer_text": "Accepting imperfection", "answer_span": [8989.0, 9038.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Implicit:Contingency.Purpose.Arg2-as-goal"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S132.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9083, "question_text": "How to accept this?", "trigger_span": [9040, 9081], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S138.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7771, "question_text": "What exactly does GDP stand for?", "trigger_span": [7679, 7682], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S22.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1758, "question_text": "What about when it rains?", "trigger_span": [1645, 1673], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S24.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2013, "question_text": "So the underbelly of society make up most of the hobos?", "trigger_span": [1926, 1947], "answer_text": "All sorts of people become hobos", "answer_span": [2013.0, 2044.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "homeless.S26.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2208, "question_text": "IS this the main reason people become hobos?", "trigger_span": [2096, 2126], "answer_text": "People also want to live off the wasteful consumer society", "answer_span": [2222.0, 2244.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "homeless.S28.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2551, "question_text": "Do any hobos work?", "trigger_span": [2299, 2309], "answer_text": "Most hobos want to do other things besides work", "answer_span": [2655.0, 2663.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous"]}
{"id": "starshade.S90.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4878, "question_text": "Is it expensive?", "trigger_span": [4733, 4750], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S92.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4943, "question_text": "Is it easily damaged?", "trigger_span": [4913, 4941], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S96.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5088, "question_text": "How do the petals unfurl?", "trigger_span": [4947, 4960], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S7.Q1", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 543, "question_text": "Were you able to fulfill your daydreams of traveling?", "trigger_span": [390, 409], "answer_text": "She was able to fulfill her daydreams by becoming a documentary photographer.", "answer_span": [686.0, 723.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence", "Explicit:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner"]}
{"id": "starshade.S124.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6603, "question_text": "how are you going to get an occulter in front of it?", "trigger_span": [6412, 6431], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S32.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2709, "question_text": "Do they only live on the streets?", "trigger_span": [2551, 2583], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S36.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2831, "question_text": "Do people eventually find themselves?", "trigger_span": [2783, 2807], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S14.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1553, "question_text": "What is your town's population?", "trigger_span": [1192, 1207], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S21.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1763, "question_text": "What type of sports?", "trigger_span": [1651, 1664], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S134.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7578, "question_text": "Why is the global stock market worth 55 trillion dollars?", "trigger_span": [7557, 7559], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S136.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7645, "question_text": "Who has the most power over all of this money?", "trigger_span": [7605, 7613], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S93.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5661, "question_text": "What is the vanguard?", "trigger_span": [5620, 5652], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S99.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5967, "question_text": "So, is Hesta not interested in the environment?", "trigger_span": [5661, 5702], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S97.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5987, "question_text": "How do they measure risk?", "trigger_span": [5805, 5838], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S88.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4693, "question_text": "Which planets can it see?", "trigger_span": [4596, 4632], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S90.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4878, "question_text": "What is the design?", "trigger_span": [4819, 4853], "answer_text": "It's wrapped around a hub", "answer_span": [4888.0, 4908.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S81.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4346, "question_text": "Why control diffraction?", "trigger_span": [4318, 4344], "answer_text": "They're creating a shadow", "answer_span": [4357.0, 4376.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S86.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4485, "question_text": "What planets?", "trigger_span": [4437, 4468], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S52.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2788, "question_text": "What does a solar eclipse have to do with the new tech?", "trigger_span": [2764, 2786], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S92.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4943, "question_text": "What does it do next?", "trigger_span": [4910, 4941], "answer_text": "The petals unfurl turning around the telescope", "answer_span": [4947.0, 5002.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence", "Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence", "Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "starshade.S96.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5088, "question_text": "What planets does it see?", "trigger_span": [5032, 5067], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S100.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5212, "question_text": "What planets are orbiting?", "trigger_span": [5178, 5210], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S46.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3432, "question_text": "What business results are they achieving?", "trigger_span": [3322, 3355], "answer_text": "Migrating applications to the cloud", "answer_span": [3454.0, 3503.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "AltLex:Hypophora", "AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "investment.S53.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3629, "question_text": "What projects?", "trigger_span": [3589, 3627], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S55.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3860, "question_text": "What other initiatives?", "trigger_span": [3629, 3650], "answer_text": "Pentair investing in water", "answer_span": [4109.0, 4123.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Succession", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "investment.S89.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5445, "question_text": "Who doubted that it would be compatible?", "trigger_span": [5387, 5443], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S91.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5600, "question_text": "Engaged in the environment?", "trigger_span": [5538, 5599], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S106.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6356, "question_text": "CalPERS or Hesta is moving in this direction?", "trigger_span": [6232, 6293], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Q/A"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Q/A"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S108.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6532, "question_text": "What are the three forms of capital?", "trigger_span": [6508, 6530], "answer_text": "the three forms are financial, human, and physical", "answer_span": [6532.0, 6562.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S112.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6604, "question_text": "Why does ESG cause concern?", "trigger_span": [6576, 6601], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S116.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6845, "question_text": "Does this mean they aren't taking enough risks?", "trigger_span": [6665, 6696], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S57.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3937, "question_text": "What else have you done?", "trigger_span": [3918, 3936], "answer_text": "Pentair reinvest in water", "answer_span": [4078.0, 4123.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Succession", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "investment.S59.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4125, "question_text": "What did that accomplish?", "trigger_span": [4078, 4123], "answer_text": "More growth in water", "answer_span": [4223.0, 4251.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "investment.S61.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4172, "question_text": "Yes, why did they do that?", "trigger_span": [4150, 4171], "answer_text": "More growth in water business", "answer_span": [4231.0, 4271.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "investment.S67.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4424, "question_text": "How do you accommodate all of those people?", "trigger_span": [4357, 4399], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S61.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4172, "question_text": "What was Pentair's motivation?", "trigger_span": [4150, 4171], "answer_text": "untapped market", "answer_span": [4357.0, 4422.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S67.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4424, "question_text": "Did their bet pay off?", "trigger_span": [4223, 4271], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S113.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8146, "question_text": "How are the different ways?", "trigger_span": [7848, 7870], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S118.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8361, "question_text": "How does that apply here?", "trigger_span": [8325, 8359], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S120.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8428, "question_text": "Do you consider yourself a master?", "trigger_span": [8404, 8411], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S122.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8495, "question_text": "What's the conceptual end for you?", "trigger_span": [8463, 8477], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S102.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6050, "question_text": "CalPERS is another retirement fund?", "trigger_span": [6022, 6048], "answer_text": "CalPERS is a pension fund", "answer_span": [6050.0, 6098.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S104.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6232, "question_text": "So is CalPERS a competitor of Hesta!", "trigger_span": [6204, 6230], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S55.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3860, "question_text": "What are the initiatives exactly?", "trigger_span": [3629, 3681], "answer_text": "Reducing the toxins in the air caused by 21,000 cars no longer being in use.", "answer_span": [3871.0, 3916.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation", "AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "investment.S57.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3937, "question_text": "Why is this awesome to the writer?", "trigger_span": [3918, 3936], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S59.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4125, "question_text": "Why did the power tools company reinvested into the water business instead?", "trigger_span": [4078, 4123], "answer_text": "There's more growth in water than in power tools", "answer_span": [4223.0, 4271.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S1.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 177, "question_text": "Why do you admire Elizabeth Murray?", "trigger_span": [151, 175], "answer_text": "The author learned a lot from her.", "answer_span": [177.0, 203.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S5.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 344, "question_text": "Why did you specifically like her paintings from the 1970s?", "trigger_span": [295, 342], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S7.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 485, "question_text": "What motifs and elements showed up again later in her work?", "trigger_span": [355, 404], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S9.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 645, "question_text": "What made the early painting so different from later works?", "trigger_span": [485, 518], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S11.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 801, "question_text": "Why did she think the trashed painting wasn't good enough to keep?", "trigger_span": [697, 728], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S38.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2516, "question_text": "What is \"she\" doing?", "trigger_span": [2451, 2484], "answer_text": "Something with archery", "answer_span": [2544.0, 2562.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S126.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7472, "question_text": "Why is institutional investors' money important in sustainability?", "trigger_span": [7451, 7471], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S133.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7524, "question_text": "Why is it funny that institutional investors have a lot of money?", "trigger_span": [7472, 7481], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S135.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7615, "question_text": "How is the bond market important to sustainability?", "trigger_span": [7582, 7600], "answer_text": "The amount of money involved can be used to address society's problems.", "answer_span": [7781.0, 7825.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S137.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7731, "question_text": "Why is it important that the global stock and bond markets have 8.5 times the US GDP?", "trigger_span": [7652, 7693], "answer_text": "It shows just how much money is tied up in those markets.", "answer_span": [7738.0, 7769.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S19.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1070, "question_text": "Who decides someone has mastered an art?", "trigger_span": [997, 1026], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S46.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3432, "question_text": "What is ESG?", "trigger_span": [3322, 3355], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S53.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3629, "question_text": "What are the applications, what exactly do they do?", "trigger_span": [3454, 3503], "answer_text": "Means to reduce amount of carbon emitted from a lot of cars.", "answer_span": [3892.0, 3916.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation", "AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S40.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2683, "question_text": "What/who is T.S.?", "trigger_span": [2665, 2681], "answer_text": "It was just cut off and should have been T.S. Eliot, the author.", "answer_span": [2683.0, 2688.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S139.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7883, "question_text": "How can the money in the markets be used to clean up the environment and feed people?", "trigger_span": [7832, 7881], "answer_text": "If investors made ESG part of the investment it could be used to help with these challenges.", "answer_span": [7978.0, 8021.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "investment.S141.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8105, "question_text": "What is ESG?", "trigger_span": [7921, 7924], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S147.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8288, "question_text": "How can we ensure there is clean air and water for years to come?", "trigger_span": [8254, 8287], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S65.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3566, "question_text": "why block the light?", "trigger_span": [3403, 3433], "answer_text": "the light shines so they can't see through the lense.", "answer_span": [3688.0, 3732.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "starshade.S70.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3676, "question_text": "Why does it not work?", "trigger_span": [3640, 3674], "answer_text": "all the light stops them from seeing ", "answer_span": [3845.0, 3884.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S67.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4837, "question_text": "Did everyone arrange themselves as they did for a reason?", "trigger_span": [4718, 4751], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S33.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2408, "question_text": "What is the \"ten ring\"?", "trigger_span": [2089, 2105], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S1.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 223, "question_text": "What changes should investors be looking for?", "trigger_span": [127, 180], "answer_text": "Investors should be paying attention to cultural issues that will direct the marketplace.", "answer_span": [327.0, 383.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S5.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 385, "question_text": "What sort of sustainability investments should investors be looking for?", "trigger_span": [274, 288], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S7.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 489, "question_text": "How can investors keep from ignoring sustainable investments?", "trigger_span": [393, 429], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S77.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4981, "question_text": "Is \"okay\" really what a stockholder wants to see?", "trigger_span": [4961, 4972], "answer_text": "No", "answer_span": [4981.0, 4993.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "investment.S83.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5008, "question_text": "How do we get more in terms of performance?", "trigger_span": [4995, 5006], "answer_text": "Some companies with sustainable practices are outperforming their counterparts.", "answer_span": [5008.0, 5050.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S129.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9083, "question_text": "What type of team is being referenced?", "trigger_span": [8743, 8747], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S134.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9190, "question_text": "What is being mastered?", "trigger_span": [9166, 9188], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S136.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9424, "question_text": "Are we comparing art to a sport?", "trigger_span": [9355, 9397], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S72.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4958, "question_text": "Why is it good to strive to be perfect when it cannot be reached?", "trigger_span": [4912, 4956], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S74.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5141, "question_text": "Again why is this something worth pursuing?", "trigger_span": [5051, 5094], "answer_text": "Acheiving these near wins is better than not trying and keeps us heading in a positive direction.", "answer_span": [5379.0, 5415.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S76.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5368, "question_text": "What else are Ben's triumphs for?", "trigger_span": [5309, 5366], "answer_text": "Having near wins makes of thrive and stay sharp.", "answer_span": [5417.0, 5463.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S80.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5465, "question_text": "Are there any other reasons to pursue mastery?", "trigger_span": [5417, 5463], "answer_text": "Looking forward to what is to come is a source of happiness.", "answer_span": [5527.0, 5582.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S9.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 693, "question_text": "How will institutional investors play the biggest role in sustainability investments?", "trigger_span": [548, 623], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S11.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 842, "question_text": "Why isn't sustainable investing as complicated as I think it is?", "trigger_span": [708, 764], "answer_text": "Sustainability will be important partly due to population growth.", "answer_span": [882.0, 932.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S13.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1017, "question_text": "How does the growing population effect the investment market and sustainable products?", "trigger_span": [934, 989], "answer_text": "We deplete resources faster than they replenish and of course climate change is increasing with all our usage.", "answer_span": [1017.0, 1081.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S19.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1246, "question_text": "What other issues are these?", "trigger_span": [1183, 1244], "answer_text": "This is an economic issue too.", "answer_span": [1246.0, 1269.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S33.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2415, "question_text": "How is human capital defined?", "trigger_span": [2141, 2154], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S38.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2730, "question_text": "What are \"productive and sustainable outcomes\"?", "trigger_span": [2693, 2728], "answer_text": "CEOs see sustainability as the root to growth in innovation.", "answer_span": [3024.0, 3069.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner"]}
{"id": "investment.S139.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7883, "question_text": "How does institutional investors money go from markets to helping these good causes?", "trigger_span": [7832, 7881], "answer_text": "By allocating capital to companies working to solve these problems.", "answer_span": [7978.0, 8008.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S84.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5626, "question_text": "Is there more wisdom to be learned from mastery?", "trigger_span": [5465, 5507], "answer_text": "As we keep learning we discover things we thought we knew we didn't know.", "answer_span": [5742.0, 5777.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "starshade.S78.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4239, "question_text": "What do they mean by \"we can see a planet\"?", "trigger_span": [4063, 4082], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S85.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4378, "question_text": "Are they doing artwork with a flower?", "trigger_span": [4245, 4289], "answer_text": " 50,000 kilometers away from the telescope ", "answer_span": [4610.0, 4651.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S87.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4534, "question_text": "Are they talking about planets or flowers?", "trigger_span": [4437, 4464], "answer_text": " 50,000 kilometers away from the telescope ", "answer_span": [4610.0, 4651.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S70.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4814, "question_text": "Is this pursuit of mastery a good or bad thing?", "trigger_span": [4680, 4733], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S40.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2203, "question_text": "What causes the light to diffract?", "trigger_span": [2163, 2201], "answer_text": "The telescope diffracts the light apparently.", "answer_span": [2203.0, 2239.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S42.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2372, "question_text": "How do we fix the scattering light problem so we can see better?", "trigger_span": [2323, 2370], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S44.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2544, "question_text": "What makes the colleagues' tech the coolest?", "trigger_span": [2515, 2542], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S48.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2742, "question_text": "What's the suggestion that Lyman Spitzer made?", "trigger_span": [2612, 2651], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S89.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4728, "question_text": "What planets?", "trigger_span": [4713, 4726], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S91.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4910, "question_text": "What hub?", "trigger_span": [4878, 4908], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S93.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5004, "question_text": "What petals?", "trigger_span": [4943, 4960], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S99.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5172, "question_text": "What creates the shadow?", "trigger_span": [5144, 5170], "answer_text": "Planets orbiting?", "answer_span": [5185.0, 5210.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S138.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9553, "question_text": "What is the ideal end?", "trigger_span": [9524, 9551], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S62.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4424, "question_text": "What is the new New World?", "trigger_span": [4329, 4347], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S69.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4513, "question_text": "Isolated cases of what exactly?", "trigger_span": [4461, 4487], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S71.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4633, "question_text": "What evidence or statistics supports the claim?", "trigger_span": [4596, 4631], "answer_text": "The data referenced indicates no negative effect of a focus on sustainability.", "answer_span": [4637.0, 4647.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S73.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4752, "question_text": "What is MSCI World?", "trigger_span": [4729, 4750], "answer_text": "The presentation would seem to include a visual aid showing that MSCI World is an index of large global companies.", "answer_span": [4752.0, 4784.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S75.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4910, "question_text": "How does the gold subset compare to the total?", "trigger_span": [4830, 4854], "answer_text": "Those companies are performing similarly to the rest.", "answer_span": [4933.0, 4956.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg1-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg1-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg1-as-detail"]}
{"id": "starshade.S33.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2070, "question_text": "How did we get so far away from earth?", "trigger_span": [1885, 1939], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S38.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2141, "question_text": "Why do we want to see inside the little red circle?", "trigger_span": [2113, 2139], "answer_text": "I believe but am not certain that the mission is to find interesting things to look at with the telescope.", "answer_span": [2219.0, 2239.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S81.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4346, "question_text": "What are you making that is a \"flower petal starshade\"?", "trigger_span": [4198, 4237], "answer_text": "I think what is being talked about is literally what it was originally called. A starshade. A big flower like shade to cover up brightness of a star so that a telescope can get better visions/view to what it is observing. ", "answer_span": [4599.0, 4651.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S86.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4485, "question_text": "What exactly is being talked about?", "trigger_span": [4346, 4376], "answer_text": "Creating a piece to cover up brightness of a star so that a telescope can view what it is looking at without being blinded out by the stars light beaming.", "answer_span": [4693.0, 4726.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "starshade.S72.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3886, "question_text": "Do they have different ideas?", "trigger_span": [3845, 3884], "answer_text": "soften the edges so the can control it better", "answer_span": [4003.0, 4051.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond", "EntRel:nan", "Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S74.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3936, "question_text": "Can they make a bigger shadow?", "trigger_span": [3886, 3908], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S76.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4084, "question_text": "Are they sure this will work?", "trigger_span": [4063, 4082], "answer_text": "they' came up with the best ways to do that", "answer_span": [4115.0, 4151.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S119.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8404, "question_text": "Why do they need a way out?", "trigger_span": [8325, 8359], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S108.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5537, "question_text": "Why do the petals unfurl?", "trigger_span": [5507, 5535], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan", "AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan", "AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S112.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5652, "question_text": "What is JPL?", "trigger_span": [5618, 5621], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S84.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4346, "question_text": "why does this work better?", "trigger_span": [4291, 4344], "answer_text": "it's a lot dimmer than before.", "answer_span": [4389.0, 4412.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S30.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2367, "question_text": "Why should they look at performance in ESG?", "trigger_span": [1925, 1964], "answer_text": "it incorporates those factors in to the process", "answer_span": [2496.0, 2558.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S37.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2560, "question_text": "Does it help to look at those a lot?", "trigger_span": [2461, 2507], "answer_text": "yes it's crucial to the business.", "answer_span": [2968.0, 2995.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "investment.S39.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2856, "question_text": "Do they think the private sector is not paying attention to ESG?", "trigger_span": [2816, 2855], "answer_text": "CEOs are watching ESG sustainability", "answer_span": [2897.0, 2905.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S42.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2896, "question_text": "What the heck is meant by the \"still point of the turning world\"?", "trigger_span": [2705, 2737], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S44.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3036, "question_text": "Why is the person \"in obscurity\"?", "trigger_span": [3009, 3021], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S48.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3262, "question_text": "Who is the author in relation to the person being discussed?", "trigger_span": [3044, 3097], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S52.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3432, "question_text": "Why do you view success as a one time thing?", "trigger_span": [3344, 3367], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S110.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8014, "question_text": "What more is there to do?", "trigger_span": [7780, 7804], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S117.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8255, "question_text": "Why would people add a deliberate imperfection?", "trigger_span": [8196, 8253], "answer_text": "An excuse and reason to continue making work.", "answer_span": [8370.0, 8402.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S46.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3864, "question_text": "Is this a physical space/event or something abstract?", "trigger_span": [3819, 3862], "answer_text": "It seems that they are talking about Rio de Janeiro.", "answer_span": [4126.0, 4183.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"]}
{"id": "investment.S41.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2997, "question_text": "Why is it crucial to Business success?", "trigger_span": [2968, 2995], "answer_text": "its the root of growth", "answer_span": [3055.0, 3083.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner"]}
{"id": "investment.S43.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3229, "question_text": "What do the ones that don't see it as that think?", "trigger_span": [3146, 3178], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S45.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3311, "question_text": "Is the enough to get the whole company on board?", "trigger_span": [3236, 3249], "answer_text": "They are all doing it together", "answer_span": [3532.0, 3567.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "AltLex:Hypophora", "AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S51.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3432, "question_text": "What are the actually doing?", "trigger_span": [3314, 3355], "answer_text": "completed numerous projects", "answer_span": [3586.0, 3627.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "AltLex:Hypophora", "AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S97.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7048, "question_text": "Why does it make people view it this way?", "trigger_span": [6899, 6926], "answer_text": "It makes it more precise.", "answer_span": [7219.0, 7269.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S65.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4614, "question_text": "Why was Franz Kafka so hard on himself?", "trigger_span": [4234, 4262], "answer_text": "It seems likely the pursuit of mastery and to never be perfect plauged him but I am not sure.", "answer_span": [4614.0, 4671.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S121.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8479, "question_text": "When are people experts?", "trigger_span": [8404, 8427], "answer_text": "They realize there isn't a conceptual end.", "answer_span": [8503.0, 8536.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S123.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8538, "question_text": "Why isn't there a conceptual end?", "trigger_span": [8521, 8536], "answer_text": "You can't give enough advice to overcome near wins and win every time.", "answer_span": [8824.0, 8867.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S125.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8749, "question_text": "Why was this said out of earshot?", "trigger_span": [8645, 8674], "answer_text": "There aren't enough techniques to help them overcome constant near wins.", "answer_span": [8824.0, 8867.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S1.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 177, "question_text": "Does the author know a lot about are history?", "trigger_span": [93, 124], "answer_text": "The author seems to have but in time consuming artwork.", "answer_span": [303.0, 310.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S44.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3261, "question_text": "What are the \"views of CEOs\"?", "trigger_span": [3236, 3249], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S48.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3388, "question_text": "What is ESG?", "trigger_span": [3352, 3355], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S52.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3532, "question_text": "What is the example?", "trigger_span": [3388, 3430], "answer_text": "Virtualized operating system environments and completed automation projects.", "answer_span": [3589.0, 3627.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "AltLex:Hypophora", "AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S7.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 543, "question_text": "Did she ever go on the road and experience unconventional things?", "trigger_span": [537, 541], "answer_text": "Many of her dreams have become a reality.", "answer_span": [691.0, 707.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S5.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 344, "question_text": "What did she do helping make the Elizabeth Murray exhibit?", "trigger_span": [236, 262], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S7.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 485, "question_text": "Did she work with Elizabeth Murray?", "trigger_span": [435, 441], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S9.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 645, "question_text": "How many paintings did she paint over the years?", "trigger_span": [578, 581], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S11.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 801, "question_text": "Is that painting found in the trash worth money now?", "trigger_span": [723, 728], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S13.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 958, "question_text": "Does Elizabeth Still paint?", "trigger_span": [934, 956], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S19.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1070, "question_text": "Does this writer want to achieve mastery for herself?", "trigger_span": [1051, 1068], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S126.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7472, "question_text": "How can money be used to improve sustainability.", "trigger_span": [7367, 7393], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S13.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1230, "question_text": "Where can her work be seen?", "trigger_span": [1111, 1116], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S19.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1414, "question_text": "How do they afford to live?", "trigger_span": [1324, 1358], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S17.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1619, "question_text": "Who is the person giving this opinion on prosthetists?", "trigger_span": [1334, 1356], "answer_text": "Someone who has received feedback from a professor.", "answer_span": [1772.0, 1781.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S22.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1867, "question_text": "How can these prosthetic sockets be improved?", "trigger_span": [1858, 1865], "answer_text": "The author is doing research to try to find the answer.", "answer_span": [1953.0, 1966.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "investment.S135.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7615, "question_text": "Do investors how controls these markets want sustainability?", "trigger_span": [7602, 7613], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S137.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7731, "question_text": "How many investors control the majority of these markets?", "trigger_span": [7622, 7643], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S1.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 123, "question_text": "Was it hard for her growing up?", "trigger_span": [113, 121], "answer_text": "She was not happy with her where she was living.", "answer_span": [278.0, 289.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "homeless.S5.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 347, "question_text": "Why was she unhappy with the routine?", "trigger_span": [326, 345], "answer_text": "She day dreamed about wanting to do more unconventional things.", "answer_span": [509.0, 523.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S106.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5457, "question_text": "What is the purpose of a star shade?", "trigger_span": [5445, 5455], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S24.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2081, "question_text": "Did the custom sockets work?", "trigger_span": [1979, 2004], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S26.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2329, "question_text": "Who did she test this on?", "trigger_span": [2292, 2311], "answer_text": "She has patients one being a U.S. veteran.", "answer_span": [2610.0, 2622.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S28.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2532, "question_text": "What do these sockets look like?", "trigger_span": [2338, 2348], "answer_text": "Its something soft", "answer_span": [2734.0, 2738.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S30.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2793, "question_text": "How many patients does she have?", "trigger_span": [2598, 2606], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S32.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 3040, "question_text": "How many people are in her research group working on this?", "trigger_span": [2951, 2965], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S9.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 909, "question_text": "Where are some places she has traveled to?", "trigger_span": [622, 643], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S11.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1038, "question_text": "Is documenting the lives of these people sad?", "trigger_span": [986, 1036], "answer_text": "She seems to be saying that the public perception of these people is not how it really is.", "answer_span": [1078.0, 1100.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S116.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5791, "question_text": "Why such an exact placement?", "trigger_span": [5759, 5789], "answer_text": "It is precise space tech", "answer_span": [5968.0, 6012.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S40.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2907, "question_text": "How do we know CEOs are paying attention?", "trigger_span": [2892, 2905], "answer_text": "80% of CEOs see sustainability as the root to growth", "answer_span": [3024.0, 3069.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner"]}
{"id": "investment.S42.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3142, "question_text": "What is the competitive advantage?", "trigger_span": [3099, 3140], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S141.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8105, "question_text": "Do institutional investors want to do help the environment?", "trigger_span": [7883, 7885], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S147.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8288, "question_text": "How likely is the world to be more stressed when we retire?", "trigger_span": [8188, 8201], "answer_text": "He is asking a similar question to the one i asked.", "answer_span": [8294.0, 8307.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "starshade.S97.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5212, "question_text": "What is it?", "trigger_span": [5009, 5035], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S102.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5262, "question_text": "What is the setting since the speaker is receiving applause?", "trigger_span": [5212, 5232], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S104.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5399, "question_text": "What type of test was conducted?", "trigger_span": [5334, 5359], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S61.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4707, "question_text": "What are the things we can do to reduce segregation?", "trigger_span": [4513, 4541], "answer_text": "People need to change who they hang out with.", "answer_span": [4796.0, 4822.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S102.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7271, "question_text": "Was this done on purpose so they would get more sales?", "trigger_span": [7157, 7197], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S104.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7399, "question_text": "Is it psychological?", "trigger_span": [7305, 7327], "answer_text": "It is because it makes you try harder", "answer_span": [7542.0, 7574.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S106.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7601, "question_text": "Why does it make us feel this way?", "trigger_span": [7513, 7530], "answer_text": "It makes you feel you still have more to do so you do better", "answer_span": [7743.0, 7779.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "starshade.S16.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1155, "question_text": "How difficult is it to turn around a space telescope?", "trigger_span": [1096, 1113], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S20.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1291, "question_text": "What will having a blurry picture help us with?", "trigger_span": [1186, 1224], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S65.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4614, "question_text": "Why was Kafka so displeased with his own works?", "trigger_span": [4240, 4262], "answer_text": "He needed mastery", "answer_span": [4629.0, 4678.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S48.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2742, "question_text": "What is this new tech suggested by Spitzer?", "trigger_span": [2612, 2634], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S32.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1885, "question_text": "What is ten times further away? ", "trigger_span": [1861, 1883], "answer_text": "Alpha Centauri", "answer_span": [1898.0, 1912.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S36.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2070, "question_text": "How far away is the planet now? ", "trigger_span": [2062, 2068], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S62.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4837, "question_text": "Shake the seating chart up how? ", "trigger_span": [4788, 4835], "answer_text": "Create interventions to reshape cities. ", "answer_span": [5287.0, 5327.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Purpose.Arg2-as-goal"]}
{"id": "cities.S69.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5102, "question_text": "What does contribute to our development of diversity? ", "trigger_span": [5058, 5100], "answer_text": "Reshaping cities. ", "answer_span": [5287.0, 5338.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Purpose.Arg2-as-goal"]}
{"id": "cities.S53.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3944, "question_text": "What the heck is the Flamengo football team?", "trigger_span": [3895, 3917], "answer_text": "It seems like it could be a Rio-based football team.", "answer_span": [4126.0, 4129.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"]}
{"id": "cities.S55.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4185, "question_text": "How is the representation different in Rio?", "trigger_span": [4035, 4070], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S57.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4342, "question_text": "How was this data gathered so that it's \"richer\"?", "trigger_span": [4284, 4313], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S59.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4472, "question_text": "Is segregation high in Rio?", "trigger_span": [4437, 4448], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S19.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1246, "question_text": "what else?", "trigger_span": [1226, 1244], "answer_text": "these are also economic issues.", "answer_span": [1246.0, 1269.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S68.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4614, "question_text": "where is all his works today? ", "trigger_span": [4478, 4503], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S71.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5400, "question_text": "what is that capability?", "trigger_span": [5375, 5398], "answer_text": "documenting relationships to reshape cities. ", "answer_span": [5790.0, 5819.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S73.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5466, "question_text": "who bears responsibility? ", "trigger_span": [5412, 5436], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S75.Q1", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5821, "question_text": "what kind of cities?", "trigger_span": [5781, 5819], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S49.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3432, "question_text": "What is that label?", "trigger_span": [3391, 3430], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S54.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3583, "question_text": "what is a constant pursuit?", "trigger_span": [3479, 3495], "answer_text": "Riddle with difficulties and flaws a near win. ", "answer_span": [3712.0, 3763.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous"]}
{"id": "starshade.S28.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1689, "question_text": "What is ten times further away?", "trigger_span": [1665, 1687], "answer_text": "Oort Cloud", "answer_span": [1712.0, 1722.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "investment.S133.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7524, "question_text": "How much money is needed to improve sustainability?", "trigger_span": [7506, 7522], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S70.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4814, "question_text": "Why was Kafka so obsessed with mastery?", "trigger_span": [4680, 4692], "answer_text": "Partially answered by the Michelangelo quote", "answer_span": [4818.0, 4842.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S72.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4958, "question_text": "Why was he reaching ?", "trigger_span": [4912, 4938], "answer_text": "He was constantly trying to close the gap", "answer_span": [4966.0, 5002.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S74.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5141, "question_text": "How far toward mastery did he actually think he achieved?", "trigger_span": [5029, 5049], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S76.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5368, "question_text": "What were his triumphs?", "trigger_span": [5309, 5343], "answer_text": "The goal is the journey.", "answer_span": [5395.0, 5415.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "investment.S9.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 693, "question_text": "Why is this?", "trigger_span": [589, 613], "answer_text": "big investors provide sustainability", "answer_span": [806.0, 840.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S11.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 842, "question_text": "Why do you think that?", "trigger_span": [693, 729], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S13.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1017, "question_text": "What's your point?", "trigger_span": [934, 955], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S29.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2125, "question_text": "So how do we conserve these things?", "trigger_span": [2089, 2123], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S80.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5465, "question_text": "How does one know when he is at \"the leading edge\"?", "trigger_span": [5417, 5426], "answer_text": "his favorite accomplishments are in the near future.", "answer_span": [5567.0, 5586.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S84.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5626, "question_text": "Can you expound on this wisdom?", "trigger_span": [5472, 5478], "answer_text": "We see more clearly as we approach mastery.", "answer_span": [5734.0, 5754.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "homeless.S30.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2776, "question_text": "What do they think is not idyllic? ", "trigger_span": [2739, 2774], "answer_text": "There's addiction, the elements, and laws against their existence. ", "answer_span": [2961.0, 3020.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S37.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3022, "question_text": "What laws criminalize homelessness? ", "trigger_span": [2961, 3020], "answer_text": "It's illegal to sit on a sidewalk", "answer_span": [3082.0, 3122.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "investment.S158.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9281, "question_text": "What are they sacrificing in the long term? ", "trigger_span": [9246, 9279], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S165.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9384, "question_text": "What if its a big hoax?", "trigger_span": [9296, 9320], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S167.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9420, "question_text": "What does he like? ", "trigger_span": [9386, 9419], "answer_text": "The fact they poke fun at both sides. ", "answer_span": [9420.0, 9454.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S81.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5626, "question_text": "What kind of music id Ellington make?", "trigger_span": [5595, 5624], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S86.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5841, "question_text": "What did he do to master this?", "trigger_span": [5666, 5684], "answer_text": "Sounds like maybe he studied", "answer_span": [5966.0, 5996.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S88.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5999, "question_text": "Were Baldwin and Ellington similar?", "trigger_span": [5841, 5885], "answer_text": "They both were successful once, leading to more successes.", "answer_span": [5999.0, 6019.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S90.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6222, "question_text": "So are people fueled by their first success, or attempt?", "trigger_span": [6025, 6069], "answer_text": "The closer we get to winning the more motivated we are", "answer_span": [6482.0, 6514.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "homeless.S39.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3209, "question_text": "What cities are affected? ", "trigger_span": [3022, 3056], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S23.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1520, "question_text": "SO what should I do instead?", "trigger_span": [1497, 1518], "answer_text": "An investor tries to predict the future and act on it", "answer_span": [1699.0, 1726.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "investment.S25.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1728, "question_text": "What is the earths \"financial data?\"", "trigger_span": [1646, 1697], "answer_text": "energy, water, waste and pollution", "answer_span": [2023.0, 2082.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S27.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1895, "question_text": "What are the fundamentals of the earth", "trigger_span": [1830, 1858], "answer_text": "energy consumption, water availability, and waste pollution.", "answer_span": [2023.0, 2082.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S42.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2372, "question_text": "What planet?", "trigger_span": [2307, 2321], "answer_text": "a new Earth-like planet in another solar system", "answer_span": [2583.0, 2610.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S44.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2544, "question_text": "What is this new tech?", "trigger_span": [2490, 2514], "answer_text": "It's a technology inspired by an eclipse", "answer_span": [2764.0, 2786.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S92.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6516, "question_text": "So are third and fourth place people less motivated?", "trigger_span": [6303, 6359], "answer_text": "They are less motivated because you seem farther from your goal, it seems less attainable.", "answer_span": [7000.0, 7046.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S96.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6855, "question_text": "Aren't gambling and and trying hard at something different?", "trigger_span": [6688, 6741], "answer_text": "Basically, we get the illusion that the odds have turned in our favor when we get close in gambling. This is so different than trying at something though", "answer_span": [6907.0, 6943.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S100.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7048, "question_text": "Does getting further from winning cause people to lose motivation?", "trigger_span": [6957, 6962], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S41.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3370, "question_text": "WHat happened to their friends? ", "trigger_span": [3257, 3308], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S43.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3574, "question_text": "Why do people choose to be homeless? ", "trigger_span": [3388, 3411], "answer_text": "freedom", "answer_span": [3702.0, 3709.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "investment.S35.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2367, "question_text": "SO if earth is like a company, how do we make it efficient like a business?", "trigger_span": [2125, 2202], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S52.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2788, "question_text": "What was inspired by Spitzer?", "trigger_span": [2749, 2762], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S1.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 223, "question_text": "What are the big drivers of change?", "trigger_span": [196, 221], "answer_text": "The previous text addressed this, I guess.", "answer_span": [417.0, 429.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S5.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 385, "question_text": "What specifically?", "trigger_span": [327, 358], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S7.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 489, "question_text": "returns on what?", "trigger_span": [470, 487], "answer_text": "returns in general -pension funds and such", "answer_span": [766.0, 800.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S131.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9040, "question_text": "What type of voraciousness is he giving himself over to?", "trigger_span": [9004, 9038], "answer_text": "A neverending unfinished path.", "answer_span": [9040.0, 9081.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Implicit:Contingency.Purpose.Arg2-as-goal"]}
{"id": "starshade.S33.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2070, "question_text": "What planet?", "trigger_span": [2044, 2068], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S38.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2141, "question_text": "What red circle?", "trigger_span": [2094, 2111], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S40.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2203, "question_text": "where is this text going?", "trigger_span": [2141, 2161], "answer_text": "The narrative describes scientists working with a telescope", "answer_span": [2208.0, 2239.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S10.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 922, "question_text": "What was the purpose of the Voyager?", "trigger_span": [754, 785], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S12.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1012, "question_text": "Why do you just want a picture of another planet?", "trigger_span": [922, 965], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S80.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4198, "question_text": "Looks something like what?", "trigger_span": [4171, 4196], "answer_text": "flower petal", "answer_span": [4215.0, 4237.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S56.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3777, "question_text": "What is a near win considered?", "trigger_span": [3765, 3776], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S58.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4013, "question_text": "what was Paul Cezannes purpose of leaving his paintings aside?", "trigger_span": [3933, 3962], "answer_text": "He was a protagonist who often though his works were incomplete. ", "answer_span": [4197.0, 4208.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S60.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4234, "question_text": "Why did he only sign 10 percent of his paintings?", "trigger_span": [4068, 4107], "answer_text": "Most were incomplete.", "answer_span": [4246.0, 4262.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S64.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4416, "question_text": "was all his work burned upon his death?", "trigger_span": [4393, 4414], "answer_text": "His friend refused to burn his work. ", "answer_span": [4416.0, 4455.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "cities.S26.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2260, "question_text": "how are geeks taking over?", "trigger_span": [2219, 2258], "answer_text": "Gentrification ", "answer_span": [2584.0, 2598.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "AltLex:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S117.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6951, "question_text": "how do you think is best to make money?", "trigger_span": [6934, 6950], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S119.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7016, "question_text": "do you think you can do greater good with ESG?", "trigger_span": [6951, 7000], "answer_text": "he does believe they can", "answer_span": [7232.0, 7289.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "investment.S121.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7144, "question_text": "Do you agree they can affect massive positive change?", "trigger_span": [7089, 7142], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S123.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7290, "question_text": "how can this be achieved?", "trigger_span": [7195, 7268], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S125.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7395, "question_text": "What do they think about sustainability?", "trigger_span": [7331, 7394], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S2.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 296, "question_text": "What does another planet need to be able to harbor life?", "trigger_span": [279, 294], "answer_text": "It needs to be an Earth-like planet.", "answer_span": [572.0, 623.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S6.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 625, "question_text": "What makes these planets like Earth?", "trigger_span": [546, 589], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S8.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 695, "question_text": "How are planets detected indirectly?", "trigger_span": [658, 693], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S35.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2285, "question_text": "How hard is it exactly to get into archery? ", "trigger_span": [2246, 2283], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S81.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5061, "question_text": "What do they want more of?", "trigger_span": [4981, 5006], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S108.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7806, "question_text": "Does it make us want more?", "trigger_span": [7733, 7742], "answer_text": "not being our best makes us better", "answer_span": [8092.0, 8144.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S112.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7963, "question_text": "Will different peoples play out differently?", "trigger_span": [7927, 7961], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S116.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8146, "question_text": "What happens when we finally reach our best?", "trigger_span": [8027, 8073], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S1.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 220, "question_text": "Are they still in Sierre Leone?", "trigger_span": [67, 104], "answer_text": "They didn't state completely but said they \"ran for safety\"", "answer_span": [427.0, 460.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S5.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 427, "question_text": "Is this person a boy or girl?", "trigger_span": [351, 374], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S110.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6698, "question_text": "how do they see it?", "trigger_span": [6661, 6697], "answer_text": "They look for profit not policy statements", "answer_span": [6712.0, 6748.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "investment.S169.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9525, "question_text": "What side are they on? ", "trigger_span": [9484, 9523], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S171.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9708, "question_text": "What motivates him? ", "trigger_span": [9619, 9640], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S107.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6425, "question_text": "why is it critical?", "trigger_span": [6356, 6382], "answer_text": "they need effective management", "answer_span": [6471.0, 6504.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S21.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1263, "question_text": "What happened with the archers? ", "trigger_span": [1187, 1228], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S23.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1487, "question_text": "Is it true you have to aim slightly askew? ", "trigger_span": [1435, 1485], "answer_text": "They have to aim with degrees? ", "answer_span": [1815.0, 1855.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous", "Explicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S25.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1703, "question_text": "Why is the ice cream important", "trigger_span": [1608, 1656], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S27.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1923, "question_text": "Why would they size him up? How is he at all relevant? ", "trigger_span": [1734, 1754], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S29.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2107, "question_text": "How will they hit the ten ring? ", "trigger_span": [2063, 2105], "answer_text": "Through pure tenacity. ", "answer_span": [2408.0, 2445.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S60.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3279, "question_text": "IS the corona the light around the moon we see in the eclipse?", "trigger_span": [3239, 3277], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S64.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3435, "question_text": "Does an eclipse cause heat from sun to go down?", "trigger_span": [3403, 3433], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S68.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3566, "question_text": "So is this how we could locate potential new homes for humans?", "trigger_span": [3491, 3522], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S14.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1246, "question_text": "How much longer do we have with current resources?", "trigger_span": [1017, 1081], "answer_text": "It seems it is a long way off.", "answer_span": [1352.0, 1380.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "investment.S21.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1472, "question_text": "We ignore it, but how long is it at this rate?", "trigger_span": [1452, 1470], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast", "Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast", "Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S1.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 220, "question_text": "do you do anything creative?", "trigger_span": [199, 219], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S109.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6564, "question_text": "what is physical capital?", "trigger_span": [6554, 6562], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S115.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6698, "question_text": "what is your job?", "trigger_span": [6645, 6659], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S5.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 427, "question_text": "any of yours amputated?", "trigger_span": [385, 426], "answer_text": "they ran so no, he was not ampuated", "answer_span": [444.0, 460.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S7.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 752, "question_text": "did you leave the country then?", "trigger_span": [554, 605], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S9.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1023, "question_text": "how did you find that out?", "trigger_span": [976, 1022], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S11.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1182, "question_text": "do you work in a hospital?", "trigger_span": [1138, 1181], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S13.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1311, "question_text": "which is the most typical duration?", "trigger_span": [1211, 1258], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S19.Q1", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1561, "question_text": "are there more modern processes?", "trigger_span": [1311, 1356], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S81.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5061, "question_text": "who is ESG?", "trigger_span": [5056, 5059], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S58.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3115, "question_text": "What was he talking about get us an earth?", "trigger_span": [3096, 3113], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S24.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2021, "question_text": "what's happening in San Francisco", "trigger_span": [1983, 2019], "answer_text": "Geeks and techies encompass the community. ", "answer_span": [2153.0, 2189.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S86.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5310, "question_text": "will there be a third color?", "trigger_span": [5137, 5141], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S88.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5359, "question_text": "how is it correlation?", "trigger_span": [5326, 5337], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S90.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5538, "question_text": "how do you figure that?", "trigger_span": [5387, 5443], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S92.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5654, "question_text": "what do you mean by at the vanguard?", "trigger_span": [5622, 5653], "answer_text": "hesta is at the vanguard", "answer_span": [5661.0, 5698.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "investment.S65.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4488, "question_text": "What did they do?", "trigger_span": [4150, 4171], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S70.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4592, "question_text": "what are they doing to be sustainable?", "trigger_span": [4526, 4550], "answer_text": "they have better ESG performance", "answer_span": [4665.0, 4687.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S72.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4720, "question_text": "what is ESG?", "trigger_span": [4672, 4675], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S28.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2461, "question_text": "How big are twitter employees in SF?", "trigger_span": [2341, 2358], "answer_text": "They're stimulating gentrification ", "answer_span": [2568.0, 2598.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "AltLex:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "cities.S32.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2745, "question_text": "How is this (Gentrification) hurting SF?", "trigger_span": [2639, 2673], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S36.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2880, "question_text": "how is the LGBT community not getting along?", "trigger_span": [2761, 2803], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S14.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1070, "question_text": "What DOES convert success into mastery? ", "trigger_span": [981, 1026], "answer_text": "When we value a \"near win\" ", "answer_span": [1092.0, 1132.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S45.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3711, "question_text": "Why is this more free?", "trigger_span": [3654, 3709], "answer_text": "The see an open road as a means to escape. ", "answer_span": [3897.0, 3936.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "homeless.S47.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3938, "question_text": "What percentage of people are barely surviving? ", "trigger_span": [3815, 3850], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S17.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1666, "question_text": "`How do sports connect people?", "trigger_span": [1617, 1664], "answer_text": "Under armor is the bridge between networks. ", "answer_span": [1865.0, 1914.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S22.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1916, "question_text": "How does under armor act as a bridge", "trigger_span": [1763, 1780], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S13.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1311, "question_text": "Did this situation improve in Sierra Leone?", "trigger_span": [1182, 1209], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S19.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1561, "question_text": "Does this pain last their whole lives?", "trigger_span": [1453, 1512], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S131.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7472, "question_text": "Are they investing more in ESG companies now than before?", "trigger_span": [7421, 7471], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S17.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1291, "question_text": "what is the fairly small telescope called? ", "trigger_span": [1242, 1264], "answer_text": "My mistake. The telescope was named in the beginning. ", "answer_span": [1358.0, 1364.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S22.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1366, "question_text": "what comes after the orbit of Uranus? ", "trigger_span": [1349, 1364], "answer_text": "Space. ", "answer_span": [1531.0, 1543.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S24.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1500, "question_text": "What is ten times further away?", "trigger_span": [1470, 1492], "answer_text": "Kuiper Belt", "answer_span": [1556.0, 1567.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S26.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1599, "question_text": "What is not resolved? ", "trigger_span": [1578, 1597], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S7.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 752, "question_text": "Is their life better now?", "trigger_span": [524, 553], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S88.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5359, "question_text": "What is their plan?", "trigger_span": [5323, 5357], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S90.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5538, "question_text": "Do they plan to make it the norm?", "trigger_span": [5511, 5537], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S92.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5654, "question_text": "Is this about stock exchange?", "trigger_span": [5580, 5589], "answer_text": "It is about a retirement fund not stocks ", "answer_span": [5661.0, 5687.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "investment.S96.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5783, "question_text": "Should one use a retirement fund?", "trigger_span": [5672, 5698], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S100.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5987, "question_text": "What does ESG stand for?", "trigger_span": [5801, 5850], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S7.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 752, "question_text": "when did they move back?", "trigger_span": [635, 681], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S9.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1023, "question_text": "Why were they painful?", "trigger_span": [985, 1022], "answer_text": "Th fit poorly", "answer_span": [1023.0, 1052.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S11.Q2", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1182, "question_text": "Why were they ill fitting?", "trigger_span": [1023, 1052], "answer_text": "It takes time to get comfortable with them", "answer_span": [1253.0, 1300.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S160.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9246, "question_text": "Do we have any assurances that what we do now is preventing the inevitable?", "trigger_span": [9081, 9102], "answer_text": "The answers is partially answered by the man asking if its a big hoax.", "answer_span": [9296.0, 9320.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S164.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9365, "question_text": "What can we tangibally see that we are making the right offsets now to benefit the long term?", "trigger_span": [9328, 9362], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S110.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5692, "question_text": "what are the petals for?", "trigger_span": [5522, 5528], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S117.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5893, "question_text": "what happens when the petals go into place?", "trigger_span": [5710, 5744], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S119.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6049, "question_text": "what will the technology do?", "trigger_span": [5952, 5983], "answer_text": "we will be able to see another solar system", "answer_span": [6376.0, 6403.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "investment.S86.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5310, "question_text": "Hoe are these factors measured?", "trigger_span": [5177, 5237], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S81.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5061, "question_text": "What is ESG?", "trigger_span": [5023, 5059], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S86.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5310, "question_text": "Are they talking about metrics and standards?", "trigger_span": [5268, 5308], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S49.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2788, "question_text": "What does he mean \"get us an Earth?\"", "trigger_span": [2576, 2591], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S54.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2901, "question_text": "Does this happen at night or day?", "trigger_span": [2831, 2859], "answer_text": "A spot light would be like a bright sun in the day", "answer_span": [2953.0, 2975.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "starshade.S56.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3039, "question_text": "Do eclipses have any other effects?", "trigger_span": [3008, 3021], "answer_text": "Other than shadows, probably not.", "answer_span": [3071.0, 3095.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora"]}
{"id": "starshade.S123.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6464, "question_text": "what is an occulter?", "trigger_span": [6423, 6431], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S125.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6617, "question_text": "How about the rest of the planets?", "trigger_span": [6464, 6483], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S127.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6778, "question_text": "what kind of life?", "trigger_span": [6710, 6730], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S96.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5783, "question_text": "do they service other countries?", "trigger_span": [5735, 5744], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S100.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5987, "question_text": "are they incorporating that strategy well?", "trigger_span": [5852, 5899], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S45.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2612, "question_text": "How to get rid of the light", "trigger_span": [2425, 2474], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S51.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2764, "question_text": "How does an eclipse help with the light issue", "trigger_span": [2733, 2740], "answer_text": "The moon blocks out the sun", "answer_span": [2788.0, 2826.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "cities.S65.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4929, "question_text": "How is race a poor proxy for diversity", "trigger_span": [4886, 4927], "answer_text": "Different races are all over the map", "answer_span": [4963.0, 5013.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "cities.S70.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5252, "question_text": "How to think of diversity in a new way", "trigger_span": [5228, 5250], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S72.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5447, "question_text": "How to change our cities for the better", "trigger_span": [5294, 5338], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S131.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7472, "question_text": "why do they have all the money?", "trigger_span": [7433, 7471], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S30.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1965, "question_text": "What planet", "trigger_span": [1949, 1955], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S37.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2113, "question_text": "How far away are we now", "trigger_span": [2026, 2052], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S103.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6156, "question_text": "what are the risks for calpers?", "trigger_span": [6050, 6077], "answer_text": "if they do not move toward 100 percent sustainable investment", "answer_span": [6374.0, 6412.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Q/A"]}
{"id": "cities.S74.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5651, "question_text": "How do relationships enter this picture", "trigger_span": [5595, 5649], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S62.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4524, "question_text": "What works do we have", "trigger_span": [4481, 4510], "answer_text": "Multiple named works", "answer_span": [4524.0, 4564.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S69.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4680, "question_text": "Other pursuits of mastery", "trigger_span": [4618, 4636], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S71.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4912, "question_text": "Where is that quote from", "trigger_span": [4680, 4733], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S23.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1952, "question_text": "How does San Francisco bring people together?", "trigger_span": [1937, 1950], "answer_text": "San Francisco has a similar society and economy when compared to Baltimore. ", "answer_span": [2054.0, 2083.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "cities.S25.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2135, "question_text": "How does San Francisco also differ when compared to Baltimore?", "trigger_span": [1972, 2019], "answer_text": "San Francisco has the IT/startup community", "answer_span": [2158.0, 2201.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S43.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2398, "question_text": "How to get rid of the light", "trigger_span": [2372, 2396], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S154.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8957, "question_text": "Is there a generally accepted solution?", "trigger_span": [8795, 8841], "answer_text": "We do what we do now to protect ourselves from the unknowns.", "answer_span": [8989.0, 9026.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S156.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9075, "question_text": "Is it right to act in the way we are acting now to preserve our future although we dont know it?", "trigger_span": [8989, 9026], "answer_text": "We are essentially doing what we do now as a risk prevention.", "answer_span": [9133.0, 9184.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S74.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4826, "question_text": "what companies?", "trigger_span": [4769, 4784], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S76.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4958, "question_text": "But are they better off?", "trigger_span": [4933, 4956], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S80.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4995, "question_text": "More what?", "trigger_span": [4981, 4993], "answer_text": "a subset of companies have out performed by two thirds", "answer_span": [5268.0, 5308.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S84.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5061, "question_text": "In what cases?", "trigger_span": [5008, 5021], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S94.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5967, "question_text": "how many fund members are there?", "trigger_span": [5953, 5965], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S101.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6022, "question_text": "why do you gotta love aussies?", "trigger_span": [5987, 6013], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S9.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1023, "question_text": "Did they do something to help amputees?", "trigger_span": [827, 860], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S11.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1182, "question_text": "Did the amputee's get help?", "trigger_span": [1036, 1052], "answer_text": "partially stated the problem can be it takes time to get used to or comfortable.", "answer_span": [1211.0, 1258.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S13.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1311, "question_text": "Did this satisfy it deeply troubling them?", "trigger_span": [1302, 1309], "answer_text": "They stated it is unacceptable, so it still deeply troubles them.", "answer_span": [1699.0, 1737.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S19.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1561, "question_text": "Is there anything to speed up the process or make them comfortable? ", "trigger_span": [1311, 1356], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S121.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6248, "question_text": "what will happen if you can put out a similar space telescope?", "trigger_span": [6139, 6179], "answer_text": "we might see a family portrait of another solar system", "answer_span": [6248.0, 6288.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S105.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6351, "question_text": "what is ESG?", "trigger_span": [6323, 6326], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S150.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8591, "question_text": "Do the programs we have now benefit the every day citizen?", "trigger_span": [8540, 8589], "answer_text": "The risk is calculated, however the benefit of today's actions are largely unknown.", "answer_span": [8749.0, 8779.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "investment.S152.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8791, "question_text": "Does science prove that we are are making the right choices right now?", "trigger_span": [8749, 8789], "answer_text": "Scientific fact is more accurate than one off disasters.", "answer_span": [8795.0, 8841.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "cities.S29.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2698, "question_text": "What brings these two groups together?", "trigger_span": [2584, 2598], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S35.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2859, "question_text": "Why does the LGBT community not get along with the tecky/geeks?", "trigger_span": [2783, 2827], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S2.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 205, "question_text": "What did you learn that helped benefit you?", "trigger_span": [177, 203], "answer_text": "They enjoyed the paintings of Elizabeth Murray.", "answer_span": [385.0, 422.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S6.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 424, "question_text": "What events came up that you saw as relate able?", "trigger_span": [385, 422], "answer_text": "The painter had a high standard for herself.", "answer_span": [582.0, 612.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S23.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1925, "question_text": "Did you work on a new method to solve the issue?", "trigger_span": [1893, 1922], "answer_text": "He designed special sockets that were more comfortable than conventional ones.", "answer_span": [2034.0, 2079.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S25.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2276, "question_text": "How long does the process to create these take?", "trigger_span": [1979, 2012], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S27.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2462, "question_text": "What is the material you use to make these sockets?", "trigger_span": [2361, 2393], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg1-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg1-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S29.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2691, "question_text": "Did this veteran find your new socket to be the most comfortable of all the ones he's tried?", "trigger_span": [2639, 2681], "answer_text": "He said their socket was really soft, which insinuates that it was comfortable.", "answer_span": [2731.0, 2768.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S73.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5051, "question_text": "How to close the gap", "trigger_span": [4988, 5002], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S75.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5211, "question_text": "Examples of people sacrificing for their craft", "trigger_span": [5141, 5210], "answer_text": "Triumphs aren't singular, they build off one another to a single thing", "answer_span": [5233.0, 5285.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S77.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5417, "question_text": "Other examples", "trigger_span": [5211, 5225], "answer_text": "Its better to always look ahead to the future", "answer_span": [5417.0, 5464.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S8.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 559, "question_text": "What about her work stood out to you?", "trigger_span": [446, 483], "answer_text": "Murray held such a high standard for herself that she herself did not understand the value of her work, whereas everyone else did. ", "answer_span": [817.0, 858.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S10.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 774, "question_text": "What happened to the painting?", "trigger_span": [748, 773], "answer_text": "The neighbor took it because they saw the value in it, not what the painter saw in it. ", "answer_span": [774.0, 799.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S12.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 860, "question_text": "What changed in a sense that you applied to your daily life?", "trigger_span": [817, 858], "answer_text": "They realized that success is how you personally take it, and that mastery is not something to chase. ", "answer_span": [981.0, 1026.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S16.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1027, "question_text": "How does one bridge the gap and change thier mindset?", "trigger_span": [981, 1026], "answer_text": "Celebrating small successes and near successes is when you begin to elevate as successful in your own eyes.", "answer_span": [1092.0, 1132.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S27.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2379, "question_text": "What other groups are in SF that relate?", "trigger_span": [2360, 2377], "answer_text": "San Francisco is becoming gentrified and polarizing the general community between the young and rich, and the native and poor.", "answer_span": [2423.0, 2459.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S83.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5588, "question_text": "Other wisdom", "trigger_span": [5465, 5478], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S2.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 332, "question_text": "What was the cause of the conflict?", "trigger_span": [260, 281], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S6.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 635, "question_text": "What did you do to protect your children from going through a similar hardship?", "trigger_span": [557, 594], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S8.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 938, "question_text": "Why didn't amputees use their prostheses?", "trigger_span": [882, 936], "answer_text": "The sockets that the prosthetic limbs went into were painful because the prostheses didn't fit in them well.", "answer_span": [1002.0, 1052.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S10.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1054, "question_text": "Was a solution realized to fix the problem of the prostheses not fitting well?", "trigger_span": [1031, 1052], "answer_text": "It takes a long time for the person who lost a limb to get a comfortable socket.", "answer_span": [1247.0, 1300.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S12.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1302, "question_text": "Is there anything to be done to speed this process along?", "trigger_span": [1282, 1300], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession+SpeechAct.Arg2-as-denier+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession+SpeechAct.Arg2-as-denier+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S20.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1134, "question_text": "How do we set those goals for us in order to achieve or nearly achieve them?", "trigger_span": [1092, 1132], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S145.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8406, "question_text": "Is there any proof?", "trigger_span": [8364, 8404], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S39.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2163, "question_text": "What is hard", "trigger_span": [2148, 2161], "answer_text": "The light of the sun blocks out the light coming from the planet", "answer_span": [2163.0, 2201.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "starshade.S41.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2301, "question_text": "What telescope are you using", "trigger_span": [2230, 2239], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S110.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6698, "question_text": "why don't they see it that way?", "trigger_span": [6665, 6697], "answer_text": "what they see that makes it so they don't see it that way", "answer_span": [6698.0, 6749.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "investment.S117.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6951, "question_text": "why does it get under your skin?", "trigger_span": [6863, 6891], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S119.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7016, "question_text": "what do you mean eyes rolling, eyes rolling?", "trigger_span": [6983, 7015], "answer_text": "why their eyes roll partially answered.", "answer_span": [7093.0, 7143.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S121.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7144, "question_text": "why are they not responsible when they have the most sway?", "trigger_span": [7061, 7084], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S123.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7290, "question_text": "why do they see it that way? they don't have children who will suffer at global warming because of their disregard for the planet?", "trigger_span": [7232, 7268], "answer_text": "they have money that will care for their children", "answer_span": [7451.0, 7471.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Q/A"]}
{"id": "investment.S125.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7395, "question_text": "what are you talking about then?", "trigger_span": [7297, 7324], "answer_text": "they have the money", "answer_span": [7472.0, 7481.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Q/A"]}
{"id": "investment.S110.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6698, "question_text": "Is this person making a speech?", "trigger_span": [6609, 6641], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S117.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6951, "question_text": "Are they trying to persuade someone they are different than the rest?", "trigger_span": [6845, 6888], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S119.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7016, "question_text": "Are they saying people claim to give it away but don't?", "trigger_span": [6988, 7014], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S121.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7144, "question_text": "Do they think companies are held to too high of a standard in regards to caring for the environment?", "trigger_span": [7089, 7142], "answer_text": "They sound like they aren't required to do such.", "answer_span": [7144.0, 7189.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "investment.S123.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7290, "question_text": "Who do they think is responsible?", "trigger_span": [7144, 7189], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S125.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7395, "question_text": "Are they saying they are liable?", "trigger_span": [7293, 7329], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S21.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1739, "question_text": "Why do they still make them this way if the outcome is not ideal?", "trigger_span": [1627, 1688], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S83.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5588, "question_text": "How does the author feel about people who retire after big achievements?", "trigger_span": [5567, 5586], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S55.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3712, "question_text": "What is an example of a classic that the creator considers unfinished?", "trigger_span": [3658, 3710], "answer_text": "Elizabeth Murray", "answer_span": [3777.0, 3793.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S131.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7472, "question_text": "Are they against investors?", "trigger_span": [7451, 7470], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S46.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2764, "question_text": "What is the coolest technology?", "trigger_span": [2520, 2542], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S88.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5359, "question_text": "What have they outperformed?", "trigger_span": [5310, 5337], "answer_text": "They have higher profits", "answer_span": [5382.0, 5443.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "investment.S90.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5538, "question_text": "Is this becoming more the norm?", "trigger_span": [5511, 5537], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S92.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5654, "question_text": "Why are some investors not engaged?", "trigger_span": [5566, 5614], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S96.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5783, "question_text": "What does Hesta invest in?", "trigger_span": [5661, 5687], "answer_text": "They invest in companies that are good in ESG", "answer_span": [5801.0, 5850.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S100.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5987, "question_text": "who is investing in this fund?", "trigger_span": [5932, 5965], "answer_text": "Australians ", "answer_span": [6006.0, 6013.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"]}
{"id": "starshade.S55.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3008, "question_text": "What does the eclipse have to do with cool tech?", "trigger_span": [2831, 2859], "answer_text": "removes light", "answer_span": [3191.0, 3223.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg1-as-cond"]}
{"id": "starshade.S57.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3062, "question_text": "Did blocking light inspire cool tech?", "trigger_span": [3045, 3061], "answer_text": "camera in moon's shadow", "answer_span": [3124.0, 3160.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S59.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3249, "question_text": "What is dim?", "trigger_span": [3228, 3247], "answer_text": "corona structure", "answer_span": [3249.0, 3277.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S61.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3325, "question_text": "What happens if the technique is used in space?", "trigger_span": [3279, 3323], "answer_text": "we can see planets", "answer_span": [3501.0, 3522.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "cities.S64.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4772, "question_text": "How have the kids arranged themselves?", "trigger_span": [4711, 4770], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S68.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4929, "question_text": "Why is race a poor proxy for diversity?", "trigger_span": [4886, 4927], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S46.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3314, "question_text": "What is the difference between mastery and excellence?", "trigger_span": [3262, 3312], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S53.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3497, "question_text": "What exactly is mastery?", "trigger_span": [3432, 3469], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S31.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2882, "question_text": "Will you be able to make enough of these to replace conventional sockets?", "trigger_span": [2826, 2880], "answer_text": "He wants his development of these sockets to be able to reach whoever needs them.", "answer_span": [2981.0, 3038.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "homeless.S26.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2208, "question_text": "Where do they commonly go?", "trigger_span": [2013, 2066], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S28.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2551, "question_text": "Are they not unlike hippies?", "trigger_span": [2222, 2257], "answer_text": "Hippies are in a sense, a nomad, living off what they have, rather than what they can purchase to have. ", "answer_span": [2556.0, 2609.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous"]}
{"id": "homeless.S32.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2709, "question_text": "How else do they express thier life on the streets?", "trigger_span": [2658, 2707], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S36.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2831, "question_text": "How else could they have dealt with the issues?", "trigger_span": [2776, 2807], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S14.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1553, "question_text": "Is country life better in some respects?", "trigger_span": [1174, 1207], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S21.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1763, "question_text": "Do sports bring all people together?", "trigger_span": [1608, 1664], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S53.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2828, "question_text": "What did the eclipse inspire?", "trigger_span": [2771, 2786], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S72.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5447, "question_text": "What interventions would these be?", "trigger_span": [5287, 5338], "answer_text": "It says the first step is to document relationships between people but doesn't say what they would do with that information. ", "answer_span": [5689.0, 5731.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond"]}
{"id": "investment.S113.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6845, "question_text": "What is your job or position in the company?", "trigger_span": [6642, 6659], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S118.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6983, "question_text": "What do you reply to the person suggesting this?", "trigger_span": [6951, 6980], "answer_text": "She says she rolls her eyes, but that isn't really a reply.", "answer_span": [6988.0, 7000.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S120.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7061, "question_text": "Why do you let people get you so emotional and angry?", "trigger_span": [6983, 7014], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S122.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7270, "question_text": "Don't you think successful businesses should do their part to better society since they have the means and resources to do so?", "trigger_span": [7144, 7189], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S124.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7331, "question_text": "What is your ideal balance of profits versus social contributions then?", "trigger_span": [7270, 7288], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S128.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7421, "question_text": "Do you have a vision that differs that you think is superior? If so, what is it?", "trigger_span": [7395, 7420], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Q/A"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Q/A"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S7.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 485, "question_text": "I asked her what she thought of her early work.", "trigger_span": [424, 445], "answer_text": "She said that if you didn't quite meet her own standards.", "answer_span": [559.0, 581.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S69.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4680, "question_text": "How far along does this book get? ", "trigger_span": [4551, 4585], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S71.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4912, "question_text": "Why does the author include this quote?", "trigger_span": [4876, 4910], "answer_text": "the author says that the journey is the main purpose, not the end. ", "answer_span": [4912.0, 4938.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S41.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2301, "question_text": "Would a different type of telescope work better to see it?", "trigger_span": [2203, 2239], "answer_text": "Sounds like there's a method to see the planet, but it hasn't clarified the details yet. It has to do with getting rid of the light. ", "answer_span": [2326.0, 2370.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S43.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2398, "question_text": "How do we get rid of it?", "trigger_span": [2372, 2396], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S45.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2612, "question_text": "What are these new technologies?", "trigger_span": [2425, 2463], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S51.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2764, "question_text": "What was first suggested?", "trigger_span": [2619, 2651], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S65.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4929, "question_text": "How can you shake up how and where people live?", "trigger_span": [4777, 4822], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S70.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5252, "question_text": "What new way is there to think about diversity?", "trigger_span": [5207, 5250], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S77.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5417, "question_text": "Are there other examples of this? ", "trigger_span": [5379, 5415], "answer_text": "He gives musical artists who don't stop making music, and who crave new music like Duke Ellington, as an example. ", "answer_span": [5588.0, 5624.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S132.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7496, "question_text": "Wouldn't you agree that since they have a lot of money they should have a responsibility to society to further social causes that better society for everyone?", "trigger_span": [7451, 7470], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S14.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1414, "question_text": "Are there still vagabonds?", "trigger_span": [1064, 1100], "answer_text": "The hobos still get around the same way.", "answer_span": [1575.0, 1604.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S21.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1635, "question_text": "Today's hobos are the same as yesterday's vagabonds.", "trigger_span": [1414, 1437], "answer_text": "They still sleep outside under the stars.", "answer_span": [1645.0, 1673.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S23.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1905, "question_text": "Many choose this lifestyle.", "trigger_span": [1773, 1799], "answer_text": "Others have no choice.", "answer_span": [1949.0, 1989.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "homeless.S25.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2068, "question_text": "Many come from bad backgrounds.", "trigger_span": [1926, 1947], "answer_text": "They live off what others throw away.", "answer_span": [2208.0, 2244.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "cities.S74.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5651, "question_text": "How can you get involved in changing relationships?", "trigger_span": [5595, 5649], "answer_text": "It says it starts with documenting relationships, but doesn't entirely clarify what you can do with that information. ", "answer_span": [5676.0, 5717.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S62.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4524, "question_text": "Why did he refuse to honor the request?", "trigger_span": [4416, 4455], "answer_text": "That there's still value in work in progress", "answer_span": [4614.0, 4671.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "homeless.S17.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1514, "question_text": "Are nomads homeless as a hobo would be?", "trigger_span": [1111, 1116], "answer_text": "Nomads live in a style similar to hobos in that there is no defined home, but constant travel. ", "answer_span": [1645.0, 1673.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S22.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1758, "question_text": "Where do they intend on going?", "trigger_span": [1575, 1633], "answer_text": "They simply have no place to go.", "answer_span": [1949.0, 1989.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "homeless.S24.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2013, "question_text": "Do they want to be homeless?", "trigger_span": [1801, 1841], "answer_text": "While some escape home, others embrace that this is thier home. ", "answer_span": [2184.0, 2206.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S16.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1428, "question_text": "Is there another method of making prostheses that is unconventional but works better?", "trigger_span": [1311, 1356], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S20.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1619, "question_text": "Why do they use this method if the outcome is poor?", "trigger_span": [1428, 1484], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S14.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1561, "question_text": "Is there another method of making prostheses that makes them less painful?", "trigger_span": [1311, 1356], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S73.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5051, "question_text": "Why does the author feel this way?", "trigger_span": [4958, 5002], "answer_text": "The author believes that it's about sacrifice to become a real master of your craft.", "answer_span": [5051.0, 5094.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S75.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5211, "question_text": "What actions make up the difference between sacrificing and crafting your career?", "trigger_span": [5119, 5139], "answer_text": "The author seems to think that a person really needs to put themselves out there to be a genius. ", "answer_span": [5233.0, 5272.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S67.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3524, "question_text": "Are these exoplanets we can see?", "trigger_span": [3515, 3522], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S2.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 267, "question_text": "What are some big changes in sustainability?", "trigger_span": [204, 265], "answer_text": "ESG", "answer_span": [327.0, 383.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S6.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 431, "question_text": "What are the consequences if people ignore sustainability?", "trigger_span": [393, 429], "answer_text": "Poor long-term returns", "answer_span": [452.0, 487.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief"]}
{"id": "investment.S8.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 625, "question_text": "How do investors influence sustainability?", "trigger_span": [564, 623], "answer_text": "they have big money", "answer_span": [629.0, 691.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S6.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 461, "question_text": "It's not a standard geographic map.", "trigger_span": [439, 459], "answer_text": "This map is about the relationships that people have.", "answer_span": [471.0, 525.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "cities.S8.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 730, "question_text": "Each dot is a person.", "trigger_span": [589, 612], "answer_text": "On the green side are one type of people.", "answer_span": [747.0, 761.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "cities.S10.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1034, "question_text": "The other side are the minorities.", "trigger_span": [862, 894], "answer_text": "This is what we call our part of the network.", "answer_span": [1093.0, 1112.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S12.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1209, "question_text": "Our network seems like it is a small town.", "trigger_span": [1174, 1207], "answer_text": "There is a different group of people on the other end.", "answer_span": [1339.0, 1370.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief", "Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief", "Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S85.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5802, "question_text": "Are there more examples of near wins?", "trigger_span": [5654, 5662], "answer_text": "Dunning-Kruger effect", "answer_span": [5818.0, 5839.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S10.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 802, "question_text": "Are there benefits to sustainable investing besides simplicity and performance?", "trigger_span": [733, 783], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S57.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3855, "question_text": "What was one of Elizabeth's paintings?", "trigger_span": [3816, 3853], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S59.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4109, "question_text": "How many of Paul's paintings are famous?", "trigger_span": [4064, 4107], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S61.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4354, "question_text": "What did Franz do with his diaries?", "trigger_span": [4308, 4352], "answer_text": "had them burned upon his death", "answer_span": [4393.0, 4414.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S67.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4524, "question_text": "Why didn't his friend burn the things he was asked to?", "trigger_span": [4416, 4455], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S1.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 220, "question_text": "where did you move after that?", "trigger_span": [67, 104], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S5.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 427, "question_text": "Did you move away because of the war?", "trigger_span": [260, 281], "answer_text": "They and their family fled from a rebel attack", "answer_span": [461.0, 506.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S89.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6071, "question_text": "What are some important ongoing quests?", "trigger_span": [6040, 6069], "answer_text": "Olympics", "answer_span": [6136.0, 6200.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S91.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6361, "question_text": "Are silver medalists more frustrated than bronze?", "trigger_span": [6303, 6359], "answer_text": "Yes silvers focus better on next time", "answer_span": [6465.0, 6514.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S93.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6780, "question_text": "Are there other gambling examples of the near win?", "trigger_span": [6660, 6697], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S29.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1846, "question_text": "How far out are we planning on going?", "trigger_span": [1640, 1687], "answer_text": "Ten times further away from the last point", "answer_span": [1846.0, 1883.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S12.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 882, "question_text": "What do we already know?", "trigger_span": [849, 880], "answer_text": "population is growing", "answer_span": [942.0, 989.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S16.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1170, "question_text": "Can Earth support 10 billion people?", "trigger_span": [979, 1015], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S20.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1320, "question_text": "What is the best investment?", "trigger_span": [1291, 1318], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S78.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5588, "question_text": "Did anyone else share the philosophy of Saunders or Ellington?", "trigger_span": [5395, 5415], "answer_text": "James Baldwin", "answer_span": [5872.0, 5885.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S9.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 645, "question_text": "Were they what she wanted them to be?", "trigger_span": [617, 643], "answer_text": "Not all of them.", "answer_span": [672.0, 695.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S11.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 801, "question_text": "She threw it out but her neighbor took it out of the trash.", "trigger_span": [748, 773], "answer_text": "Success and creativity didn't mean what I thought they did.", "answer_span": [820.0, 858.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S13.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 958, "question_text": "Success is brief but we always celebrate creativity.", "trigger_span": [876, 895], "answer_text": "I've always asked myself this.", "answer_span": [981.0, 1026.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "cities.S16.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1509, "question_text": "They feel like they are living in the DC or Maryland area.", "trigger_span": [1444, 1497], "answer_text": "There is something that connects the two communities.", "answer_span": [1608.0, 1645.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "cities.S20.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1666, "question_text": "Sports connects the two communities.", "trigger_span": [1651, 1664], "answer_text": "There are plenty of sports teams and even companies that bridge the two ends of the network.", "answer_span": [1666.0, 1695.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S1.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 177, "question_text": "What was my first job?", "trigger_span": [76, 88], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S5.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 344, "question_text": "How much did I learn from her?", "trigger_span": [177, 203], "answer_text": "Motives and elements would come up later in her life.", "answer_span": [355.0, 379.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S87.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5953, "question_text": "What did Baldwin say increases with knowledge?", "trigger_span": [5907, 5951], "answer_text": "You learn how little you know", "answer_span": [5966.0, 5996.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S125.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7395, "question_text": "What about retail investors?", "trigger_span": [7363, 7394], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S131.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7472, "question_text": "Is spending the only way to impact our sustainability?", "trigger_span": [7451, 7470], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S110.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5692, "question_text": "What kind of petals are they?", "trigger_span": [5543, 5565], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S44.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3702, "question_text": "What's the word?", "trigger_span": [3689, 3700], "answer_text": "Freedom", "answer_span": [3702.0, 3709.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "homeless.S46.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3826, "question_text": "How can we assure this?", "trigger_span": [3759, 3789], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S48.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3982, "question_text": "Does he have rebellious feelings?", "trigger_span": [3971, 3980], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S96.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5783, "question_text": "Are they environmentally friendly?", "trigger_span": [5661, 5721], "answer_text": "Yes they are incorporating this mindset into their culture.", "answer_span": [5903.0, 5921.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "investment.S100.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5987, "question_text": "How many fund members do they have?", "trigger_span": [5953, 5965], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S153.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8918, "question_text": "Is this based on any type of consensus?", "trigger_span": [8758, 8789], "answer_text": "We protect ourselves with insurance.", "answer_span": [8989.0, 9026.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Exception.Arg2-as-excpt"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S155.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9068, "question_text": "Can bad things happen financially?", "trigger_span": [9039, 9066], "answer_text": "We are investing sustainably.", "answer_span": [9078.0, 9102.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous"]}
{"id": "investment.S157.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9127, "question_text": "How many things are we doing?", "trigger_span": [9103, 9125], "answer_text": "We are creating insurance and reducing risk to the planet.", "answer_span": [9127.0, 9170.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S163.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9281, "question_text": "Are we sacrificing performance?", "trigger_span": [9246, 9279], "answer_text": "What if all of this is for nothing?", "answer_span": [9325.0, 9362.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S19.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1070, "question_text": "I'm still asking myself.", "trigger_span": [1046, 1068], "answer_text": "We value a gift that is near win.", "answer_span": [1092.0, 1132.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S142.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8288, "question_text": "What did they integrate into an investment?", "trigger_span": [7910, 7940], "answer_text": "The integrated ESG into investment.", "answer_span": [8318.0, 8375.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "investment.S149.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8460, "question_text": "What might be exaggerated?", "trigger_span": [8377, 8404], "answer_text": "There are always risks and costs when you take action.", "answer_span": [8540.0, 8589.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora"]}
{"id": "investment.S151.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8675, "question_text": "Are they more or less than long-range risks?", "trigger_span": [8600, 8638], "answer_text": "There is risk but it's an estimate.", "answer_span": [8681.0, 8721.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S90.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5538, "question_text": "Do you think all companies should take more of an environmental focus?", "trigger_span": [5387, 5443], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S24.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1608, "question_text": "Why is he so interested in archers paradox?", "trigger_span": [1365, 1381], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S1.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 220, "question_text": "How long did you live there?", "trigger_span": [73, 104], "answer_text": "They left when she was 12 years old.", "answer_span": [446.0, 480.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S5.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 427, "question_text": "What is it like currently there?", "trigger_span": [260, 293], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S7.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 752, "question_text": "Where do you live now?", "trigger_span": [585, 626], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S9.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1023, "question_text": "What can be done to ease the pain of these prosthetics?", "trigger_span": [985, 1022], "answer_text": "They can be fitted properly to each person.", "answer_span": [1031.0, 1052.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S11.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1182, "question_text": "Do you work with prosthetic sockets now?", "trigger_span": [1058, 1087], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S13.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1311, "question_text": "Is there a way for people to get them quicker?", "trigger_span": [1232, 1258], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S27.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2370, "question_text": "The American dream does not exist for them.", "trigger_span": [2316, 2368], "answer_text": "They give up comfort for freedom.", "answer_span": [2551.0, 2583.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S29.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2655, "question_text": "There is plenty of food to scavenge.", "trigger_span": [2435, 2480], "answer_text": "They are free to work on whatever their passion is.", "answer_span": [2655.0, 2695.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous"]}
{"id": "homeless.S35.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2776, "question_text": "This life is not very comfortable though.", "trigger_span": [2758, 2774], "answer_text": "Drug addiction and bad weather are constant companions.", "answer_span": [2831.0, 2871.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "cities.S2.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 386, "question_text": "We always think maps are roads and streets.", "trigger_span": [128, 168], "answer_text": "I'm going to show you a new kind of map.", "answer_span": [395.0, 429.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S19.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1561, "question_text": "Is there a way to make prosthetics without conventional processes?", "trigger_span": [1311, 1356], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S81.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5061, "question_text": "How often will ESG outperform?", "trigger_span": [5036, 5059], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S86.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5310, "question_text": "Are climate change focused companies the best investments?", "trigger_span": [5177, 5237], "answer_text": "There is some correlation to support this idea.", "answer_span": [5318.0, 5337.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S88.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5359, "question_text": "How much has this correlation increased as of late?", "trigger_span": [5326, 5337], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S168.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9484, "question_text": "Is climate change important to them?", "trigger_span": [9462, 9482], "answer_text": "Sort of but sort of not. Basically neutral it seems", "answer_span": [9484.0, 9523.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S170.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9641, "question_text": "Why is planning for the future so important?", "trigger_span": [9619, 9639], "answer_text": "Because future me will appreciate it", "answer_span": [9669.0, 9705.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "starshade.S30.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1965, "question_text": "Ten times further away from what? What was the starting point?", "trigger_span": [1640, 1687], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S37.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2113, "question_text": "What planet is being referred to? ", "trigger_span": [2026, 2068], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S39.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2163, "question_text": "What do we want to see?", "trigger_span": [2113, 2139], "answer_text": "The unnamed planet", "answer_span": [2255.0, 2299.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S92.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5654, "question_text": "Are investors looking at the wrong things?", "trigger_span": [5606, 5653], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S26.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1848, "question_text": "Numbers? What kind of numbers", "trigger_span": [1839, 1846], "answer_text": "The degrees.", "answer_span": [1848.0, 1855.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous", "Explicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S28.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2039, "question_text": "What positions do they use?", "trigger_span": [1868, 1877], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S56.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4211, "question_text": "What data do you have?", "trigger_span": [4185, 4209], "answer_text": "Data about cities", "answer_span": [4230.0, 4276.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "cities.S58.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4369, "question_text": "What is richer than any data set?", "trigger_span": [4296, 4309], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S60.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4578, "question_text": "Why is segregation a social construct?", "trigger_span": [4437, 4470], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S99.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6964, "question_text": "What do near wins do to goals?", "trigger_span": [6948, 6962], "answer_text": "Puts them closer", "answer_span": [7005.0, 7028.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S14.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1414, "question_text": "How are they able to travel across the country?", "trigger_span": [1285, 1322], "answer_text": "They hitchhike and ride freight trains.", "answer_span": [1527.0, 1545.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "homeless.S21.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1635, "question_text": "Is this illegal?", "trigger_span": [1527, 1545], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S23.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1905, "question_text": "Are there any that do it out of necessity?", "trigger_span": [1773, 1799], "answer_text": "People that come from disadvantaged circumstances do it.", "answer_span": [1926.0, 1947.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "investment.S123.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7290, "question_text": "Why do you think most people aren't willing to oblige socially?", "trigger_span": [7149, 7189], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S152.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8791, "question_text": "What course of action should we take?", "trigger_span": [8758, 8789], "answer_text": "odds are in favor of us listening/obeying the actions previously suggested by corporations for climate change", "answer_span": [8795.0, 8830.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S6.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 424, "question_text": "What were some of these elements?", "trigger_span": [391, 422], "answer_text": "some of the works didn't meet her mark of approval", "answer_span": [582.0, 612.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S8.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 559, "question_text": "What made the early works so different?", "trigger_span": [446, 483], "answer_text": "the work wasn't up to her standards", "answer_span": [675.0, 695.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S10.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 774, "question_text": "What happened to the painting?", "trigger_span": [748, 773], "answer_text": "it became valuable to the new owner (neighbor)", "answer_span": [782.0, 799.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S12.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 860, "question_text": "Is your work different today because of this experience?", "trigger_span": [817, 858], "answer_text": "work now involves asking questions about mastery", "answer_span": [981.0, 1026.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "starshade.S35.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1965, "question_text": "Which planet is gone?", "trigger_span": [1945, 1963], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S49.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3882, "question_text": "Is there metal music?", "trigger_span": [3679, 3723], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S54.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4072, "question_text": "What else gets represented?", "trigger_span": [4026, 4070], "answer_text": "Cities", "answer_span": [4266.0, 4272.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S110.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6698, "question_text": "Which type of capital is most important of the three?", "trigger_span": [6508, 6562], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S117.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6951, "question_text": "How do you feel about people who disagree with your views?", "trigger_span": [6845, 6891], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S119.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7016, "question_text": "What is a better way to give than a charity?", "trigger_span": [6960, 7000], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S121.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7144, "question_text": "Do you think people need to be more focused on the planet?", "trigger_span": [7089, 7142], "answer_text": "Institutional investors are essential to help sustain the planet.", "answer_span": [7335.0, 7394.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S16.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1027, "question_text": "How do you define success or mastery?", "trigger_span": [860, 895], "answer_text": "success/mastery happens the moment we value the gift of a near win", "answer_span": [1092.0, 1132.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S20.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1134, "question_text": "Have you reached success or mastery?", "trigger_span": [1046, 1068], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S145.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8406, "question_text": "What is our alternative?", "trigger_span": [8350, 8387], "answer_text": "there is also elimination risk", "answer_span": [8706.0, 8721.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S150.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8591, "question_text": "Should we take these risks and accept the cost?", "trigger_span": [8551, 8589], "answer_text": "probably not, since the odds are in favor of \"It's actually happening.\"", "answer_span": [8835.0, 8855.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "AltLex:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "investment.S164.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9365, "question_text": "What could it hurt to try?", "trigger_span": [9325, 9349], "answer_text": "it's a positive action, so try it", "answer_span": [9371.0, 9397.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"]}
{"id": "starshade.S14.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1226, "question_text": "What hasn't been done?", "trigger_span": [986, 1011], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S21.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1330, "question_text": "What is being moved away from?", "trigger_span": [1291, 1328], "answer_text": "Uranus", "answer_span": [1358.0, 1364.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S23.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1423, "question_text": "What has less resolve?", "trigger_span": [1387, 1421], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S25.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1569, "question_text": "Is the Kuiper belt similar to the asteroid belt?", "trigger_span": [1556, 1567], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Synchronous"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Synchronous"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S27.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1640, "question_text": "Who is Carl Sagan?", "trigger_span": [1626, 1638], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S154.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8957, "question_text": "How can I make the decision to act or not?", "trigger_span": [8924, 8955], "answer_text": "we decide to buy insurance for protection", "answer_span": [8992.0, 9038.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S156.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9075, "question_text": "Is that always an effective way to handle this situation?", "trigger_span": [9039, 9066], "answer_text": "yes, it's effective due to risk reduction", "answer_span": [9153.0, 9170.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "cities.S16.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1509, "question_text": "Why are they not fully exploring te city?", "trigger_span": [1272, 1313], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S32.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2709, "question_text": "Do hobos have families?", "trigger_span": [2556, 2583], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S36.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2831, "question_text": "Are the hobos on the run from the law?", "trigger_span": [2795, 2807], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S25.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2068, "question_text": "Were any exceptions able to mobilize upwards?", "trigger_span": [1963, 1989], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S27.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2370, "question_text": "Is their enough excess for everyone?", "trigger_span": [2268, 2293], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S29.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2655, "question_text": "Does this exploration lead to more happiness?", "trigger_span": [2626, 2653], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S35.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2776, "question_text": "What are some of the unfavorable aspects?", "trigger_span": [2728, 2774], "answer_text": "Addiction, elements, dangerous transportation, and laws against homelessness.", "answer_span": [2961.0, 3021.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S2.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 386, "question_text": "What are some of these other ways?", "trigger_span": [316, 356], "answer_text": "By mapping relationships between people in a town.", "answer_span": [471.0, 525.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S120.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8428, "question_text": "What's the proposal for bridging the mastery expert gap?", "trigger_span": [8404, 8427], "answer_text": "The importance of mastery doesn't derive from completing projects. ", "answer_span": [8448.0, 8477.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S122.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8495, "question_text": "What makes a master?", "trigger_span": [8479, 8494], "answer_text": "There is no such as a master which a \"master\" realizes. ", "answer_span": [8508.0, 8536.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S124.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8645, "question_text": "What did his archery coach tell him?", "trigger_span": [8594, 8607], "answer_text": "The coach expressed frustration about the impossibility of teaching the team everything they needed to win. ", "answer_span": [8703.0, 8747.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S128.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8869, "question_text": "What prompted this sort of feeling of hopelessness?", "trigger_span": [8749, 8776], "answer_text": "He wanted to express his recognition of being in a perpetual battle that require ever increasing resources. ", "answer_span": [9040.0, 9081.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Implicit:Contingency.Purpose.Arg2-as-goal"]}
{"id": "cities.S6.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 461, "question_text": "What is new about this kind of map?", "trigger_span": [414, 429], "answer_text": "It is a map of the relationships between people in a town.", "answer_span": [471.0, 525.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "cities.S8.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 730, "question_text": "How many communities are there?", "trigger_span": [700, 728], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S10.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1034, "question_text": "What kind of things are they concerned about?", "trigger_span": [972, 1013], "answer_text": "Hip hop music", "answer_span": [1421.0, 1434.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "cities.S12.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1209, "question_text": "How small is it?", "trigger_span": [1192, 1207], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief", "Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief", "Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S32.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2220, "question_text": "That's impressive. It must take a lot of skill to hit that and i wonder how .long the girls have trained?", "trigger_span": [2179, 2218], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S36.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2408, "question_text": "How could she be so accurate and then miss the next?", "trigger_span": [2356, 2406], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S161.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9365, "question_text": "Why is the man in comic here?", "trigger_span": [9281, 9294], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S166.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9399, "question_text": "Like what?", "trigger_span": [9386, 9397], "answer_text": "He likes to look at both sides", "answer_span": [9412.0, 9454.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S132.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9083, "question_text": "What was the narrator's reaction to his coach's revelation?", "trigger_span": [8930, 8941], "answer_text": "It inspired the narrator to build himself from the perpetual nature of being incomplete. ", "answer_span": [9083.0, 9091.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "homeless.S33.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2831, "question_text": "What aspects?", "trigger_span": [2723, 2774], "answer_text": "Society in general. They see the truth in the world.", "answer_span": [2831.0, 2892.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "homeless.S38.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3154, "question_text": "I am wondering if he is saying this from experience", "trigger_span": [2922, 2953], "answer_text": "It seems he's leading up to something more important.", "answer_span": [3209.0, 3232.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora"]}
{"id": "homeless.S40.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3233, "question_text": "Why does he know the laws so well?", "trigger_span": [3209, 3232], "answer_text": "He saw people he cared about go to jail for idiotic things. Horrible", "answer_span": [3285.0, 3330.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Disjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S94.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5967, "question_text": "Why ESG?", "trigger_span": [5801, 5822], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S101.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6022, "question_text": "What does being Aussie have to do with anything? ", "trigger_span": [5991, 6013], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S103.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6156, "question_text": "Why trust anything from California? ", "trigger_span": [6078, 6112], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S125.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6617, "question_text": "What angel is this from?", "trigger_span": [6472, 6520], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S127.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6778, "question_text": "Is there any evidence thus far?", "trigger_span": [6691, 6730], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S65.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4488, "question_text": "What kind of growth?", "trigger_span": [4231, 4251], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S70.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4592, "question_text": "What kind?", "trigger_span": [4516, 4550], "answer_text": "ESG", "answer_span": [4672.0, 4687.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S72.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4720, "question_text": "Perform how?", "trigger_span": [4688, 4708], "answer_text": "MSCI", "answer_span": [4893.0, 4908.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "investment.S109.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6564, "question_text": "What is the financial aspect? ", "trigger_span": [6514, 6541], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S115.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6698, "question_text": "What kind of investors? ", "trigger_span": [6614, 6641], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S1.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 123, "question_text": "Why did you want to run away?", "trigger_span": [105, 121], "answer_text": "Because she did not like routine and boredom?", "answer_span": [303.0, 345.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "homeless.S5.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 347, "question_text": "Were you abused as a child?", "trigger_span": [276, 289], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S7.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 543, "question_text": "What kinds of strange people did you meet?", "trigger_span": [469, 501], "answer_text": "She met vagrants,tramps,travelers,hobos,and hitchikers", "answer_span": [980.0, 1036.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S76.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4958, "question_text": "How was it compared?", "trigger_span": [4933, 4956], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S80.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4995, "question_text": "MOre what, exactly? ", "trigger_span": [4981, 4993], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S84.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5061, "question_text": "What kind of cases?", "trigger_span": [5008, 5021], "answer_text": "climate change......", "answer_span": [5182.0, 5217.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "cities.S30.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2859, "question_text": "Why are they not getting along?", "trigger_span": [2761, 2817], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S37.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2917, "question_text": "What changes?", "trigger_span": [2880, 2915], "answer_text": "He has photo proof", "answer_span": [2957.0, 2978.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "cities.S39.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3131, "question_text": "What is the photo containing?", "trigger_span": [2957, 2962], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S41.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3326, "question_text": "What do you mean by mixed up?", "trigger_span": [3316, 3324], "answer_text": "He means in diversity", "answer_span": [3338.0, 3350.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "cities.S43.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3499, "question_text": "How come it's not working in baltimore or san fran but it is in rio?", "trigger_span": [3370, 3396], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S45.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3679, "question_text": "How can we have the same thing in the united states?", "trigger_span": [3610, 3629], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S105.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6351, "question_text": "This is juat a money grab government fund?", "trigger_span": [6259, 6326], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S107.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6425, "question_text": "What kind of returns? ", "trigger_span": [6386, 6412], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S160.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9246, "question_text": "What are our immediate gains?", "trigger_span": [9227, 9244], "answer_text": "we maintain full performance levels", "answer_span": [9252.0, 9279.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous"]}
{"id": "cities.S51.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3864, "question_text": "Why can't we have something like this in america.", "trigger_span": [3826, 3862], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S17.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1134, "question_text": "Why do you think this?", "trigger_span": [1095, 1132], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S22.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1335, "question_text": "Why was he there to watch the archers?", "trigger_span": [1221, 1228], "answer_text": "He was there to observe archers paradox.", "answer_span": [1365.0, 1381.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S61.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4172, "question_text": "Did they make the right bet?", "trigger_span": [4141, 4148], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S67.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4424, "question_text": "Did they succeed?", "trigger_span": [4300, 4310], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S113.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8146, "question_text": "What sort of wins is he talking about?", "trigger_span": [7909, 7912], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S118.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8361, "question_text": "What does Navajo culture have to do with the matter at hand?", "trigger_span": [8149, 8155], "answer_text": "It's a parallel to his situation of working on imperfect initiatives. ", "answer_span": [8382.0, 8402.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S52.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3432, "question_text": "Who is the speaker and their relation to the event? ", "trigger_span": [3350, 3367], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S81.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4346, "question_text": "Is this related to some sort of smart lighting  product?", "trigger_span": [4228, 4237], "answer_text": "Seems to be related to astronomy and potentially a telescope or telescope related product. ", "answer_span": [4440.0, 4459.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S86.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4485, "question_text": "Can you see all the planets?", "trigger_span": [4452, 4459], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S88.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4693, "question_text": "How heavy is the starshade?", "trigger_span": [4562, 4591], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S90.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4878, "question_text": "What's the next step for this plan?", "trigger_span": [4828, 4834], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S92.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4943, "question_text": "What happens after it separates from the telescope?", "trigger_span": [4913, 4922], "answer_text": "It will fly a very large distance away from the telescope after separating from it. ", "answer_span": [5045.0, 5086.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S19.Q6", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1070, "question_text": "Did you ever find the answer to this question?", "trigger_span": [1027, 1068], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S126.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7472, "question_text": "How do they get the  money?", "trigger_span": [7451, 7470], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S11.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1038, "question_text": "Did you take photographs of these people?", "trigger_span": [980, 1036], "answer_text": "Yes she took them in color", "answer_span": [1240.0, 1264.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "homeless.S13.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1230, "question_text": "What is a boxcar?", "trigger_span": [1213, 1228], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S19.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1414, "question_text": "Why dont others get to see them?", "trigger_span": [1384, 1412], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S96.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5088, "question_text": "Where will it eventually land?", "trigger_span": [5032, 5035], "answer_text": "It's going to be adjacent to a star in space.", "answer_span": [5110.0, 5127.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "starshade.S100.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5212, "question_text": "How will this device enable planets to orbit it?", "trigger_span": [5185, 5210], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S46.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3432, "question_text": "What's the example?", "trigger_span": [3392, 3399], "answer_text": "They finished a bunch of automation projects and virtualized their OS", "answer_span": [3589.0, 3627.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "AltLex:Hypophora", "AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S53.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3629, "question_text": "Did you have any other notable projects after 2012?", "trigger_span": [3435, 3439], "answer_text": "These 2012 activities have resulted in saving millions annually in addition to reducing the company's carbon footprint. ", "answer_span": [3790.0, 3798.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "AltLex:Hypophora", "AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "investment.S55.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3860, "question_text": "What are your future plans?", "trigger_span": [3629, 3632], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S24.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2081, "question_text": "If you went to MIT why cant you figure it out?", "trigger_span": [1946, 1966], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S26.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2329, "question_text": "How much do the sockets cost?", "trigger_span": [2294, 2327], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S28.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2532, "question_text": "When will they be available?", "trigger_span": [2492, 2530], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S30.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2793, "question_text": "When will they be available to the public?", "trigger_span": [2537, 2585], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S32.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 3040, "question_text": "Can this tech be used for anything else?", "trigger_span": [2913, 2965], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S57.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3937, "question_text": "What is the next initiative planned to augment your gains thus far?", "trigger_span": [3921, 3928], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S59.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4125, "question_text": "How did Pentair's water venture turn out?", "trigger_span": [4109, 4123], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S9.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 909, "question_text": "Where has your photography been published?", "trigger_span": [716, 753], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S74.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4826, "question_text": "how does a stock market index prove sustainability ?", "trigger_span": [4732, 4750], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S42.Q2", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3483, "question_text": "Why are these laws like this?", "trigger_span": [3370, 3417], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S117.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5893, "question_text": "Why is the position so important?", "trigger_span": [5759, 5789], "answer_text": "can build this technology", "answer_span": [5958.0, 5983.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S119.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6049, "question_text": "why in space?", "trigger_span": [5985, 6012], "answer_text": "take a similar space telescope", "answer_span": [6149.0, 6179.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond", "EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S121.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6248, "question_text": "why an occulter? ", "trigger_span": [6216, 6246], "answer_text": "see someone else's solar system", "answer_span": [6376.0, 6431.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "starshade.S123.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6464, "question_text": "Why the interest?", "trigger_span": [6354, 6375], "answer_text": "earth at center", "answer_span": [6565.0, 6615.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S17.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1619, "question_text": "Why cant they make sockets that are more tolerable?", "trigger_span": [1433, 1484], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S22.Q3", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1867, "question_text": "How can we solve the problem of uncomfortable sockets?", "trigger_span": [1821, 1865], "answer_text": "This seems to help in the process of making things better for patients", "answer_span": [2178.0, 2241.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S1.Q6", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 177, "question_text": "What was their job there?", "trigger_span": [93, 128], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S5.Q6", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 344, "question_text": "What did they learn from her?", "trigger_span": [179, 203], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S25.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2135, "question_text": "What is the downfall?", "trigger_span": [2021, 2036], "answer_text": "geeks and techies taking over the network", "answer_span": [2219.0, 2258.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S27.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2379, "question_text": "What problems has this caused?", "trigger_span": [2158, 2180], "answer_text": "tension over gentrification and new tech companies", "answer_span": [2490.0, 2502.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "cities.S29.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2698, "question_text": "What is the outcome of all this tension?", "trigger_span": [2555, 2577], "answer_text": "the different groups aren't getting along", "answer_span": [2779.0, 2803.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "cities.S35.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2859, "question_text": "Has anything been done to solve this problem?", "trigger_span": [2702, 2743], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S2.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 205, "question_text": "What type of paintings did she do?", "trigger_span": [134, 158], "answer_text": "motifs and elements of her life", "answer_span": [360.0, 379.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "cities.S20.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1666, "question_text": "What kind of sports connect the communities?", "trigger_span": [1647, 1664], "answer_text": "Football, baseball, swimming.", "answer_span": [1678.0, 1747.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S13.Q6", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 958, "question_text": "How is it celebrated?", "trigger_span": [912, 957], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S19.Q7", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1070, "question_text": "How is success converted into mastery?", "trigger_span": [997, 1026], "answer_text": "Placing value on close victories.", "answer_span": [1104.0, 1132.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S142.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8288, "question_text": "What is ESG?", "trigger_span": [7910, 7940], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S28.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2002, "question_text": "What does the ESG do?", "trigger_span": [1895, 1944], "answer_text": "They show the performance of a company's social and environmental impact with energy consumption, innovation capacity ect.", "answer_span": [2156.0, 2211.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S32.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2283, "question_text": "How is innovation capacity measured?", "trigger_span": [2192, 2211], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S36.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2415, "question_text": "Why is this considered juicy information?", "trigger_span": [2383, 2413], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S94.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6964, "question_text": "Was the near win technique banned in Britain?", "trigger_span": [6798, 6840], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S101.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7157, "question_text": "What does asking me about how I envision a great day have to do with gambling?", "trigger_span": [7064, 7095], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S5.Q7", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 344, "question_text": "What kind of style were her paintings>", "trigger_span": [272, 293], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S7.Q6", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 485, "question_text": "What were some of her motifs?", "trigger_span": [350, 366], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S9.Q6", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 645, "question_text": "Why didnt they meet her own mark?", "trigger_span": [582, 612], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S11.Q6", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 801, "question_text": "What happned to the art that was put in the trash?", "trigger_span": [701, 742], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S115.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8014, "question_text": "What is the purpose of this motivational text?", "trigger_span": [7982, 8012], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S7.Q7", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 485, "question_text": "What did she think of those works?", "trigger_span": [446, 483], "answer_text": "They didn't measure up to what she wanted of them.", "answer_span": [578.0, 612.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S9.Q7", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 645, "question_text": "What did she want them to be?", "trigger_span": [622, 644], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S11.Q7", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 801, "question_text": "What was its value?", "trigger_span": [782, 800], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S133.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7524, "question_text": "Why is this funny?", "trigger_span": [7472, 7482], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S135.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7615, "question_text": "Why is the global bond market bigger than stock market?", "trigger_span": [7578, 7613], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S137.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7731, "question_text": "What is the worlds smallest economy?", "trigger_span": [7695, 7729], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S89.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6071, "question_text": "How are we motivated by near wins?", "trigger_span": [6025, 6069], "answer_text": "Getting close to winning motivates us to perform better in future competitions", "answer_span": [6482.0, 6514.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S91.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6361, "question_text": "Was it just frustration that motivated them?", "trigger_span": [6307, 6349], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S44.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3036, "question_text": "Why did the person think about leaving? ", "trigger_span": [3023, 3035], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S48.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3262, "question_text": "Who is this person that decided to stay? ", "trigger_span": [3044, 3071], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S1.Q7", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 177, "question_text": "Where was the musuem?", "trigger_span": [108, 128], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S60.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3279, "question_text": "What are we trying to see in space?", "trigger_span": [3122, 3145], "answer_text": "We are trying to find new planets and other features.", "answer_span": [3501.0, 3522.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S64.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3435, "question_text": "Is the big screen meant to create a shadow effect and increase visibility?", "trigger_span": [3325, 3346], "answer_text": "The shadow would allow us to see a better view of space, and potentially see more planets.", "answer_span": [3501.0, 3522.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S12.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1012, "question_text": "Why haven't they done what? ", "trigger_span": [932, 984], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S16.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1155, "question_text": "What type of picture is it the person is wanting? ", "trigger_span": [1060, 1113], "answer_text": "A distant picture from space. ", "answer_span": [1240.0, 1289.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "starshade.S20.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1291, "question_text": "What is the subject of the photo this person seeks? ", "trigger_span": [1255, 1289], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S46.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3864, "question_text": "What is TEDxRio?", "trigger_span": [3499, 3506], "answer_text": "A section of a website for Rio that you can click on. ", "answer_span": [4089.0, 4129.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"]}
{"id": "investment.S139.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7883, "question_text": "Why is fresh water a problem? Do you have more details about this?", "trigger_span": [7800, 7843], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S141.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8105, "question_text": "What is an integrated ESG?", "trigger_span": [7910, 7924], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S61.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3325, "question_text": "Did it work to put the telescope in space?", "trigger_span": [3279, 3323], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S67.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3524, "question_text": "What is the big screen made of?", "trigger_span": [3325, 3347], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S2.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 267, "question_text": "What are the drivers of change?", "trigger_span": [184, 221], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S6.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 431, "question_text": "Why is it reckless?", "trigger_span": [393, 429], "answer_text": "Because it will jeopardize future returns.", "answer_span": [431.0, 487.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief"]}
{"id": "starshade.S49.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2788, "question_text": "What is the significance of the solar eclipse in the discussion?", "trigger_span": [2764, 2786], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S54.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2901, "question_text": "How are the mechanics of a solar eclipse significant to the larger discussion?", "trigger_span": [2792, 2826], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S56.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3039, "question_text": "Does the solar eclipse affect visibility somehow?", "trigger_span": [3008, 3037], "answer_text": "The shadow of an eclipse can give better visibility when viewing objects in space", "answer_span": [3228.0, 3263.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S58.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3115, "question_text": "What does the moon and its shadow mean to the discussion?", "trigger_span": [3071, 3113], "answer_text": "The shadow of the moon can give us better visibility of the sun by blocking its light", "answer_span": [3191.0, 3223.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg1-as-cond"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S40.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2683, "question_text": "What is T.S.?", "trigger_span": [2678, 2681], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S42.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2896, "question_text": "What is this whole section even about?", "trigger_span": [2683, 2737], "answer_text": "The endurance that archers undergo. ", "answer_span": [2979.0, 3008.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "cities.S53.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3944, "question_text": "What type of website is this? ", "trigger_span": [3891, 3942], "answer_text": "A description of a website dedicated for Rio. ", "answer_span": [4126.0, 4183.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"]}
{"id": "cities.S55.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4185, "question_text": "What exactly is being described in whole here? ", "trigger_span": [3974, 4024], "answer_text": "This is describing a website dedicated towards informing others about the City of Rio. ", "answer_span": [4235.0, 4276.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "cities.S57.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4342, "question_text": "Is the website for all cities, or exclusively Rio? ", "trigger_span": [4242, 4276], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S59.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4472, "question_text": "What exactly is the purpose of what is being explained? ", "trigger_span": [4404, 4428], "answer_text": "A website designed to inform others about Rio culture. ", "answer_span": [4578.0, 4604.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S68.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3566, "question_text": "How would we know exactly where to create a shadow?", "trigger_span": [3438, 3489], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S14.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1246, "question_text": "What are the environmental and social issues related to population growth?", "trigger_span": [1193, 1224], "answer_text": "Environment and social issues also effect the economy and risk/return.", "answer_span": [1246.0, 1269.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "cities.S14.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1553, "question_text": "Is this a good place to live?", "trigger_span": [1174, 1208], "answer_text": "community connection is a positive reason to enjoy a city", "answer_span": [1585.0, 1636.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "cities.S21.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1763, "question_text": "Are the communities united in other ways?", "trigger_span": [1637, 1645], "answer_text": "Under Armour acts as a bridge, connecting the communities", "answer_span": [1870.0, 1914.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S23.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1952, "question_text": "How is San Francisco like Baltimore?", "trigger_span": [1922, 1950], "answer_text": "San Francisco's situation is different than Baltimore's situation", "answer_span": [1960.0, 2002.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S13.Q7", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 958, "question_text": "What is your view of success?", "trigger_span": [817, 835], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S61.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4707, "question_text": "Who is this data aimed at helping?", "trigger_span": [4578, 4609], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S67.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4837, "question_text": "How are they going to 'shake up the seating chart'?", "trigger_span": [4783, 4822], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S33.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2408, "question_text": "What type of archery game are they playing? ", "trigger_span": [2238, 2283], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S38.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2516, "question_text": "Is she competing or practicing? ", "trigger_span": [2451, 2484], "answer_text": "It was said that this was practice. ", "answer_span": [2516.0, 2542.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S20.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1320, "question_text": "How are they relevant to risk and return?", "trigger_span": [1275, 1318], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S78.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5588, "question_text": "What is it that you see?", "trigger_span": [5211, 5220], "answer_text": "that the near win is inbuilt to mastery", "answer_span": [5650.0, 5684.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "homeless.S42.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3483, "question_text": "Why would anyone choose to be homeless?", "trigger_span": [3401, 3441], "answer_text": "The answer is varied depending on the person.", "answer_span": [3610.0, 3616.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora"]}
{"id": "homeless.S44.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3702, "question_text": "How do these travelers respond?", "trigger_span": [3658, 3681], "answer_text": "They respond by saying Freedom.", "answer_span": [3702.0, 3709.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "homeless.S46.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3826, "question_text": "Will society ever change?", "trigger_span": [3720, 3737], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S48.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3982, "question_text": "What are they rebelling against?", "trigger_span": [3971, 3980], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S57.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3062, "question_text": "How does this apply to finding another earth", "trigger_span": [3045, 3061], "answer_text": "It has to do with telescope placement", "answer_span": [3118.0, 3160.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S59.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3249, "question_text": "Where is this telescope located?", "trigger_span": [3115, 3133], "answer_text": "In space", "answer_span": [3304.0, 3323.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S85.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5802, "question_text": "What more is there to know?", "trigger_span": [5760, 5800], "answer_text": "That we are motivated by success but a near win can also push us forward.", "answer_span": [5999.0, 6049.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S87.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5953, "question_text": "What did James Baldwin respond to that question?", "trigger_span": [5886, 5935], "answer_text": "He said you learn how little you know", "answer_span": [5966.0, 5998.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S21.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1472, "question_text": "Why do these issues seem to be so far away and difficult to deal with?", "trigger_span": [1333, 1380], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast", "Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S23.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1520, "question_text": "What are some examples of how individuals avoid responsibility?", "trigger_span": [1497, 1518], "answer_text": "Does financial data alone not tell the whole story?", "answer_span": [1699.0, 1726.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "investment.S8.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 625, "question_text": "How does it rest with institutional investors?", "trigger_span": [600, 623], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S10.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 802, "question_text": "Why is it less complicated?", "trigger_span": [730, 765], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S12.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 882, "question_text": "What do we already know?", "trigger_span": [842, 880], "answer_text": "We have a growing population and shrinking resources. ", "answer_span": [892.0, 932.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S16.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1170, "question_text": "Why is a growing population a problem?", "trigger_span": [934, 967], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S88.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5999, "question_text": "How does gaining more knowledge make you realize that you need more knowledge?", "trigger_span": [5907, 5951], "answer_text": "Being near to having knowledge makes you want to seek it out", "answer_span": [5999.0, 6049.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S90.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6222, "question_text": "How does being closer instead of slightly further away from a goal change performance?", "trigger_span": [6136, 6200], "answer_text": "Silver medalists focus more on improving their performance in the future and trying for the gold next time.", "answer_span": [6465.0, 6514.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S92.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6516, "question_text": "Is frustration for just missing a goal part of motivation to succeed?", "trigger_span": [6307, 6359], "answer_text": "Near wins seem to be a motivating force to continue a behavior", "answer_span": [6660.0, 6697.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S25.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1728, "question_text": "Do investors not take everything into consideration that they should?", "trigger_span": [1561, 1615], "answer_text": "Looking and financials alone will lead to poor investment outcomes for individuals and the world.", "answer_span": [1875.0, 1893.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "investment.S27.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1895, "question_text": "What else should be looked at when making investment decisions?", "trigger_span": [1728, 1789], "answer_text": "Investors should take ESG metrics into consideration right along with financial performance.", "answer_span": [1895.0, 1936.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S29.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2125, "question_text": "How is it determined whether or not a company is being responsible re:meeting ESG guidelines?", "trigger_span": [2089, 2123], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S35.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2367, "question_text": "Who monitors a company to make sure they are performing effective internal oversight?", "trigger_span": [2313, 2365], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S81.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5626, "question_text": "Is the text implying that we should never be satisfied by what we have already accomplished?", "trigger_span": [5417, 5463], "answer_text": "Pushing yourself to reach the next goal promotes mastery of skill.", "answer_span": [5654.0, 5684.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S147.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8288, "question_text": "Where do these people work? Fora government or private institution?", "trigger_span": [8105, 8120], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S93.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6780, "question_text": "What other industries does this apply to?", "trigger_span": [6519, 6555], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S99.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6964, "question_text": "How does it effect our goals?", "trigger_span": [6910, 6962], "answer_text": "It put our goals closer to us when we have a near win.", "answer_span": [7000.0, 7047.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S2.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 296, "question_text": "What is it they want a telescope to do? ", "trigger_span": [211, 252], "answer_text": "They are searching for a new star that may have Earth like planets. ", "answer_span": [546.0, 589.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S6.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 625, "question_text": "What are astronomers planning on doing if they ever find such a planet? ", "trigger_span": [572, 623], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S8.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 695, "question_text": "How did astronomers detect Earth like planets indirectly? ", "trigger_span": [658, 693], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S10.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 922, "question_text": "How far is six billion kilometers? ", "trigger_span": [893, 915], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S86.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5841, "question_text": "How exactly does the Dunning-Kruger effect apply to mastery?", "trigger_span": [5818, 5839], "answer_text": "When you realize where you are lacking knowledge, you know where your deficiencies are.", "answer_span": [5966.0, 5996.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S105.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7505, "question_text": "What is a heptathlon?", "trigger_span": [7468, 7478], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S107.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7733, "question_text": "Was the competition held every 4 years?", "trigger_span": [7601, 7617], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S109.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7927, "question_text": "In what kind of room is this conversation being held?", "trigger_span": [7913, 7925], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S40.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3233, "question_text": "Why do you understand the law so well?", "trigger_span": [3209, 3232], "answer_text": "He's watched people go to jail or receive citations.", "answer_span": [3290.0, 3330.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Disjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S166.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9399, "question_text": "Does this person like discussions of clean energy?", "trigger_span": [9384, 9397], "answer_text": "They seem to like talking about both sides of the climate change issue. ", "answer_span": [9444.0, 9482.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "investment.S168.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9484, "question_text": "Was the comic the thing poking fun at both sides?", "trigger_span": [9412, 9419], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S170.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9641, "question_text": "How should we plan for the future?", "trigger_span": [9619, 9639], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S46.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2764, "question_text": "What kind of technology are you talking about?", "trigger_span": [2425, 2463], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S22.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1758, "question_text": "How do they eat?", "trigger_span": [1645, 1673], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S24.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2013, "question_text": "Is it dangerous being a hobo?", "trigger_span": [1922, 1947], "answer_text": "liberation and freedom", "answer_span": [2184.0, 2206.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "homeless.S26.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2208, "question_text": "Are the hobos happy?", "trigger_span": [2138, 2162], "answer_text": "they take advantage of the perks of a wasteful society", "answer_span": [2370.0, 2389.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "homeless.S28.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2551, "question_text": "Do hobos get sick or unhealthy?", "trigger_span": [2514, 2549], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S149.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8460, "question_text": "What is sustainability risk?", "trigger_span": [8335, 8354], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S151.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8675, "question_text": "What are the long term risks of inaction in this case?", "trigger_span": [8622, 8672], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S153.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8918, "question_text": "Is there any way to prove this?", "trigger_span": [8835, 8880], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Exception.Arg2-as-excpt"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Exception.Arg2-as-excpt"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S103.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7305, "question_text": "How does a near win resemble being general vs clear?", "trigger_span": [7275, 7303], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S171.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9708, "question_text": "What kind of future are they planning?", "trigger_span": [9619, 9639], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S62.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3524, "question_text": "Is the star causing the light?", "trigger_span": [3381, 3415], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S69.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3618, "question_text": "Are you talking about the planets in the solar system?", "trigger_span": [3606, 3616], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S71.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3790, "question_text": "Would heavy waves act differently?", "trigger_span": [3688, 3732], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Similarity"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S73.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3910, "question_text": "How big is the shadow?", "trigger_span": [3893, 3908], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S75.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3974, "question_text": "If spitzer knew the answer, why did he suggest we do this in space?", "trigger_span": [3940, 3972], "answer_text": "We came up with optimal solutons in the last 10 years.", "answer_span": [4095.0, 4128.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S155.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9068, "question_text": "Is the cost of insurance worth it with these odds?", "trigger_span": [8992, 9038], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S17.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1514, "question_text": "Where can we find them?", "trigger_span": [1283, 1322], "answer_text": "riding the highways and freight trains", "answer_span": [1575.0, 1592.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S33.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2831, "question_text": "How do they make a living?", "trigger_span": [2556, 2583], "answer_text": "They are homeless living on the streets.", "answer_span": [3002.0, 3010.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S38.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3154, "question_text": "Where do they go?", "trigger_span": [3092, 3122], "answer_text": "Some of these people go to jail.", "answer_span": [3304.0, 3308.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S17.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1619, "question_text": "How can these issues be eliminated?", "trigger_span": [1532, 1559], "answer_text": "individualized prosthetics", "answer_span": [1979.0, 2004.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "investment.S157.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9127, "question_text": "What are these two things?", "trigger_span": [9078, 9125], "answer_text": "Creating insurance and not sacrificing performance.", "answer_span": [9133.0, 9184.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S163.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9281, "question_text": "How much is the risk reduced this way?", "trigger_span": [9153, 9203], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S1.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 123, "question_text": "Where would you run to?", "trigger_span": [113, 121], "answer_text": "across territory lines", "answer_span": [429.0, 443.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "homeless.S5.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 347, "question_text": "How was your life after childhood?", "trigger_span": [326, 345], "answer_text": "joining and journaling nomadic lives", "answer_span": [822.0, 852.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Comparison.Similarity", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S7.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 543, "question_text": "Then what would happen?", "trigger_span": [509, 529], "answer_text": "opportunities for adventure presented", "answer_span": [622.0, 643.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S30.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2859, "question_text": "How could these communities get along better?", "trigger_span": [2779, 2803], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S37.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2917, "question_text": "What does it lead to?", "trigger_span": [2887, 2915], "answer_text": "It leads to the Evict Twitter movement.", "answer_span": [2917.0, 2932.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S39.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3131, "question_text": "What is happening on the ground in San Francisco?", "trigger_span": [2993, 3024], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S41.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3326, "question_text": "What's mixed up about Rio?", "trigger_span": [3316, 3324], "answer_text": "People are involved with government, newspapers, politics, and columnists.", "answer_span": [3439.0, 3497.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "cities.S43.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3499, "question_text": "What makes the city heterogenous?", "trigger_span": [3338, 3355], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S45.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3679, "question_text": "What kinds of music are they interested in?", "trigger_span": [3653, 3677], "answer_text": "They like Justin Bieber, boy bands, country, gospel, funk, and rap.", "answer_span": [3731.0, 3785.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S115.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5692, "question_text": "What connects the petals? ", "trigger_span": [5658, 5690], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S49.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3532, "question_text": "What is ESG?", "trigger_span": [3322, 3387], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S41.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3326, "question_text": "What is happening in Rio de Janeiro?", "trigger_span": [3301, 3324], "answer_text": "It has all types of people and a diverse group in higher powers.", "answer_span": [3333.0, 3355.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "cities.S43.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3499, "question_text": "What other good traits does Rio de Janeiro have?", "trigger_span": [3405, 3447], "answer_text": "There is a lot of diversity in music.", "answer_span": [3653.0, 3677.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S45.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3679, "question_text": "How else is Rio de Janeiro diverse?", "trigger_span": [3599, 3619], "answer_text": "There is a football team amongst musicians, stand up comedians and different types of fans. ", "answer_span": [3895.0, 3942.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S51.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3864, "question_text": "Is there a drug problem in Rio de Janeiro?", "trigger_span": [3826, 3852], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S46.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3826, "question_text": "What will happen if people aren't given their dignity in their labor?", "trigger_span": [3711, 3737], "answer_text": "People will seek their own freedom.", "answer_span": [3893.0, 3936.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "homeless.S48.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3982, "question_text": "In what ways will they rebel?", "trigger_span": [3971, 3980], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S30.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2859, "question_text": "Who else don't the LGBT community get along with?", "trigger_span": [2761, 2808], "answer_text": "the music community", "answer_span": [2859.0, 2879.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "cities.S37.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2917, "question_text": "What types of things does it lead to?", "trigger_span": [2887, 2915], "answer_text": "It seems as if people are getting evicted.", "answer_span": [2917.0, 2924.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S17.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1134, "question_text": "How do we get over the disappointment of losing?", "trigger_span": [1104, 1132], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S22.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1335, "question_text": "Did the women lose?", "trigger_span": [1198, 1228], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S24.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1608, "question_text": "How long have these women practiced?", "trigger_span": [1563, 1606], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S26.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1848, "question_text": "Why did they speak in numbers?", "trigger_span": [1839, 1846], "answer_text": "They were discussing the way to aim their bow and arrow.", "answer_span": [1882.0, 1921.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous", "Explicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "cities.S51.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3864, "question_text": "What kind of drugs?", "trigger_span": [3847, 3852], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S17.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1134, "question_text": "What value does a near win have?", "trigger_span": [1104, 1132], "answer_text": "In order to hit your target, you have to aim slightly away from it.", "answer_span": [1447.0, 1477.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S22.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1335, "question_text": "Why did you go to watch the archers?", "trigger_span": [1198, 1228], "answer_text": "They wanted to see the archer's paradox.", "answer_span": [1365.0, 1381.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "cities.S39.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3131, "question_text": "How many people are being evicted?", "trigger_span": [3103, 3129], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S53.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2828, "question_text": "What about the eclipse inspired him?", "trigger_span": [2771, 2786], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S55.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3008, "question_text": "How does this relate to the technology you're discussing", "trigger_span": [2870, 2903], "answer_text": "It allows you to see more", "answer_span": [3008.0, 3037.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S96.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 6855, "question_text": "How do near wins effect the brain and body?", "trigger_span": [6747, 6778], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S100.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7048, "question_text": "Do we believe we are more able to accomplish a goal when we get closer to doing so?", "trigger_span": [6910, 6943], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S28.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2039, "question_text": "Did she need support mentally or physically?", "trigger_span": [1991, 2020], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S32.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2220, "question_text": "Were the women able to hit their target?", "trigger_span": [2165, 2189], "answer_text": "She hit many points at many times. ", "answer_span": [2285.0, 2307.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S36.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2408, "question_text": "Why didn't her last arrow hit?", "trigger_span": [2369, 2406], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S161.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9365, "question_text": "In what way can we invest in sustainability? ", "trigger_span": [9081, 9102], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S83.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4239, "question_text": "Does it look like a flower petal?", "trigger_span": [4215, 4237], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S17.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1320, "question_text": "What kind of emissions are responsible for this climate change?", "trigger_span": [1091, 1128], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S22.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1497, "question_text": "What do you want me to do?", "trigger_span": [1472, 1483], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S24.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1617, "question_text": "Don't do what at home?", "trigger_span": [1497, 1518], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S26.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1826, "question_text": "How will the environmental change effect the financial data?", "trigger_span": [1699, 1726], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S9.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 909, "question_text": "What have you learned from this experience?", "trigger_span": [866, 882], "answer_text": "wanderers wishes", "answer_span": [921.0, 934.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "homeless.S11.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1038, "question_text": "What has this dream taught you?", "trigger_span": [938, 970], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S13.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1230, "question_text": "What other impressions exist?", "trigger_span": [1118, 1129], "answer_text": "living their lives as they see fit", "answer_span": [1324.0, 1358.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S14.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1070, "question_text": "Did you find an answer to your question?", "trigger_span": [1027, 1068], "answer_text": "They are piecing the answer together through learning and experiences.", "answer_span": [1134.0, 1167.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S21.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1263, "question_text": "What does \"the gift of a near win\" mean?", "trigger_span": [1104, 1132], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S23.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1487, "question_text": "Why do you have to aim off from the target?", "trigger_span": [1435, 1477], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S25.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1703, "question_text": "What did the women do next?", "trigger_span": [1563, 1606], "answer_text": "They passed the writer and smiled while sizing them up and talking.", "answer_span": [1712.0, 1754.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S27.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1923, "question_text": "Were the numbers actually degrees?", "trigger_span": [1839, 1877], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S29.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2107, "question_text": "Did the archer hit the target?", "trigger_span": [2080, 2105], "answer_text": "She hit different parts of the target with 4 arrows.", "answer_span": [2289.0, 2335.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S22.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1867, "question_text": "How can this problem be solved?", "trigger_span": [1847, 1865], "answer_text": "precision modeling", "answer_span": [2174.0, 2201.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "starshade.S77.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4168, "question_text": "How do we soften the edges?", "trigger_span": [4003, 4051], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S105.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5425, "question_text": "What are the petals? ", "trigger_span": [5399, 5423], "answer_text": "It's a sub-scale star shade", "answer_span": [5425.0, 5455.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S107.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5507, "question_text": "How large is the one we saw? ", "trigger_span": [5468, 5505], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S19.Q8", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1070, "question_text": "Have you found an answer?", "trigger_span": [1037, 1068], "answer_text": "When we near complete achievement.", "answer_span": [1095.0, 1132.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S24.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2081, "question_text": "How can custom prosthetics be made quicker and cheaper than conventional ones?", "trigger_span": [2005, 2024], "answer_text": "MRI for correctness", "answer_span": [2088.0, 2142.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Implicit:Contingency.Purpose.Arg2-as-goal"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S26.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2329, "question_text": "What happened with manufacturing?", "trigger_span": [2294, 2327], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S28.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2532, "question_text": "What materials are used?", "trigger_span": [2361, 2375], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S30.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2793, "question_text": "What are other people's opinions?", "trigger_span": [2740, 2768], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S32.Q4", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 3040, "question_text": "What other ways can this technology help people with disabilities?", "trigger_span": [2833, 2880], "answer_text": "help them reach their life fulfillment", "answer_span": [3255.0, 3316.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S54.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3800, "question_text": "What are they doing with the savings? ", "trigger_span": [3735, 3798], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S56.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3918, "question_text": "How do they decrease the emissions? ", "trigger_span": [3804, 3823], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S58.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3965, "question_text": "What is Pentair?", "trigger_span": [3937, 3963], "answer_text": "a US industrial conglomerate", "answer_span": [3976.0, 4006.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S60.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4150, "question_text": "How much did Pentair save? ", "trigger_span": [4125, 4148], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S54.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3583, "question_text": "How do we get ourselves to master something, such in a way the author is describing.", "trigger_span": [3497, 3520], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S94.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5172, "question_text": "What flies away from the telescope? ", "trigger_span": [5032, 5086], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S101.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5234, "question_text": "What do the planets orbit around? ", "trigger_span": [5185, 5210], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S103.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5321, "question_text": "What have they been working on? ", "trigger_span": [5262, 5288], "answer_text": "A sub-scale star shade", "answer_span": [5425.0, 5455.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "homeless.S42.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3483, "question_text": "Why would they choose that life?", "trigger_span": [3443, 3481], "answer_text": "There are many reasons why they would choose such a life.", "answer_span": [3574.0, 3616.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora"]}
{"id": "homeless.S44.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3702, "question_text": "What is that single word?", "trigger_span": [3687, 3700], "answer_text": "Freedom", "answer_span": [3702.0, 3709.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "investment.S64.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4350, "question_text": "What level of growth did Pentair achieve? ", "trigger_span": [4231, 4271], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S68.Q1", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4488, "question_text": "Is there another relevant case?", "trigger_span": [4457, 4487], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S126.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9040, "question_text": "Why can't they make more visualization techniques?", "trigger_span": [8791, 8801], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S56.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3777, "question_text": "How many times, as described?", "trigger_span": [3583, 3597], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S58.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4013, "question_text": "Why was the author surprised?", "trigger_span": [3794, 3853], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S60.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4234, "question_text": "Why had he only signed 10%?", "trigger_span": [4061, 4107], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S26.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1599, "question_text": "What's not resolved?", "trigger_span": [1573, 1597], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S133.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9158, "question_text": "Why can't they do more? ", "trigger_span": [9061, 9081], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S135.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9292, "question_text": "Do they ever win? ", "trigger_span": [9238, 9280], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S137.Q1", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9498, "question_text": "Whose early paintings did she see? ", "trigger_span": [9361, 9397], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S30.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2776, "question_text": "Who is \"they\"?", "trigger_span": [2551, 2555], "answer_text": "The homeless", "answer_span": [3002.0, 3010.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S37.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3022, "question_text": "What laws are they talking about?", "trigger_span": [2961, 2984], "answer_text": "Its illegal to sit on the street, cover up with a blanket, sleep in your own car, or offer food to a stranger.", "answer_span": [3092.0, 3099.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "homeless.S39.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3209, "question_text": "Why is it illegal to offer food to someone?", "trigger_span": [3183, 3208], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S40.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3233, "question_text": "What other laws are there against homeless people?", "trigger_span": [3209, 3232], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S26.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1848, "question_text": "How do you speak with numbers?", "trigger_span": [1795, 1846], "answer_text": "They were speaking about positions for how they could hit their targets.", "answer_span": [1868.0, 1921.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous", "Explicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S28.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2039, "question_text": "What was the coach watching for?", "trigger_span": [2026, 2037], "answer_text": "He was watching to see how they would shoot.", "answer_span": [2271.0, 2283.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S32.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2220, "question_text": "How talented were the archers?", "trigger_span": [2063, 2105], "answer_text": "They had some talent as shown by the scores.", "answer_span": [2331.0, 2354.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "homeless.S41.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3370, "question_text": "How are homeless people going to pay citations?", "trigger_span": [3312, 3330], "answer_text": "They sometimes get seasonal jobs.", "answer_span": [3533.0, 3557.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "homeless.S43.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3574, "question_text": "Why would anyone want to be homeless?", "trigger_span": [3418, 3441], "answer_text": "freedom", "answer_span": [3702.0, 3709.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "homeless.S45.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3711, "question_text": "What are some other responses?", "trigger_span": [3668, 3681], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S22.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1366, "question_text": "What is being made an example of?", "trigger_span": [1330, 1364], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S24.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1500, "question_text": "What has gotten smaller?", "trigger_span": [1366, 1385], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S19.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1414, "question_text": "What are some unexpected things that you have seen?", "trigger_span": [1389, 1412], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S109.Q1", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5623, "question_text": "What are the petals made of? ", "trigger_span": [5537, 5588], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S36.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2408, "question_text": "Did she miss more than once?", "trigger_span": [2380, 2406], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S161.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9365, "question_text": "How are they investing sustainably?", "trigger_span": [9081, 9102], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S166.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9399, "question_text": "What do you like about it?", "trigger_span": [9384, 9397], "answer_text": "It pokes fun at both sides of the climate change issue.", "answer_span": [9431.0, 9482.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "investment.S168.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9484, "question_text": "How does it poke fun?", "trigger_span": [9431, 9440], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S170.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9641, "question_text": "Do you like Mark Twain?", "trigger_span": [9592, 9602], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S24.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1608, "question_text": "Why do you think they seemed so focused?", "trigger_span": [1593, 1606], "answer_text": "They were well supported by their coach.", "answer_span": [1991.0, 2020.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence", "Implicit:Contingency.Purpose.Arg2-as-goal"]}
{"id": "starshade.S36.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2070, "question_text": "Why is it so bright?", "trigger_span": [2026, 2068], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S62.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4837, "question_text": "What are they doing?", "trigger_span": [4472, 4507], "answer_text": "Determining diversity across populations", "answer_span": [5038.0, 5100.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S69.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5102, "question_text": "What else contributes to diversity?", "trigger_span": [5022, 5068], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S52.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2788, "question_text": "Can you only observe during a rare solar eclipse then?", "trigger_span": [2764, 2786], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S1.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 223, "question_text": "What are some of the biggest drivers of change?", "trigger_span": [184, 221], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S5.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 385, "question_text": "What do environmental and social issues have to do with change?", "trigger_span": [327, 358], "answer_text": "Ignoring them can put expected returns in danger in the long run.", "answer_span": [452.0, 487.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief"]}
{"id": "investment.S7.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 489, "question_text": "Do long-term returns bring in more revenue than short term ones?", "trigger_span": [452, 479], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S25.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1703, "question_text": "What is a fletching?", "trigger_span": [1692, 1701], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S36.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2880, "question_text": "Why can't the different communities get along?", "trigger_span": [2779, 2803], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S71.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5400, "question_text": "Why does the individual think they have the capability?", "trigger_span": [5357, 5398], "answer_text": "The individual thinks documenting relationships will help create positive cities.", "answer_span": [5689.0, 5731.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond"]}
{"id": "cities.S73.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5466, "question_text": "What is a city, as described by this individual?", "trigger_span": [5447, 5465], "answer_text": "The population residing in it.", "answer_span": [5595.0, 5649.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "cities.S75.Q2", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5821, "question_text": "What is ideal for this individual?", "trigger_span": [5781, 5819], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S49.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3432, "question_text": "What caused this individual to compared mastery vs success (what event)?", "trigger_span": [3044, 3097], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S47.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3938, "question_text": "How is the open road an escape?", "trigger_span": [3906, 3936], "answer_text": "liberation and rebellion", "answer_span": [3941.0, 3980.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S28.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1689, "question_text": "Why does the text keep going further out?", "trigger_span": [1644, 1687], "answer_text": "Looks like it's referring the distance of a certain planet", "answer_span": [1825.0, 1844.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S32.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1885, "question_text": "What is lastly 10x further away?", "trigger_span": [1861, 1883], "answer_text": "Alpha Centauri's distance appears to have been described.", "answer_span": [1898.0, 1912.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "investment.S11.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 842, "question_text": "Why is sustainable investing so important?", "trigger_span": [806, 841], "answer_text": "An aging and expanding population", "answer_span": [892.0, 932.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S13.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1017, "question_text": "What does the population number have to do with investing?", "trigger_span": [942, 989], "answer_text": "Natural resource depletion, emissions, and climate change", "answer_span": [1133.0, 1147.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S17.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1666, "question_text": "How does sports connect the two communities?", "trigger_span": [1608, 1664], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S22.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1916, "question_text": "What sport did Michael Phelps play?", "trigger_span": [1733, 1747], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S24.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2021, "question_text": "What different is happening?", "trigger_span": [1983, 2002], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S26.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2260, "question_text": "What kind of network is the geeks taking over?", "trigger_span": [2219, 2230], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S28.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2461, "question_text": "Why is this group distinct?", "trigger_span": [2292, 2303], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S32.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2745, "question_text": "What tension?", "trigger_span": [2494, 2502], "answer_text": "LGBT and geek community tension", "answer_span": [2779.0, 2803.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S64.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4416, "question_text": "Were they burned?", "trigger_span": [4367, 4414], "answer_text": "They were not, his friend would not burn them.", "answer_span": [4416.0, 4455.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S68.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4614, "question_text": "Why do people get so discouraged?", "trigger_span": [4565, 4612], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S33.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2831, "question_text": "What can one do to lose their inner demons?", "trigger_span": [2776, 2800], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S38.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3154, "question_text": "What can we do to combat homelessness?", "trigger_span": [2990, 3020], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S14.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1070, "question_text": "How does success turn into mastery?", "trigger_span": [997, 1026], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S21.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1263, "question_text": "Is varsity archers a sport?", "trigger_span": [1213, 1228], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S23.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1487, "question_text": "What does skew mean?", "trigger_span": [1473, 1477], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S9.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 693, "question_text": "Why does do institutional investors have more power to influence?", "trigger_span": [537, 573], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S7.Q8", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 485, "question_text": "Which motifs and elements recurred?", "trigger_span": [360, 379], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S9.Q8", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 645, "question_text": "What were her expectations?", "trigger_span": [582, 612], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S11.Q8", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 801, "question_text": "What did Elizabeth Murray's neighbor see in this painting?", "trigger_span": [782, 799], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S13.Q8", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 958, "question_text": "How are we always celebrating creativity and mastery?", "trigger_span": [912, 956], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S80.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5465, "question_text": "Do losses have any effect on thriving within the pursuit of mastery?", "trigger_span": [5379, 5415], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S84.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5626, "question_text": "What were some of Duke Ellington's notable works?", "trigger_span": [5493, 5507], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S17.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1291, "question_text": "What analogy is being made?", "trigger_span": [1186, 1224], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S64.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4416, "question_text": "How was he valuing them when wanting them destroyed?", "trigger_span": [4393, 4414], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S47.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3938, "question_text": "How can we change society so that people can thrive instead of just trying to get by?", "trigger_span": [3711, 3743], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S35.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2285, "question_text": "How does someone hit something so small?", "trigger_span": [2165, 2193], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S158.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9281, "question_text": "How do you make sure you're not sacrificing performance?", "trigger_span": [9246, 9279], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S165.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9384, "question_text": "What does the person like, the comic?", "trigger_span": [9365, 9382], "answer_text": "I think they're talking about the comic but it's not spelled out.", "answer_span": [9384.0, 9419.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S167.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9420, "question_text": "What do you like about it?", "trigger_span": [9384, 9419], "answer_text": "They like that it pokes fun at both sides of the issue instead of just one.", "answer_span": [9420.0, 9454.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "investment.S169.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9525, "question_text": "Which side are they on?", "trigger_span": [9500, 9523], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S1.Q8", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 177, "question_text": "What did the retrospective teach you?", "trigger_span": [134, 175], "answer_text": "quite a bit", "answer_span": [177.0, 194.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S5.Q8", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 344, "question_text": "Which 1970's Elizabeth Murray's painting was your favorite?", "trigger_span": [297, 342], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S133.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7524, "question_text": "How much is a lot?", "trigger_span": [7504, 7516], "answer_text": "over 77 trillion", "answer_span": [7602.0, 7613.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S135.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7615, "question_text": "Besides global stock and global bond markets, what are some other potential investors?", "trigger_span": [7528, 7547], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S137.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7731, "question_text": "How can we get them to invest?", "trigger_span": [7702, 7729], "answer_text": "Turn ESG into worthwhile transactions.", "answer_span": [7910.0, 7940.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond"]}
{"id": "investment.S139.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7883, "question_text": "How can we get people to address these challenges?", "trigger_span": [7832, 7874], "answer_text": "give additional money to sustainable companies", "answer_span": [7978.0, 8008.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "homeless.S39.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3209, "question_text": "Why would it be against the law to be kind?", "trigger_span": [3180, 3208], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S41.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3370, "question_text": "Were you also living on the street?", "trigger_span": [3257, 3284], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S43.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3574, "question_text": "Why would anyone live such a dangerous life?", "trigger_span": [3401, 3441], "answer_text": "Freedom is a common answer, but a lot of other answers are hinted at as well.", "answer_span": [3702.0, 3709.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "homeless.S45.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3711, "question_text": "Is it freedom if you're in danger of being jailed all the time?", "trigger_span": [3702, 3709], "answer_text": "It's freedom from a demeaning job, and freedom to work the way you want, even if it's not freedom from fear or persecution.", "answer_span": [3750.0, 3789.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond", "NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S27.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1923, "question_text": "How did they size you up?", "trigger_span": [1743, 1754], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S29.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2107, "question_text": "Did the coach give any instructions?", "trigger_span": [1956, 1961], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S40.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2203, "question_text": "What happens when light diffracts?", "trigger_span": [2167, 2201], "answer_text": "The light is scattering inside the telescope and causes the view of the planet to be obscured.", "answer_span": [2208.0, 2239.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S42.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2372, "question_text": "What are we going to do about all that light?", "trigger_span": [2326, 2346], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S44.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2544, "question_text": "What's the technology?", "trigger_span": [2490, 2508], "answer_text": "A solar eclipse", "answer_span": [2764.0, 2786.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S48.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2742, "question_text": "What did Lyman Spitzer make?", "trigger_span": [2612, 2651], "answer_text": "A solar eclipse", "answer_span": [2764.0, 2786.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "cities.S22.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1916, "question_text": "How do sports bring these two ends together?", "trigger_span": [1846, 1876], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S126.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7472, "question_text": "How do we get institutional investors to invest?", "trigger_span": [7451, 7470], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S62.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4837, "question_text": "How would you shake it up?", "trigger_span": [4796, 4835], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S69.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5102, "question_text": "what does contribute to the development of diversity? ", "trigger_span": [5038, 5100], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S71.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5400, "question_text": "What are those interventions? ", "trigger_span": [5287, 5338], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S35.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2285, "question_text": "Did any of them hit the ten ring?", "trigger_span": [2168, 2193], "answer_text": "She hit two tens.", "answer_span": [2346.0, 2354.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "investment.S158.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9281, "question_text": "How do you invest in sustainably?", "trigger_span": [9081, 9102], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S165.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9384, "question_text": "What comic are you reading?", "trigger_span": [9289, 9294], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S167.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9420, "question_text": "Why do you like it?", "trigger_span": [9410, 9419], "answer_text": "Because it pokes fun at both sides of the climate change issue.", "answer_span": [9431.0, 9482.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "investment.S169.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9525, "question_text": "Which side of the climate change issue are you on?", "trigger_span": [9506, 9523], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S49.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3432, "question_text": "What is mastery?", "trigger_span": [3262, 3304], "answer_text": "The constant pursuit of a goal.", "answer_span": [3449.0, 3495.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S54.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3583, "question_text": "How do yo find value in a near win?", "trigger_span": [3560, 3581], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S56.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3777, "question_text": "How is the creator finding value with something they are clearly unsatisfied with? ", "trigger_span": [3668, 3737], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S58.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4013, "question_text": "How are they valuing their near wins?", "trigger_span": [3933, 3962], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S60.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4234, "question_text": "Did he find value in the other ninety percent?", "trigger_span": [4068, 4107], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S14.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1226, "question_text": "What haven't we done?", "trigger_span": [986, 1011], "answer_text": "Use the telescope for far away viewing", "answer_span": [1226.0, 1264.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "starshade.S21.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1330, "question_text": "What type of telescope is it?", "trigger_span": [1249, 1264], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S36.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2070, "question_text": "Can you make out anything other than the brightness?", "trigger_span": [2026, 2068], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S76.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5368, "question_text": "What things did Ben Saunders do?", "trigger_span": [5257, 5285], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S23.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1423, "question_text": "Are they talking about pictures from space?", "trigger_span": [1366, 1421], "answer_text": "You can see the moon, but it is smaller", "answer_span": [1426.0, 1455.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "starshade.S25.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1569, "question_text": "What is the Kuiper Belt?", "trigger_span": [1556, 1567], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Synchronous"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Synchronous"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S27.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1640, "question_text": "Are they talking about how big things are in space, verses how big we imagine they are?", "trigger_span": [1609, 1638], "answer_text": "When you move further out, you can see the whole picture once the sun comes into the field of  vision", "answer_span": [1780.0, 1811.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S29.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1846, "question_text": "How small is the planet in this perspective?", "trigger_span": [1825, 1844], "answer_text": "When you move further out, you can't even see the planet anymore", "answer_span": [1918.0, 1963.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S35.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1965, "question_text": "Are the planets near Alpha Centauri as big as our planents", "trigger_span": [1898, 1912], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S73.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5466, "question_text": "Why is it your responsibility?", "trigger_span": [5412, 5445], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S75.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5821, "question_text": "How will documenting help diversity?", "trigger_span": [5689, 5731], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S68.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4614, "question_text": "How is this an example of valuing anything?", "trigger_span": [4416, 4443], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S33.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2070, "question_text": "Where are we going next?", "trigger_span": [1885, 1912], "answer_text": "It seems we're stopping here.", "answer_span": [2163.0, 2186.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "starshade.S38.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2141, "question_text": "Why do we want to see the star?", "trigger_span": [2125, 2139], "answer_text": "To observe diffraction.", "answer_span": [2167.0, 2201.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S19.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1246, "question_text": "What else is there?", "trigger_span": [1230, 1244], "answer_text": "The text meant that they're also economic issues.", "answer_span": [1254.0, 1269.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S65.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4614, "question_text": "Were there any other works saved?", "trigger_span": [4524, 4564], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S70.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4814, "question_text": "Is this the concept of pursuing mastery something that most artists experience?", "trigger_span": [4618, 4636], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S72.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4958, "question_text": "Does anyone ever arrive at mastery?", "trigger_span": [4912, 4956], "answer_text": "It sort of seems like an ongoing concept, so it's not something you can arrive at.", "answer_span": [5068.0, 5079.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S74.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5141, "question_text": "Why is crafting your career not under the effects of mastery?", "trigger_span": [5099, 5140], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S23.Q5", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1905, "question_text": "Why do those going not by choice go?", "trigger_span": [1758, 1799], "answer_text": "foster care dropouts and  teenage runaways", "answer_span": [1991.0, 2029.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "homeless.S25.Q4", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2068, "question_text": "But do those escaping abuse get abused in other ways?", "trigger_span": [2030, 2044], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S24.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2021, "question_text": "What's happening in San Francisco that's different?", "trigger_span": [1960, 2019], "answer_text": "There are different groups in San Francisco too but the geeks are taking over.", "answer_span": [2184.0, 2230.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S26.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2260, "question_text": "If the techies are taking over the top half who's at the bottom?", "trigger_span": [2219, 2258], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S28.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2461, "question_text": "What does twitter have to do with hip-hop?", "trigger_span": [2419, 2459], "answer_text": "Twitter people are part of a movement that has people worried about gentrification.", "answer_span": [2584.0, 2629.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "AltLex:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S32.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2745, "question_text": "Why would people be tense about new wealth coming into the city?", "trigger_span": [2639, 2687], "answer_text": "It seems like the text is saying new wealth leads to new groups of people coming in who don't get along with the current group living there.", "answer_span": [2887.0, 2934.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "cities.S36.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2880, "question_text": "Aren't there LGBT people who are part of that same community?", "trigger_span": [2761, 2803], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S141.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8105, "question_text": "How would this benefit investors?", "trigger_span": [8045, 8069], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S81.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5061, "question_text": "What does ESG stand for?", "trigger_span": [5056, 5059], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S86.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5310, "question_text": "What types of changes have they made to conserve energy?", "trigger_span": [5194, 5217], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S88.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5359, "question_text": "What is the strategy used in the correlation?", "trigger_span": [5326, 5337], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S90.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5538, "question_text": "Why aren't more companies using climate change strategies?", "trigger_span": [5511, 5537], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S125.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7395, "question_text": "Who are the institutional investors?", "trigger_span": [7335, 7358], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S131.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7472, "question_text": "Are they willing to invest the money that they have into saving the environment?", "trigger_span": [7465, 7470], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S14.Q5", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1414, "question_text": "What types of sides are they seeing?", "trigger_span": [1367, 1412], "answer_text": "truckers and soccer moms", "answer_span": [1598.0, 1634.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S21.Q5", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 1635, "question_text": "Where do they go by train?", "trigger_span": [1527, 1545], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S17.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1291, "question_text": "Will it be earth or mars based?", "trigger_span": [1242, 1289], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S22.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1366, "question_text": "Will we even be able to see earth from that distance?", "trigger_span": [1295, 1328], "answer_text": "It will be smaller with less resolution and detail.", "answer_span": [1366.0, 1421.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S24.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1500, "question_text": "Will we be able to see it?", "trigger_span": [1461, 1498], "answer_text": "It cannot be resolved from this distance.", "answer_span": [1569.0, 1597.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "AltLex:Temporal.Synchronous"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S133.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9158, "question_text": "What does all this building lead to?", "trigger_span": [9083, 9118], "answer_text": "It leads to goal attainment.", "answer_span": [9234.0, 9280.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "homeless.S27.Q5", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2370, "question_text": "But aren't the slaving away in a different way at an illusion?", "trigger_span": [2294, 2334], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S11.Q5", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1182, "question_text": "Is there a way to make the prosthetic fit properly?", "trigger_span": [1148, 1174], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S13.Q5", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1311, "question_text": "Is there a way to speed up the process to get a comfortable socket at a reasonable price?", "trigger_span": [1232, 1258], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S19.Q5", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1561, "question_text": "What can be done to prevent the pressure sores and blisters?", "trigger_span": [1476, 1497], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S171.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9708, "question_text": "What are you planning?", "trigger_span": [9619, 9639], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S26.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1599, "question_text": "what can be done to make it resolve?", "trigger_span": [1569, 1597], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S28.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1689, "question_text": "what can we see from this distance?", "trigger_span": [1644, 1687], "answer_text": "The sun", "answer_span": [1780.0, 1811.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S32.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1885, "question_text": "What will we see from this distance?", "trigger_span": [1861, 1883], "answer_text": "All we can see is the star and its brightness. ", "answer_span": [1989.0, 2018.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S53.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3497, "question_text": "are all constant pursuits mastery?", "trigger_span": [3479, 3495], "answer_text": "Mastery is when people see it as fantastic, but the creator can see flaws and wants to perfect it further", "answer_span": [3560.0, 3581.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S55.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3712, "question_text": "When does the creator stop tweaking something?", "trigger_span": [3668, 3710], "answer_text": "Some creators never stop working on a piece", "answer_span": [3946.0, 3962.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"]}
{"id": "investment.S109.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6564, "question_text": "What if a company only has two of the three?", "trigger_span": [6484, 6530], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S115.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6698, "question_text": "How do other investors see it?", "trigger_span": [6665, 6696], "answer_text": "others don't see the benefit, just the added work", "answer_span": [6712.0, 6748.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "cities.S70.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5252, "question_text": "What new way is that?", "trigger_span": [5243, 5250], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S72.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5447, "question_text": "What kinds of interventions?", "trigger_span": [5294, 5307], "answer_text": "Documenting relationships in a more authentic way.", "answer_span": [5689.0, 5731.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond"]}
{"id": "cities.S74.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5651, "question_text": "What kinds of relationships?", "trigger_span": [5595, 5619], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S62.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4524, "question_text": "What works do we have?", "trigger_span": [4498, 4503], "answer_text": "America, The Trial and The Castle", "answer_span": [4524.0, 4563.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S30.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1965, "question_text": "What planet is referenced?", "trigger_span": [1945, 1955], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S37.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2113, "question_text": "What planet is in the red circle?", "trigger_span": [2086, 2111], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S39.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2163, "question_text": "Are we wanting to see the planet?", "trigger_span": [2113, 2124], "answer_text": "The light makes it hard to see the planet.", "answer_span": [2289.0, 2299.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S41.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2301, "question_text": "Which planet is it?", "trigger_span": [2293, 2299], "answer_text": "Earth", "answer_span": [2586.0, 2591.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S58.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4369, "question_text": "Are they taking things from social media and then applying them to how cities are represented?", "trigger_span": [4230, 4272], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S60.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4578, "question_text": "What type of segregation are they speaking of?", "trigger_span": [4437, 4470], "answer_text": "People find groups to cling to", "answer_span": [4718.0, 4770.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S69.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4680, "question_text": "What is the final sentence fragment of The Castle?", "trigger_span": [4594, 4612], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S71.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4912, "question_text": "Are you comparing Michelangelo to Kafka?", "trigger_span": [4736, 4748], "answer_text": "Both people made sacrifices for their art.", "answer_span": [5051.0, 5094.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S73.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5051, "question_text": "Is mastery only about reaching?", "trigger_span": [4912, 4938], "answer_text": "Mastery involves sacrifice.", "answer_span": [5051.0, 5094.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S75.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5211, "question_text": "Do you have any specific individuals in mind?", "trigger_span": [5141, 5184], "answer_text": "Ben Saunders", "answer_span": [5273.0, 5285.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S51.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2764, "question_text": "What was suggested by Spitzer?", "trigger_span": [2612, 2614], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S65.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4929, "question_text": "Is this about analyzing diversity?", "trigger_span": [4918, 4927], "answer_text": "They are studying how we approach thinking about diversity.", "answer_span": [5196.0, 5237.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S46.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3314, "question_text": "What is the difference between excellence and mastery?", "trigger_span": [3262, 3304], "answer_text": "Mastery is constantly trying to improve and be the best you can be", "answer_span": [3432.0, 3469.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S101.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6022, "question_text": "Is this only available to Australians?", "trigger_span": [5987, 6021], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S103.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6156, "question_text": "Does CalPERS invest in ESG?", "trigger_span": [6022, 6048], "answer_text": "they are trying to get 100 percent sustainable investments", "answer_span": [6237.0, 6293.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S105.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6351, "question_text": "How long before they are at 100%?", "trigger_span": [6237, 6293], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S107.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6425, "question_text": "What do they think will happen to long term return with ESG?", "trigger_span": [6356, 6412], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S49.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3882, "question_text": "Is that about a music streaming platform?", "trigger_span": [3623, 3677], "answer_text": "Whatever this is, also looks at sports and arts", "answer_span": [3974.0, 4014.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"]}
{"id": "cities.S54.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4072, "question_text": "Is this a social media platform?", "trigger_span": [4035, 4070], "answer_text": "They are talking about diversity in Rio", "answer_span": [4126.0, 4183.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"]}
{"id": "cities.S56.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4211, "question_text": "Where is the data from?", "trigger_span": [4191, 4209], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S147.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8288, "question_text": "How will we remedy this situation?", "trigger_span": [8248, 8287], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S1.Q5", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 220, "question_text": "Do you still live in Sierra Leone?", "trigger_span": [73, 104], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S5.Q5", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 427, "question_text": "Has Sierra Leone recovered after the long war?", "trigger_span": [260, 281], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S7.Q5", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 752, "question_text": "How did you ensure change for the future generations growing up in Sierra Leone?", "trigger_span": [682, 732], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S9.Q5", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1023, "question_text": "Did you create something new for the the amputees to assist them?", "trigger_span": [991, 1022], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S17.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1666, "question_text": "What are people in your group interested in that the others aren't?", "trigger_span": [1381, 1434], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S64.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4772, "question_text": "Where is this data from?", "trigger_span": [4605, 4647], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S68.Q3", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4929, "question_text": "So what introduces diversity into a population?", "trigger_span": [4886, 4927], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S77.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5417, "question_text": "Is Ben Saunders still alive?", "trigger_span": [5287, 5299], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S83.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5588, "question_text": "What are some other examples?", "trigger_span": [5417, 5419], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S123.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6464, "question_text": "Do you think its likely you'll see another solar system?", "trigger_span": [6354, 6403], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S125.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6617, "question_text": "Where are the other planets?", "trigger_span": [6464, 6520], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S127.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6778, "question_text": "What are the odds you'll find those things?", "trigger_span": [6638, 6673], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S65.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4488, "question_text": "What is the \"new New World\"", "trigger_span": [4329, 4347], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S70.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4592, "question_text": "How many companies pay attention to sustainability?", "trigger_span": [4516, 4550], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S72.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4720, "question_text": "Do sustainable companies attract different consumers?", "trigger_span": [4688, 4718], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S109.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5623, "question_text": "What is JPL?", "trigger_span": [5618, 5621], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S115.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5692, "question_text": "Why do they have to rotate?", "trigger_span": [5652, 5690], "answer_text": "They have to go to the same place each time.", "answer_span": [5717.0, 5755.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S74.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4826, "question_text": "How about companies from undeveloped markets?", "trigger_span": [4775, 4807], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S76.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4958, "question_text": "Is there a tradeoff over a longer period?", "trigger_span": [4910, 4956], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S80.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4995, "question_text": "We want more companies or more information?", "trigger_span": [4981, 4993], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S84.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5061, "question_text": "Is there or isn't there outperformance from ESG?", "trigger_span": [5023, 5059], "answer_text": "They have out performed by about 2/3s over almost 8 years", "answer_span": [5268.0, 5308.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S94.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5967, "question_text": "What other kinds of companies are they invested in?", "trigger_span": [5855, 5899], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S94.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5172, "question_text": "What are they looking at through the telescope?", "trigger_span": [5088, 5127], "answer_text": "Planets are orbiting around what they're looking at", "answer_span": [5178.0, 5210.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "investment.S56.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3918, "question_text": "What else are they doing to promote sustainability?", "trigger_span": [3860, 3916], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S58.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3965, "question_text": "What is the Pentair example?", "trigger_span": [3937, 3963], "answer_text": "They sold power tools and reinvested the funds in a water business", "answer_span": [4074.0, 4123.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Succession", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "investment.S60.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4150, "question_text": "Are there any more examples?", "trigger_span": [4125, 4148], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S64.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4350, "question_text": "What is the new world?", "trigger_span": [4329, 4348], "answer_text": "A world where resources are scarce", "answer_span": [4357.0, 4404.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S101.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5234, "question_text": "Where is this taking place?", "trigger_span": [5212, 5232], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S103.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5321, "question_text": "What have they been working on for so long?", "trigger_span": [5273, 5319], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S105.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5425, "question_text": "What are these petals they're talking about?", "trigger_span": [5399, 5423], "answer_text": "It sounds like the petals are something called a sub-scale star shade", "answer_span": [5425.0, 5455.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S107.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5507, "question_text": "What are some of its other properties?", "trigger_span": [5462, 5505], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S43.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2398, "question_text": "How do we get rid of the light?", "trigger_span": [2375, 2396], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S45.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2612, "question_text": "What is the coolest technology?", "trigger_span": [2535, 2542], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S57.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3855, "question_text": "How does a creator know to stop working on a piece?", "trigger_span": [3725, 3747], "answer_text": "Some creators never stop working on a piece?", "answer_span": [4061.0, 4107.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S59.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4109, "question_text": "Who decides what is a masterpiece?", "trigger_span": [3893, 3918], "answer_text": "The artist doesn't decide which of his works is a masterpiece", "answer_span": [4234.0, 4262.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S61.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4354, "question_text": "Did he want his diaries published?", "trigger_span": [4319, 4352], "answer_text": "He wanted them destroyed", "answer_span": [4393.0, 4414.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S67.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4524, "question_text": "Did Kafka plan to have anything he wrote published?", "trigger_span": [4481, 4522], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S49.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3532, "question_text": "What type of company is this?", "trigger_span": [3352, 3355], "answer_text": "I don't know what type of company it is but I at least know that they are involved in automation.", "answer_span": [3586.0, 3627.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "AltLex:Hypophora", "AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S54.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3800, "question_text": "What are they doing with these savings?", "trigger_span": [3752, 3770], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S135.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9292, "question_text": "Does this cause you to change what you want to achieve?", "trigger_span": [9190, 9233], "answer_text": "Our achievements always leave us wanting more.", "answer_span": [9452.0, 9496.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S137.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9498, "question_text": "How do we become complete people?", "trigger_span": [9477, 9496], "answer_text": "We keep striving for it but hopefully it never ends.", "answer_span": [9520.0, 9551.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "homeless.S30.Q5", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2776, "question_text": "What makes the life far from idyllic?", "trigger_span": [2723, 2774], "answer_text": "The life is dangerous, with addiction, trouble with law enforcement, and environmental dangers.", "answer_span": [2831.0, 2871.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "homeless.S37.Q5", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3022, "question_text": "If it's such a hard life why is it against the law?", "trigger_span": [2980, 3020], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S92.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5654, "question_text": "Is vanguard helping with investing in the climate change strategies?", "trigger_span": [5644, 5652], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S96.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5783, "question_text": "Is Hesta safe to invest in?", "trigger_span": [5661, 5666], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S100.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5987, "question_text": "What strategies are they investing in?", "trigger_span": [5881, 5899], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S68.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4488, "question_text": "What are the other companies doing things like this?", "trigger_span": [4457, 4487], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S103.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5321, "question_text": "When is this technology going to be launched?", "trigger_span": [5297, 5319], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S105.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5425, "question_text": "When is the next test?", "trigger_span": [5321, 5354], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S2.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 386, "question_text": "What other ways should we think about cities?", "trigger_span": [308, 335], "answer_text": "new kind of maps", "answer_span": [436.0, 460.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "cities.S6.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 461, "question_text": "What is a non-geograhic map?", "trigger_span": [439, 459], "answer_text": "relationships between people", "answer_span": [471.0, 510.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "cities.S8.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 730, "question_text": "What is considered a network?", "trigger_span": [710, 729], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S10.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1034, "question_text": "What are the Latino folks concerned about?", "trigger_span": [944, 1006], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S12.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1209, "question_text": "What are some other community names?", "trigger_span": [1093, 1112], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Reason+Belief", "Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S16.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1509, "question_text": "Is there a large hip-hop music scene in Baltimore?", "trigger_span": [1395, 1434], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S133.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9158, "question_text": "What does their former self look like?", "trigger_span": [9120, 9156], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S135.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9292, "question_text": "What are they trying to master?", "trigger_span": [9158, 9188], "answer_text": "They are trying to master completion", "answer_span": [9498.0, 9518.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S137.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9498, "question_text": "Who is Elizabeth Murray?", "trigger_span": [9320, 9336], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S58.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3965, "question_text": "What is Pentair doing?", "trigger_span": [3945, 3963], "answer_text": "They changed their business model.", "answer_span": [4032.0, 4073.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Succession"]}
{"id": "cities.S20.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1666, "question_text": "What sports do the people of Baltimore care about?", "trigger_span": [1608, 1665], "answer_text": "Orioles baseball, Ravens football", "answer_span": [1678.0, 1731.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S1.Q9", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 177, "question_text": "What style does Murray feature?", "trigger_span": [151, 175], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S5.Q9", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 344, "question_text": "What other decades did she paint in?", "trigger_span": [328, 342], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S101.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5234, "question_text": "Who is this person speaking in front of?", "trigger_span": [5212, 5222], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S6.Q5", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 635, "question_text": "Where do you live now?", "trigger_span": [557, 605], "answer_text": "It suggests that she still lives in Sierra Leone", "answer_span": [635.0, 681.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S8.Q5", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 938, "question_text": "How old are you now?", "trigger_span": [752, 782], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S10.Q5", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1054, "question_text": "Did the prosthetic sockets get fixed?", "trigger_span": [985, 1022], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S12.Q5", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1302, "question_text": "How did they cope with the situation in the mean time?", "trigger_span": [1211, 1258], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession+SpeechAct.Arg2-as-denier+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession+SpeechAct.Arg2-as-denier+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S16.Q5", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1428, "question_text": "Are there new methods for prosthetists?", "trigger_span": [1311, 1356], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S20.Q5", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1619, "question_text": "Are there other consequences from uncomfortable sockets?", "trigger_span": [1428, 1484], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S68.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4488, "question_text": "Are there going to be more examples?", "trigger_span": [4457, 4487], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S126.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9040, "question_text": "A voracious what?", "trigger_span": [9027, 9038], "answer_text": "Unfinished path", "answer_span": [9040.0, 9081.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Implicit:Contingency.Purpose.Arg2-as-goal"]}
{"id": "cities.S49.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3882, "question_text": "What kind of event is this?", "trigger_span": [3824, 3839], "answer_text": "Appears to be some kind of fair or festival.", "answer_span": [3974.0, 4024.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"]}
{"id": "cities.S54.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4072, "question_text": "Represented in a different way from what?", "trigger_span": [4035, 4070], "answer_text": "Rio is multicultural so it's different.", "answer_span": [4126.0, 4159.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"]}
{"id": "cities.S56.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4211, "question_text": "What are they studying?", "trigger_span": [4185, 4209], "answer_text": "They're trying to study how cities differ.", "answer_span": [4266.0, 4272.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "cities.S58.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4369, "question_text": "What are they trying to do with this data?", "trigger_span": [4342, 4368], "answer_text": "They're trying to see how segregation can be reduced.", "answer_span": [4437.0, 4471.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora"]}
{"id": "starshade.S23.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1423, "question_text": "Why are we trying to make the image smaller?", "trigger_span": [1366, 1421], "answer_text": "They're trying to show how small the earth gets when you move far away from it.", "answer_span": [1599.0, 1638.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "starshade.S25.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1569, "question_text": "What is the Kuiper Belt?", "trigger_span": [1552, 1567], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Synchronous"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Synchronous"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S27.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1640, "question_text": "What causes it to be so hard to see?", "trigger_span": [1569, 1597], "answer_text": "It's bunched up near the sun from this distance.", "answer_span": [1776.0, 1811.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S29.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1846, "question_text": "What is the Oort Cloud?", "trigger_span": [1712, 1722], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S31.Q5", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2882, "question_text": "Did these sockets change many people's lives?", "trigger_span": [2804, 2851], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S113.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6845, "question_text": "What job does this person have?", "trigger_span": [6642, 6659], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S60.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4578, "question_text": "How can we choose not to do it?", "trigger_span": [4513, 4541], "answer_text": "Relocate people or get the seating flipped around a bit.", "answer_span": [4796.0, 4835.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "cities.S64.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4772, "question_text": "How are they using the data to reduce segregation?", "trigger_span": [4613, 4647], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S68.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4929, "question_text": "How does race differ from diversity?", "trigger_span": [4886, 4927], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S14.Q5", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1561, "question_text": "What are the new methods for creating sockets?", "trigger_span": [1311, 1356], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S21.Q5", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1739, "question_text": "Did a solution for this problem get discovered?", "trigger_span": [1619, 1661], "answer_text": "Not yet", "answer_span": [1875.0, 1887.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S23.Q5", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 1925, "question_text": "How long did it take for a new solution?", "trigger_span": [1893, 1922], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S53.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3497, "question_text": "Mastery of what?", "trigger_span": [3432, 3439], "answer_text": "Mastery of artwork.", "answer_span": [3844.0, 3853.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S55.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3712, "question_text": "How can something be mastered if the creator doesn't consider it such?", "trigger_span": [3676, 3710], "answer_text": "It's a near win regardless.", "answer_span": [3765.0, 3776.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S57.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3855, "question_text": "How is something riddled with difficulties and flaws a near win?", "trigger_span": [3712, 3747], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S59.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4109, "question_text": "How can a master think most of his works are incomplete?", "trigger_span": [3885, 3918], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S61.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4354, "question_text": "Why did Kafka see incompletion everywhere?", "trigger_span": [4234, 4262], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "prosthetic.S25.Q5", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2276, "question_text": "Are these sockets expensive or affordable?", "trigger_span": [1970, 2004], "answer_text": "Cheap", "answer_span": [2492.0, 2530.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg1-as-detail"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S27.Q5", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2462, "question_text": "Are these sockets durable?", "trigger_span": [2338, 2375], "answer_text": "Seems to be durable", "answer_span": [2750.0, 2790.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg1-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg1-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S29.Q5", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 2691, "question_text": "Did the veteran find the new socket to be comfortable?", "trigger_span": [2587, 2622], "answer_text": "Very comfortable, soft", "answer_span": [2725.0, 2738.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S126.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9040, "question_text": "What is the coach giving himself over to?", "trigger_span": [8997, 9038], "answer_text": "A path or task that never ends.", "answer_span": [9040.0, 9081.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Implicit:Contingency.Purpose.Arg2-as-goal"]}
{"id": "prosthetic.S2.Q5", "source_id": "prosthetic", "source_cutoff": 332, "question_text": "Was your village burned down?", "trigger_span": [299, 330], "answer_text": "Yes", "answer_span": [481.0, 506.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S67.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4524, "question_text": "Is being a master equivalent to being an extreme perfectionist?", "trigger_span": [4354, 4414], "answer_text": "It's about never being satisfied with your work.", "answer_span": [4657.0, 4678.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S110.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5692, "question_text": "What are the petals for?", "trigger_span": [5507, 5535], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S117.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5893, "question_text": "What happens if the petals don't go to the same place?", "trigger_span": [5710, 5755], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S119.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6049, "question_text": "How would this be used in space?", "trigger_span": [5985, 6012], "answer_text": "used with a telescope", "answer_span": [6156.0, 6179.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond", "EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S121.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 6248, "question_text": "What is an occulter?", "trigger_span": [6216, 6231], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S46.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3314, "question_text": "/What is a ten ring?", "trigger_span": [3171, 3179], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S60.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4150, "question_text": "We're they successful?", "trigger_span": [4125, 4148], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S64.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4350, "question_text": "What is the new New World?", "trigger_span": [4329, 4347], "answer_text": "The needs of the middle class.", "answer_span": [4350.0, 4399.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S110.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6698, "question_text": "What does ESG stand for?", "trigger_span": [6445, 6504], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S117.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6951, "question_text": "How do they expect you to make the money?", "trigger_span": [6934, 6949], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S119.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7016, "question_text": "Why do they suggest giving the profits to charities?", "trigger_span": [6951, 6980], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S121.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7144, "question_text": "Who should hold the companies accountable for playing their part in sustaining the environment?", "trigger_span": [7124, 7142], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S123.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7290, "question_text": "How are they compatible?", "trigger_span": [7278, 7288], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S107.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5507, "question_text": "What does a star shade do?", "trigger_span": [5445, 5455], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S54.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3800, "question_text": "Do these companies have employees that work from home, then?", "trigger_span": [3660, 3681], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S7.Q9", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 485, "question_text": "What did she think of those early works?", "trigger_span": [435, 484], "answer_text": "she's not impressed!", "answer_span": [582.0, 612.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S9.Q9", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 645, "question_text": "How is her painting different now than in the 70s?", "trigger_span": [520, 557], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S11.Q9", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 801, "question_text": "Did the neighbor sell the painting she took out of the trash?", "trigger_span": [752, 773], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S13.Q9", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 958, "question_text": "Does Murray think she's mastered painting?", "trigger_span": [919, 956], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S19.Q9", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1070, "question_text": "What other questions do you ask yourself?", "trigger_span": [1035, 1068], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S142.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8288, "question_text": "What is ESG?", "trigger_span": [7910, 7940], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S149.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8460, "question_text": "How do you define sustainability risk?", "trigger_span": [8318, 8375], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S124.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7331, "question_text": "How are investing and sustainability compatible?", "trigger_span": [7270, 7288], "answer_text": "Investors have money to promote sustainability", "answer_span": [7451.0, 7470.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Q/A"]}
{"id": "investment.S128.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7421, "question_text": "What can investors invest in to help sustainability?", "trigger_span": [7395, 7420], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Q/A"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Q/A"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S132.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7496, "question_text": "How can you convince them to invest?", "trigger_span": [7483, 7494], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S151.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8675, "question_text": "What are the long range costs of inaction on clean water and air?", "trigger_span": [8622, 8672], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S153.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8918, "question_text": "What are the consensus on the odds?", "trigger_span": [8758, 8789], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Exception.Arg2-as-excpt"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S155.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9068, "question_text": "What kind of insurance might there be for clean water and air?", "trigger_span": [8989, 9038], "answer_text": "investing sustainably could help", "answer_span": [9078.0, 9126.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous"]}
{"id": "investment.S157.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9127, "question_text": "What are the two things that investing sustainably does?", "trigger_span": [9078, 9126], "answer_text": "creating insurance and not sacrificing performance", "answer_span": [9246.0, 9280.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous"]}
{"id": "investment.S163.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9281, "question_text": "What are the risks to the economy?", "trigger_span": [9153, 9203], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S35.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1965, "question_text": "How is it gone? Did it disappear from view?", "trigger_span": [1959, 1963], "answer_text": "The star greatly outshines the planet.", "answer_span": [2026.0, 2068.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S22.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1366, "question_text": "How far away are we going to move?", "trigger_span": [1291, 1315], "answer_text": "There going 10 further again", "answer_span": [1461.0, 1498.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S24.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1500, "question_text": "Why are we looking at the little moon?", "trigger_span": [1444, 1455], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S26.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1599, "question_text": "What are you trying to resolve?", "trigger_span": [1578, 1597], "answer_text": "pale blue dot ", "answer_span": [1599.0, 1638.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "starshade.S28.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1689, "question_text": "How far away are you going to move?", "trigger_span": [1665, 1687], "answer_text": "ten times further away again", "answer_span": [1861.0, 1883.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S116.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8146, "question_text": "Can you give an example of such a myth?", "trigger_span": [8088, 8144], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S14.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1226, "question_text": "Why haven't we done what?", "trigger_span": [986, 1011], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S21.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1330, "question_text": "Why are we moving a telescope far into outer space?", "trigger_span": [1291, 1328], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S84.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4346, "question_text": "Has this been done in space yet, or just as an experiment?", "trigger_span": [4318, 4344], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S30.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2367, "question_text": "Which metric is most important?", "trigger_span": [1895, 1944], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S37.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2560, "question_text": "Why is sustainable investing important?", "trigger_span": [2483, 2558], "answer_text": "It prevents future harm to people and the planet.", "answer_span": [2593.0, 2629.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence", "Explicit:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner"]}
{"id": "investment.S39.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2856, "question_text": "What are some examples of sustainable outcomes?", "trigger_span": [2675, 2728], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S41.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2997, "question_text": "Which CEOs are engaged in sustainable investing?", "trigger_span": [2892, 2905], "answer_text": "About 80% of CEOs see sustainability as crucial to their industry.", "answer_span": [2997.0, 3028.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "starshade.S65.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3566, "question_text": "Which planets could we see?", "trigger_span": [3501, 3522], "answer_text": "It doesn't work, so we can't see any planets.", "answer_span": [3598.0, 3616.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S70.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3676, "question_text": "Why doesn't it work?", "trigger_span": [3640, 3674], "answer_text": "The screen doesn't block the light, because the light diffracts around it.", "answer_span": [3703.0, 3751.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "starshade.S72.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3886, "question_text": "Would a bigger screen solve the problem?", "trigger_span": [3845, 3884], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S45.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3311, "question_text": "How much money has sustainable investing produced?", "trigger_span": [3261, 3309], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S51.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3432, "question_text": "What's a good example of ESG being used today?", "trigger_span": [3388, 3430], "answer_text": "The moved some applications to the cloud and retired others. They virtualized their OS environments.", "answer_span": [3454.0, 3491.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "AltLex:Hypophora", "AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "cities.S73.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5466, "question_text": "What is a city?", "trigger_span": [5450, 5465], "answer_text": "A city is relationships", "answer_span": [5583.0, 5619.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "cities.S75.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5821, "question_text": "How will you document those relationships?", "trigger_span": [5689, 5717], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S49.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3432, "question_text": "What is success?", "trigger_span": [3335, 3342], "answer_text": "A near win is success", "answer_span": [3765.0, 3776.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S54.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3583, "question_text": "Why should we value the near win?", "trigger_span": [3563, 3581], "answer_text": "We as humans see our work flawed but that can be a near win", "answer_span": [3765.0, 3776.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S56.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3777, "question_text": "Is near win a success?", "trigger_span": [3765, 3776], "answer_text": "protagonist was him", "answer_span": [4197.0, 4232.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S80.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4198, "question_text": "What do you think will happen in the next 10 years?", "trigger_span": [4088, 4114], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S104.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7399, "question_text": "How can we fight back against these gambling abuses?", "trigger_span": [7275, 7303], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S106.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7601, "question_text": "Did Jackie Joyner-Kersee win in the follow-up competition?", "trigger_span": [7564, 7599], "answer_text": "Yes, she won in 1988.", "answer_span": [7601.0, 7626.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S108.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7806, "question_text": "So near misses are good for us, in life?", "trigger_span": [7733, 7769], "answer_text": "We thrive when we stay just short of the goal.", "answer_span": [8030.0, 8073.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S112.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7963, "question_text": "How could you manufacture a near miss?", "trigger_span": [7856, 7901], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S118.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 6983, "question_text": "Why does that comment annoy you so much?", "trigger_span": [6845, 6888], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S120.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7061, "question_text": "What does he want to clarify?", "trigger_span": [7024, 7048], "answer_text": "He believes investors have limited social responsibility", "answer_span": [7144.0, 7189.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "investment.S122.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7270, "question_text": "What solution he is offering for sustainability?", "trigger_span": [7239, 7268], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S43.Q2", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3229, "question_text": "Who is the 7% that does not see ESG as important?", "trigger_span": [3142, 3164], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S109.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5623, "question_text": "What else are they building?", "trigger_span": [5560, 5588], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S115.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5692, "question_text": "What happens once the petals are in place?", "trigger_span": [5673, 5690], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S49.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3532, "question_text": "What were the results of the migration to the cloud?", "trigger_span": [3441, 3503], "answer_text": "It allowed them to save 23 million in operating costs.", "answer_span": [3741.0, 3770.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "AltLex:Hypophora", "AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "investment.S54.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3800, "question_text": "What is the company doing with the reduced costs?", "trigger_span": [3741, 3789], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S56.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3918, "question_text": "How does this effect the people who drive for the company?", "trigger_span": [3892, 3916], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S17.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1291, "question_text": "What will we see?", "trigger_span": [1155, 1184], "answer_text": "the little moon", "answer_span": [1436.0, 1455.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S97.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7048, "question_text": "What other abuses are there in the gambling industry?", "trigger_span": [6798, 6829], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S102.Q2", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7271, "question_text": "Is this from a TED talk?", "trigger_span": [7186, 7213], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S60.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4234, "question_text": "Can we measure our success ourselves?", "trigger_span": [4185, 4232], "answer_text": "No we can't we see our work as flawed", "answer_span": [4240.0, 4262.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S64.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4416, "question_text": "Were any of his works burned?", "trigger_span": [4393, 4414], "answer_text": "His friend didn't burn his works", "answer_span": [4416.0, 4455.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S68.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4614, "question_text": "Aren't somethings good even incomplete?", "trigger_span": [4575, 4585], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S116.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8146, "question_text": "Can you give examples?", "trigger_span": [8117, 8144], "answer_text": "A deliberate flaw in a pattern in Navajo crafts.", "answer_span": [8149.0, 8163.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "starshade.S33.Q6", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2070, "question_text": "Where did the planet go?", "trigger_span": [1945, 1963], "answer_text": "The planet should be in a red circle.", "answer_span": [2070.0, 2111.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "starshade.S38.Q6", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2141, "question_text": "Is the planet in the circle?", "trigger_span": [2076, 2111], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S40.Q6", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2203, "question_text": "Why is the star's light so bright?", "trigger_span": [2163, 2201], "answer_text": "The light shows up too bright in the telescope.", "answer_span": [2219.0, 2272.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S104.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7399, "question_text": "How does that work?", "trigger_span": [7275, 7303], "answer_text": "It makes us more determined, and tenacious.", "answer_span": [7536.0, 7574.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"]}
{"id": "investment.S30.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2367, "question_text": "What else should investors consider?", "trigger_span": [1895, 1924], "answer_text": "A long term, holistic view like this limits future risk.", "answer_span": [2569.0, 2608.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence", "Explicit:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner"]}
{"id": "investment.S37.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2560, "question_text": "Is one more important than the other?", "trigger_span": [2483, 2530], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S39.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2856, "question_text": "And is it?", "trigger_span": [2816, 2855], "answer_text": "Yes, mostly.", "answer_span": [2892.0, 2905.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S65.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3566, "question_text": "Could that really work?", "trigger_span": [3328, 3366], "answer_text": "No, it doesn't.", "answer_span": [3640.0, 3674.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "starshade.S70.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3676, "question_text": "Did they actually try it?", "trigger_span": [3569, 3616], "answer_text": "They found out light behaves the same around the screen.", "answer_span": [3723.0, 3764.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "starshade.S72.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3886, "question_text": "Is there a solution to that problem?", "trigger_span": [3845, 3884], "answer_text": "If we feather the edges, we control diffraction.", "answer_span": [3977.0, 4001.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond", "EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S74.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3936, "question_text": "Is there any other way?", "trigger_span": [3886, 3908], "answer_text": "There is a way to adapt to correct the problem.", "answer_span": [3940.0, 3972.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S58.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4013, "question_text": "Are we to critical of our own work to judge it?", "trigger_span": [3893, 3918], "answer_text": "He didn't feel good about his own paintings", "answer_span": [4061.0, 4107.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "investment.S41.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2997, "question_text": "Do you have some examples?", "trigger_span": [2892, 2905], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S43.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3229, "question_text": "And what does this mean for the future of business?", "trigger_span": [3146, 3178], "answer_text": "There are opportunities there.", "answer_span": [3261.0, 3309.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "investment.S45.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3311, "question_text": "How can we use that?", "trigger_span": [3261, 3309], "answer_text": "The text is about to tell us.", "answer_span": [3388.0, 3399.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "AltLex:Hypophora"]}
{"id": "investment.S51.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3432, "question_text": "And who is that?", "trigger_span": [3388, 3399], "answer_text": "State Street", "answer_span": [3441.0, 3453.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "AltLex:Hypophora", "AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S97.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7048, "question_text": "What happened as a result, if they were seen as abuses?", "trigger_span": [6793, 6829], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S76.Q2", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4084, "question_text": "How many planets have been found this way?", "trigger_span": [4058, 4082], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S80.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4198, "question_text": "You've been using this method for ten years?", "trigger_span": [4088, 4114], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S84.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4346, "question_text": "So the proper shape is like a flower petal?", "trigger_span": [4201, 4237], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S74.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3936, "question_text": "If there anything that can be done to make a better shadow?", "trigger_span": [3886, 3908], "answer_text": "Control the diffraction by softening the edges.", "answer_span": [4003.0, 4051.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond", "EntRel:nan", "Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S76.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4084, "question_text": "What planet can we see?", "trigger_span": [4058, 4082], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S32.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1885, "question_text": "What planet are you trying to see?", "trigger_span": [1831, 1841], "answer_text": "Seeing a big star", "answer_span": [1989.0, 2018.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S36.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2070, "question_text": "Is it the sun?", "trigger_span": [2026, 2068], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S62.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4837, "question_text": "How will you shake up the seating chart?", "trigger_span": [4796, 4835], "answer_text": "trying to achieve diversity", "answer_span": [5076.0, 5100.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S69.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5102, "question_text": "What should we look at beside race?", "trigger_span": [4886, 4927], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S71.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5400, "question_text": "What are our intractable problems?", "trigger_span": [5174, 5194], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S68.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4614, "question_text": "Are there others who requested their works burned at death?", "trigger_span": [4444, 4455], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S56.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3918, "question_text": "What kind of companies are these that are avoiding the emissions of a 100,000 metric tons of carbon?", "trigger_span": [3804, 3858], "answer_text": "Pentair is one of these companies and it has a water business.", "answer_span": [4109.0, 4123.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Succession", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "investment.S58.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3965, "question_text": "What kind of company is Pentair?", "trigger_span": [3956, 3963], "answer_text": "Pentair is an industrial conglomerate that is in the U.S.", "answer_span": [3965.0, 4006.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S60.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4150, "question_text": "Why was Pentair's reinvesting a really big bet?", "trigger_span": [4125, 4148], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S64.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4350, "question_text": "Do they have anything else planned for the future?", "trigger_span": [4300, 4348], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S68.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4488, "question_text": "What could be \"isolated cases\"?", "trigger_span": [4457, 4487], "answer_text": "Companies that consider sustainability.", "answer_span": [4516.0, 4563.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S112.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7963, "question_text": "Do you have some examples of how we might apply that?", "trigger_span": [7890, 7912], "answer_text": "Creation myths have a deliberate near win built in.", "answer_span": [8092.0, 8144.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S49.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3432, "question_text": "What label?", "trigger_span": [3391, 3398], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S54.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3583, "question_text": "How do you get motivated for that constant pursuit?", "trigger_span": [3479, 3495], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S37.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2113, "question_text": "What is the red circle?", "trigger_span": [2089, 2111], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S126.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9040, "question_text": "Have they ever won?", "trigger_span": [8858, 8867], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S133.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9158, "question_text": "Do they have any ideas they haven't tried?", "trigger_span": [9061, 9081], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S135.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9292, "question_text": "What are they trying to master?", "trigger_span": [9181, 9188], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S137.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9498, "question_text": "Who is Elizabeth Murray?", "trigger_span": [9320, 9336], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S94.Q3", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5172, "question_text": "What is separating from the telescope?", "trigger_span": [4910, 4922], "answer_text": "Something that can cause planets to orbit around itself.", "answer_span": [5185.0, 5210.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "homeless.S29.Q5", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2655, "question_text": "What's their favorite type of produce?", "trigger_span": [2499, 2549], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S35.Q5", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2776, "question_text": "What are the aspects that aren't idyllic?", "trigger_span": [2723, 2775], "answer_text": "freight train injuries", "answer_span": [2873.0, 2901.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S65.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4929, "question_text": "Where is this data from?", "trigger_span": [4578, 4609], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S70.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5252, "question_text": "What country or countries are we talking about here?", "trigger_span": [4963, 5018], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S58.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3965, "question_text": "What is Pentair?", "trigger_span": [3956, 3964], "answer_text": "A large coorperation", "answer_span": [4109.0, 4123.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Succession", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "investment.S60.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4150, "question_text": "Are they still in the water business?", "trigger_span": [4078, 4123], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S64.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4350, "question_text": "What do they mean by the New World?", "trigger_span": [4329, 4347], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S68.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4488, "question_text": "Why are 4 billion people demanding these things?", "trigger_span": [4357, 4422], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S126.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9040, "question_text": "Why can't the coaches keep up?", "trigger_span": [8703, 8747], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S30.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1965, "question_text": "How did you get to Alpha Centauri?", "trigger_span": [1885, 1912], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S106.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7601, "question_text": "How can we use this constructively?", "trigger_span": [7536, 7574], "answer_text": "We do better with a reasonable, achievable challenge than with total success.", "answer_span": [7733.0, 7742.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S108.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7806, "question_text": "Is there anything more we can do to make this work for us?", "trigger_span": [7775, 7804], "answer_text": "Set ourselves up to perceive near wins in our lives.", "answer_span": [7890.0, 7912.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S94.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5172, "question_text": "What separates from the telescope?", "trigger_span": [4910, 4941], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S39.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2163, "question_text": "Why is it hard?", "trigger_span": [2141, 2161], "answer_text": "The light from the star scatters in the telescope and washes out the planet.", "answer_span": [2278.0, 2299.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S41.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2301, "question_text": "Whose telescope is it?", "trigger_span": [2208, 2239], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S43.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2398, "question_text": "How do you get rid of the light?", "trigger_span": [2375, 2396], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S45.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2612, "question_text": "Why is it the coolest?", "trigger_span": [2520, 2542], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S51.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2764, "question_text": "Where was Spitzer from?", "trigger_span": [2619, 2651], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S166.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9399, "question_text": "Why is it something liked?", "trigger_span": [9371, 9382], "answer_text": "Pokes fun at both sides of climate change.", "answer_span": [9431.0, 9454.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "investment.S168.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9484, "question_text": "Why laugh about climate change?", "trigger_span": [9399, 9408], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S170.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9641, "question_text": "Why plan for the future?", "trigger_span": [9619, 9639], "answer_text": "That's where you're going to spend the rest of your life.", "answer_span": [9688.0, 9705.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "starshade.S17.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1291, "question_text": "Do you think we will ever have a telescope in the orbit of Mars?", "trigger_span": [1140, 1153], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S22.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1366, "question_text": "Why did it move there?", "trigger_span": [1342, 1364], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S42.Q6", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2372, "question_text": "How will you dim the light?", "trigger_span": [2331, 2370], "answer_text": "We have technologies to get rid of it.", "answer_span": [2425.0, 2463.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S44.Q6", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2544, "question_text": "Which tech is the coolest?", "trigger_span": [2505, 2542], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S48.Q6", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2742, "question_text": "How will the tech get us an Earth?", "trigger_span": [2557, 2591], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S65.Q6", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4614, "question_text": "Why didn't his friend honor Kafka's request?", "trigger_span": [4416, 4455], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S70.Q6", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4814, "question_text": "How can we master accomplishment?", "trigger_span": [4614, 4636], "answer_text": "You don't master it.", "answer_span": [4912.0, 4956.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "AltLex:Expansion.Substitution.Arg1-as-subst"]}
{"id": "starshade.S24.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1500, "question_text": "What moon, the earth's moon?", "trigger_span": [1444, 1455], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S26.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1599, "question_text": "What is the Kuiper Belt?", "trigger_span": [1556, 1567], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S28.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1689, "question_text": "What's ten times further away?", "trigger_span": [1665, 1687], "answer_text": "The \"Oort Cloud\" is there, outside the solar system.", "answer_span": [1712.0, 1748.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S32.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1885, "question_text": "What's ten times further out?", "trigger_span": [1861, 1883], "answer_text": "Alpha Centauri, the nearest star, is ten times further out.", "answer_span": [1898.0, 1939.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "investment.S5.Q6", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 385, "question_text": "How can we sustain these issues?", "trigger_span": [271, 288], "answer_text": "We shouldn't ignore these issues.", "answer_span": [393.0, 429.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S161.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9365, "question_text": "Performance of what is not being sacrificed?", "trigger_span": [9256, 9279], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S71.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5400, "question_text": "What is the new way we need to think about diversity?", "trigger_span": [5216, 5250], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S73.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5466, "question_text": "What's a city?", "trigger_span": [5450, 5465], "answer_text": "A city is the people and their relationship not the geography and physical features.", "answer_span": [5583.0, 5619.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "cities.S75.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5821, "question_text": "How can we document those relationships correctly?", "trigger_span": [5689, 5717], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S7.Q6", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 489, "question_text": "How will long-term returns be affected?", "trigger_span": [452, 487], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S9.Q6", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 693, "question_text": "How will pensions be affected in the future?", "trigger_span": [625, 663], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S11.Q6", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 842, "question_text": "How can we sustainable invest?", "trigger_span": [708, 749], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S13.Q6", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1017, "question_text": "How will our aging population be affected?", "trigger_span": [892, 932], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S19.Q6", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 1246, "question_text": "How can we replenish resources faster?", "trigger_span": [1020, 1081], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S56.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3777, "question_text": "What's an example of this?", "trigger_span": [3583, 3597], "answer_text": "Murray and Cezanne are both examples.", "answer_span": [3868.0, 3875.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S58.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4013, "question_text": "How many of Cezanne's final painting did he think were incomplete?", "trigger_span": [3946, 3962], "answer_text": "He only signed 10% of his paintings as complete.", "answer_span": [4080.0, 4090.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S60.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4234, "question_text": "What other works did he enjoy?", "trigger_span": [4109, 4127], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S64.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4416, "question_text": "Why wasn't Kafka satisfied?", "trigger_span": [4246, 4262], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S102.Q3", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7271, "question_text": "How so?", "trigger_span": [7237, 7269], "answer_text": "It causes us to focus on a plan.", "answer_span": [7305.0, 7324.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "starshade.S36.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2070, "question_text": "Is Alpha Centauri similar to the sun?", "trigger_span": [1898, 1939], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S62.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4837, "question_text": "What is something we choose to do?", "trigger_span": [4472, 4486], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S69.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5102, "question_text": "What does contribute to our development of diversity?", "trigger_span": [5058, 5100], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S101.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5234, "question_text": "What are the planets orbiting?", "trigger_span": [5178, 5210], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S103.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5321, "question_text": "What is being worked on?", "trigger_span": [5273, 5319], "answer_text": "Possibly a star", "answer_span": [5435.0, 5455.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S62.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4524, "question_text": "When was this novel written?", "trigger_span": [4113, 4159], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S101.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5234, "question_text": "What are the planets orbiting?", "trigger_span": [5185, 5210], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S103.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5321, "question_text": "What have they been working on????", "trigger_span": [5262, 5288], "answer_text": "Looks like they are possibly working on a \"star shade\".", "answer_span": [5425.0, 5455.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S105.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5425, "question_text": "What are the petals?", "trigger_span": [5412, 5423], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S107.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5507, "question_text": "What is a star shade?", "trigger_span": [5445, 5455], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S109.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5623, "question_text": "What is the internship for?", "trigger_span": [5597, 5614], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S73.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5051, "question_text": "What would be an example of this?", "trigger_span": [4912, 4938], "answer_text": "Ben Saunders is an example of mastery.", "answer_span": [5273.0, 5285.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S75.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5211, "question_text": "What would be an example of this?", "trigger_span": [5051, 5094], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S77.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5417, "question_text": "Where was Ben Saunders from?", "trigger_span": [5257, 5285], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S83.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5588, "question_text": "Where was Duke Ellington from?", "trigger_span": [5493, 5507], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S2.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 296, "question_text": "How powerful would the telescope need to be?", "trigger_span": [176, 199], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S61.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4354, "question_text": "What did he want with all the diaries?", "trigger_span": [4324, 4352], "answer_text": "He wanted them burned", "answer_span": [4393.0, 4414.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S67.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4524, "question_text": "Would kafka have been happy with his friends decision?", "trigger_span": [4490, 4522], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S94.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5172, "question_text": "What is moving in front of the star?", "trigger_span": [5088, 5127], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S51.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3864, "question_text": "Is there a lot of interest in drug culture?", "trigger_span": [3847, 3862], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S17.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1134, "question_text": "What turns success into mastery?", "trigger_span": [997, 1026], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S22.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1335, "question_text": "What does being a woman have to do with archery?", "trigger_span": [1230, 1239], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S24.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1608, "question_text": "Does archer's paradox work?", "trigger_span": [1383, 1391], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S26.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1848, "question_text": "How do archers communicate with numbers?", "trigger_span": [1795, 1814], "answer_text": "Numbers and degrees for how to hit their target", "answer_span": [1905.0, 1921.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous", "Explicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S28.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2039, "question_text": "Why would an archer require support?", "trigger_span": [2002, 2020], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S69.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4680, "question_text": "When were these works written?", "trigger_span": [4524, 4563], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S71.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4912, "question_text": "Who was Michelangelo?", "trigger_span": [4736, 4758], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S52.Q6", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2788, "question_text": "How did a solar eclipse inspire this tech?", "trigger_span": [2764, 2786], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S1.Q6", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 223, "question_text": "How is the world changing?", "trigger_span": [75, 121], "answer_text": "Environment, social issues, and corporate matters are changing the world.", "answer_span": [327.0, 383.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S36.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2408, "question_text": "How are points calculated?", "trigger_span": [2295, 2306], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S84.Q6", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5626, "question_text": "How do we know there will be a next one?", "trigger_span": [5567, 5586], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S65.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3566, "question_text": "what would we build?", "trigger_span": [3334, 3346], "answer_text": "A big screen", "answer_span": [3606.0, 3616.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S70.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3676, "question_text": "It there a planet?", "trigger_span": [3609, 3616], "answer_text": "NO", "answer_span": [3865.0, 3884.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S72.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3886, "question_text": "what does bending around a rockin the stream do?", "trigger_span": [3865, 3884], "answer_text": "destroys shadows", "answer_span": [3902.0, 3908.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S74.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3936, "question_text": "How is the shadow", "trigger_span": [3902, 3908], "answer_text": "terrible", "answer_span": [4076.0, 4082.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S102.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7271, "question_text": "Describe TED", "trigger_span": [7234, 7269], "answer_text": "mountain is on our side", "answer_span": [7375.0, 7397.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S37.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2560, "question_text": " ESG is a measure of?", "trigger_span": [2441, 2455], "answer_text": "sustainabilty", "answer_span": [2593.0, 2603.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence", "Explicit:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner"]}
{"id": "investment.S39.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2856, "question_text": "how does it limit future risk?", "trigger_span": [2593, 2618], "answer_text": "maximixing harm to people", "answer_span": [2927.0, 2941.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S41.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2997, "question_text": "what did they start to see", "trigger_span": [2927, 2941], "answer_text": "sustainibility", "answer_span": [3142.0, 3156.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "investment.S43.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3229, "question_text": "how many percent of company sees ESG as the future?", "trigger_span": [3146, 3156], "answer_text": "93%", "answer_span": [3295.0, 3309.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "starshade.S76.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4084, "question_text": "what happens when you feather edges", "trigger_span": [4032, 4051], "answer_text": "controls diffraction ", "answer_span": [4103.0, 4108.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S80.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4198, "question_text": "when did we come up with optimal solutions for that", "trigger_span": [4100, 4108], "answer_text": "10 years", "answer_span": [4333.0, 4344.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S84.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4346, "question_text": "What can we control", "trigger_span": [4333, 4344], "answer_text": "Diffraction", "answer_span": [4389.0, 4405.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "cities.S37.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2917, "question_text": "Leads to what things?", "trigger_span": [2890, 2905], "answer_text": "Everything is mixed up", "answer_span": [3308.0, 3324.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S104.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7399, "question_text": "what does a near win do?", "trigger_span": [7370, 7397], "answer_text": "gets us to focus", "answer_span": [7564.0, 7599.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S106.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7601, "question_text": "who needed to fol low up in the competition", "trigger_span": [7542, 7567], "answer_text": "Jackie", "answer_span": [7736.0, 7770.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S108.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7806, "question_text": "when do we strive?", "trigger_span": [7775, 7804], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S112.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7963, "question_text": "what were you wondering", "trigger_span": [7927, 7961], "answer_text": "how to manufacture a near win in the room", "answer_span": [8092.0, 8144.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "investment.S45.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3311, "question_text": "Is there an opportunity in sustainibility ", "trigger_span": [3261, 3291], "answer_text": "yes", "answer_span": [3341.0, 3387.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"]}
{"id": "investment.S51.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3432, "question_text": "Are companies leveraging to hard disk business result?", "trigger_span": [3403, 3430], "answer_text": "yes", "answer_span": [3441.0, 3478.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "AltLex:Hypophora", "AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S97.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 7048, "question_text": "why does the near win have propultion?", "trigger_span": [6910, 6943], "answer_text": "because it canges our view of landscape and puts our goals", "answer_span": [7142.0, 7155.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "cities.S39.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3131, "question_text": "What does the map show?", "trigger_span": [3103, 3119], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S41.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3326, "question_text": "What about Rio is mixed up?", "trigger_span": [3270, 3279], "answer_text": "Heterogeneous city", "answer_span": [3333.0, 3355.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "cities.S43.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3499, "question_text": "Why does a heterogeneous city equate being mixed up?", "trigger_span": [3432, 3447], "answer_text": "The range of interests here range far and wide.", "answer_span": [3707.0, 3723.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "cities.S45.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3679, "question_text": "What different kinds of music are people interested in?", "trigger_span": [3653, 3677], "answer_text": "Fan bases for a variety of music located here.", "answer_span": [3698.0, 3723.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S72.Q6", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 4958, "question_text": "Why can we never arrive at mastery?", "trigger_span": [4912, 4956], "answer_text": "Mastery is about trying to accomplish something beyond you, so there will always be a gap.", "answer_span": [4966.0, 5002.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S74.Q6", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5141, "question_text": "How do you sacrifice your craft?", "trigger_span": [5051, 5094], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S76.Q6", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5368, "question_text": "What are some of Ben Saunders' triumphs?", "trigger_span": [5305, 5317], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S80.Q6", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5465, "question_text": "How do we stay at the leading edge?", "trigger_span": [5432, 5463], "answer_text": "Always look ahead to your next piece that is not yet created.", "answer_span": [5588.0, 5624.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S115.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5692, "question_text": "How do the petals rotate?", "trigger_span": [5652, 5690], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S49.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3532, "question_text": "What is ESG?", "trigger_span": [3352, 3355], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S72.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5447, "question_text": "What interventions are suggested?", "trigger_span": [5264, 5307], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S74.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 5651, "question_text": "Can you give an example of that relationship?", "trigger_span": [5595, 5633], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S133.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9158, "question_text": "What would the former self be?", "trigger_span": [9141, 9156], "answer_text": "Improving oneself for the future.", "answer_span": [9190.0, 9233.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S135.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9292, "question_text": "What is being achieved?", "trigger_span": [9247, 9290], "answer_text": "A general term for completing.", "answer_span": [9498.0, 9518.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S137.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9498, "question_text": "What is incomplete?", "trigger_span": [9462, 9497], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S32.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2220, "question_text": "How does an archer hit such a small target?", "trigger_span": [2168, 2193], "answer_text": "She had more tenacity after missing", "answer_span": [2423.0, 2445.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "starshade.S115.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5692, "question_text": "Where are they deploying?", "trigger_span": [5634, 5650], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S49.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3532, "question_text": "What results are needed?", "trigger_span": [3356, 3387], "answer_text": "Seems that automation was integrated.", "answer_span": [3599.0, 3627.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "AltLex:Hypophora", "AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S54.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3800, "question_text": "How does the mobile workplace work?", "trigger_span": [3660, 3681], "answer_text": "Going to infer that people are working from home, instead of driving to an office or location.", "answer_span": [3871.0, 3917.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation", "AltLex:Expansion.Equivalence"]}
{"id": "investment.S56.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3918, "question_text": "Why do the emissions need reduced?", "trigger_span": [3804, 3858], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S6.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 625, "question_text": "Are there more planets than we currently think there are?", "trigger_span": [477, 514], "answer_text": "haven't seen them...only detected them indirectly", "answer_span": [658.0, 693.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"]}
{"id": "starshade.S8.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 695, "question_text": "How many planets do you think there are?", "trigger_span": [629, 656], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S10.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 922, "question_text": "Are there other pictures like this?", "trigger_span": [710, 745], "answer_text": "I want to take more photos...why haven't we?", "answer_span": [986.0, 1011.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "starshade.S105.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5425, "question_text": "What are the four petals?", "trigger_span": [5402, 5423], "answer_text": "Is it a star?", "answer_span": [5435.0, 5455.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "cities.S56.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4211, "question_text": "What's the significance of this data?", "trigger_span": [4185, 4209], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S58.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4369, "question_text": "What exactly can we do with the data?", "trigger_span": [4342, 4368], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S60.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4578, "question_text": "How does the data back up this claim?", "trigger_span": [4437, 4470], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S64.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4772, "question_text": "What can we conclude from looking at this?", "trigger_span": [4711, 4770], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S12.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1012, "question_text": "Is it possible to take more photos like this?", "trigger_span": [932, 965], "answer_text": "take the Hubble....turn it around and move it....", "answer_span": [1057.0, 1091.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "AltLex:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond"]}
{"id": "starshade.S16.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1155, "question_text": "Would you be able to photograph Mars?", "trigger_span": [1118, 1153], "answer_text": "...a slightly blurry picture of the Earth", "answer_span": [1155.0, 1184.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "starshade.S107.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5507, "question_text": "Who is seeing?", "trigger_span": [5485, 5505], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S109.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5623, "question_text": "Where did they build?", "trigger_span": [5560, 5588], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S33.Q5", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2831, "question_text": "Who makes these sacrifices?", "trigger_span": [2551, 2565], "answer_text": "The homeless", "answer_span": [3002.0, 3010.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "homeless.S38.Q5", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3154, "question_text": "What is a homeless person to do?", "trigger_span": [2961, 2984], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S40.Q5", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3233, "question_text": "What good are these laws?", "trigger_span": [3222, 3232], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S20.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1291, "question_text": "But can you photograph the other planets?", "trigger_span": [1188, 1224], "answer_text": "here we are...at Uranus", "answer_span": [1342.0, 1364.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "cities.S46.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3864, "question_text": "What exactly is TEDxRio?", "trigger_span": [3499, 3533], "answer_text": "multicultural, musically diverse city", "answer_span": [4139.0, 4183.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"]}
{"id": "cities.S53.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3944, "question_text": "How does football tie into TEDxRio?", "trigger_span": [3891, 3942], "answer_text": "sports, civics, arts, and music", "answer_span": [3974.0, 4024.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"]}
{"id": "cities.S55.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4185, "question_text": "Are current events included?", "trigger_span": [4035, 4070], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S57.Q4", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4342, "question_text": "What do you do with this data?", "trigger_span": [4216, 4246], "answer_text": "understand that segregation is a social construct", "answer_span": [4418.0, 4470.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora"]}
{"id": "investment.S30.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2367, "question_text": "give one example of what environment causes", "trigger_span": [2023, 2041], "answer_text": "energy consumption", "answer_span": [2441.0, 2455.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "homeless.S44.Q5", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3702, "question_text": "Why not seek help?", "trigger_span": [3658, 3681], "answer_text": "Freedom", "answer_span": [3702.0, 3709.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "homeless.S46.Q5", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3826, "question_text": "Is there dignity in homelessness?", "trigger_span": [3759, 3774], "answer_text": "Dignity in freedom by escape", "answer_span": [3921.0, 3936.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "homeless.S48.Q5", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3982, "question_text": "Homelessness is rebellion from what?", "trigger_span": [3971, 3980], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S30.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2859, "question_text": "Why are these communities at odds?", "trigger_span": [2779, 2803], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S116.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5791, "question_text": "what happens if they're off by a millimeter?", "trigger_span": [5759, 5789], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S48.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3262, "question_text": "Did she win the competition?", "trigger_span": [3218, 3260], "answer_text": "Mastery is not the same as success", "answer_span": [3262.0, 3304.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S52.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3432, "question_text": "Was she a master?", "trigger_span": [3262, 3304], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S134.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9190, "question_text": "what is the idea?", "trigger_span": [9099, 9118], "answer_text": "it's vague, but coming close to what you thought you wanted", "answer_span": [9190.0, 9233.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S136.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9424, "question_text": "what are you trying to obtain?", "trigger_span": [9238, 9258], "answer_text": "a utopia?", "answer_span": [9443.0, 9450.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "AltLex:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond"]}
{"id": "investment.S62.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4424, "question_text": "what is the specific bet?", "trigger_span": [4134, 4148], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S69.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4513, "question_text": "what are the isolated cases related to?", "trigger_span": [4467, 4487], "answer_text": "companies taking sustainability into account doing alright financially.", "answer_span": [4536.0, 4591.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S71.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4633, "question_text": "why wouldn't being sustainable be profitable?", "trigger_span": [4596, 4631], "answer_text": "ESG performance performs just as well as others", "answer_span": [4665.0, 4718.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S73.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4752, "question_text": "what is MSCI World?", "trigger_span": [4740, 4750], "answer_text": "an index of large companies from developed markets", "answer_span": [4760.0, 4824.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S75.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4910, "question_text": "are these companies the most sustainable?", "trigger_span": [4888, 4908], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg1-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg1-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S68.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4929, "question_text": "How does the data help us realize this?", "trigger_span": [4886, 4927], "answer_text": "Race is not the only variable we should be looking at", "answer_span": [5022.0, 5068.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S138.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9553, "question_text": "what is incomplete?", "trigger_span": [9471, 9496], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S14.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1226, "question_text": "Why would we do that anyway?", "trigger_span": [1096, 1132], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S21.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1330, "question_text": "What do we see now?", "trigger_span": [1291, 1328], "answer_text": "We see less detail", "answer_span": [1366.0, 1421.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S23.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1423, "question_text": "Will we go further?", "trigger_span": [1330, 1364], "answer_text": "We went 10 times further", "answer_span": [1457.0, 1498.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S25.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1569, "question_text": "What do we see from the Kuiper Belt?", "trigger_span": [1545, 1567], "answer_text": "It's completely unclear now", "answer_span": [1569.0, 1597.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Synchronous"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Temporal.Synchronous"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "AltLex:Temporal.Synchronous"]}
{"id": "investment.S77.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4981, "question_text": "these companies don't sacrifice anything for a better ESG performance?", "trigger_span": [4933, 4956], "answer_text": "maybe the companies sacrifice less climate change strategies", "answer_span": [5162.0, 5217.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"]}
{"id": "investment.S83.Q4", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5008, "question_text": "more what, companies with better ESG scores?", "trigger_span": [4981, 4993], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S129.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9083, "question_text": "what kind of team is this?", "trigger_span": [8737, 8747], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S102.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5262, "question_text": "what's not science fiction?", "trigger_span": [5234, 5260], "answer_text": "the petals unfurling on a sub-scale star shade.", "answer_span": [5412.0, 5423.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S104.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5399, "question_text": "what was tested?", "trigger_span": [5341, 5359], "answer_text": "a sub-scale star shade.", "answer_span": [5435.0, 5455.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S106.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5457, "question_text": "what does it actually do, though?", "trigger_span": [5425, 5429], "answer_text": "the petals unfurl.", "answer_span": [5522.0, 5535.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "starshade.S27.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1640, "question_text": "What is this pale blue dot?", "trigger_span": [1599, 1638], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S29.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1846, "question_text": "What do we see if we move further?", "trigger_span": [1780, 1811], "answer_text": "We don't see the planet at all anymore", "answer_span": [1941.0, 1963.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S35.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 1965, "question_text": "Now what?", "trigger_span": [1846, 1883], "answer_text": "We don't move further, all we see is the sun", "answer_span": [1975.0, 2018.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "cities.S49.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 3882, "question_text": "Represented where?", "trigger_span": [3703, 3723], "answer_text": "Rio", "answer_span": [4126.0, 4183.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"]}
{"id": "cities.S54.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 4072, "question_text": "How is it represented differently?", "trigger_span": [4026, 4070], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S42.Q5", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3483, "question_text": "Why choose homelessness?", "trigger_span": [3418, 3441], "answer_text": "Freedom", "answer_span": [3702.0, 3709.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "starshade.S108.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5537, "question_text": "what's the size?", "trigger_span": [5468, 5481], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan", "AltLex:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S112.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5652, "question_text": "what does deploying it do?", "trigger_span": [5634, 5650], "answer_text": "the petals rotate into place and unfurl.", "answer_span": [5658.0, 5690.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S40.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2683, "question_text": "What happened next?", "trigger_span": [2581, 2624], "answer_text": "what doggedness looks like...this level of exactitude", "answer_span": [2827.0, 2864.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S42.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 2896, "question_text": "Did she continue in the same fashion?", "trigger_span": [2739, 2771], "answer_text": "author stayed to watch more", "answer_span": [3023.0, 3035.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S44.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 3036, "question_text": "What happened next?", "trigger_span": [3023, 3035], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S116.Q4", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8146, "question_text": "why do they deliberate ", "trigger_span": [8045, 8073], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S97.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 5212, "question_text": "what's going to move?", "trigger_span": [5088, 5092], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S42.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3142, "question_text": "Why do 20 percent of CEOs not see it as a tool?", "trigger_span": [3003, 3013], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Contrast"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S44.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3261, "question_text": "Why is ESG the future but not the present?", "trigger_span": [3157, 3178], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Equivalence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S48.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3388, "question_text": "How are they using ESG to get results?", "trigger_span": [3341, 3387], "answer_text": "They used it to save 23 million dollars annually.", "answer_span": [3741.0, 3770.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "AltLex:Hypophora", "AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation", "AltLex:Contingency.Cause.Result", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"]}
{"id": "investment.S52.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 3532, "question_text": "What does it mean to migrate applications to the cloud?", "trigger_span": [3466, 3503], "answer_text": "They virtualized portions of their work.", "answer_span": [3535.0, 3580.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "AltLex:Hypophora", "AltLex:Expansion.Instantiation", "Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S75.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4910, "question_text": "What companies does it consist of?", "trigger_span": [4760, 4784], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg1-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg1-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S77.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 4981, "question_text": "Three years plus what?", "trigger_span": [4910, 4931], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S83.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 5008, "question_text": "What more do you want?", "trigger_span": [4995, 5006], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S129.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 9083, "question_text": "What more would they like to be doing?", "trigger_span": [8703, 8747], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S157.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9127, "question_text": "What are the two things they are doing by investing sustainable? ", "trigger_span": [9081, 9125], "answer_text": "They are helping the planet and economy while also being able to make money ", "answer_span": [9153.0, 9203.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"]}
{"id": "investment.S163.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9281, "question_text": "How is performance not scarified? ", "trigger_span": [9246, 9279], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S110.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8014, "question_text": "What would be a near win?", "trigger_span": [7902, 7912], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S117.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8255, "question_text": "What type of imperfections?", "trigger_span": [8209, 8228], "answer_text": "A deliberate flaw.", "answer_span": [8289.0, 8306.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S119.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8404, "question_text": "What does it mean for the worker to have a way out?", "trigger_span": [8344, 8359], "answer_text": "To keep working.", "answer_span": [8479.0, 8507.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S121.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8479, "question_text": "Why are masters experts?", "trigger_span": [8404, 8427], "answer_text": "They realize there isn't a conceptual end.", "answer_span": [8508.0, 8536.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S123.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 8538, "question_text": "Why isn't their a conceptual end?", "trigger_span": [8487, 8507], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S40.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2907, "question_text": "Why do CEO's care?", "trigger_span": [2897, 2905], "answer_text": "They see it as crucial to success.", "answer_span": [2968.0, 2995.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "starshade.S55.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3008, "question_text": "Did you not know that we are not supposed to look at the eclipse without protection for our eyes?", "trigger_span": [2991, 3006], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S57.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3062, "question_text": "Who are you talking about?", "trigger_span": [3014, 3021], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S59.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3249, "question_text": "Why is the dim part so important?", "trigger_span": [3235, 3247], "answer_text": "The dim part would be the shadow where the telescope would be placed.", "answer_span": [3468.0, 3489.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "starshade.S61.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 3325, "question_text": "What would this achieve?", "trigger_span": [3304, 3323], "answer_text": "The shadow or dim part would serve for the telescope to be placed there in order for us to see planets.", "answer_span": [3444.0, 3489.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S83.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 5588, "question_text": "Does this lead to a loss of satisfaction?", "trigger_span": [5563, 5586], "answer_text": "You can't know your potential without pushing yourself; that itself is satisfying.", "answer_span": [5729.0, 5750.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"]}
{"id": "investment.S151.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8675, "question_text": "Why is the quote from JFK spot on?", "trigger_span": [8484, 8538], "answer_text": "the author is saying that there may be risk in doing something,but more risk in not doing anything,which is what JFK said", "answer_span": [8989.0, 9026.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan"]}
{"id": "investment.S153.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 8918, "question_text": "What is the estimated risk?", "trigger_span": [8697, 8729], "answer_text": "investing in sustainability ", "answer_span": [9081.0, 9102.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Exception.Arg2-as-excpt"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Manner.Arg2-as-manner", "Explicit:Temporal.Synchronous"]}
{"id": "investment.S155.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 9068, "question_text": "Why not if you live in boston? ", "trigger_span": [8924, 8955], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S78.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4239, "question_text": "What are you trying to see by controlling diffraction?", "trigger_span": [4063, 4082], "answer_text": "Planets", "answer_span": [4448.0, 4459.0], "answer_score": 5.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S85.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4378, "question_text": "What purpose does the shadow serve?", "trigger_span": [4350, 4376], "answer_text": "Dimmer shadow means planets stand out", "answer_span": [4437.0, 4468.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "starshade.S87.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4534, "question_text": "What size are the planets normally?", "trigger_span": [4512, 4532], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S89.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4728, "question_text": "What is the size of the starshade?", "trigger_span": [4539, 4591], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S91.Q5", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 4910, "question_text": "Where does it go after the hub?", "trigger_span": [4878, 4908], "answer_text": "Separates from the telescope", "answer_span": [4913.0, 4941.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"]}
{"id": "homeless.S25.Q5", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 2068, "question_text": "How old is the average traveler? ", "trigger_span": [1991, 2029], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S46.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2764, "question_text": "What is the technology that you are talking about?", "trigger_span": [2499, 2514], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["EntRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "starshade.S53.Q4", "source_id": "starshade", "source_cutoff": 2828, "question_text": "How did the eclipse inspire him?", "trigger_span": [2779, 2786], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S22.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1916, "question_text": "What is the other community?", "trigger_span": [1877, 1914], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S24.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2021, "question_text": "How does the situation differ in San Francisco?", "trigger_span": [1972, 2019], "answer_text": "Geeks/techies taking over upper half of network", "answer_span": [2219.0, 2258.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Level-of-detail.Arg2-as-detail", "Explicit:Comparison.Contrast", "Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "investment.S33.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2415, "question_text": "Why does governance relate to oversight?", "trigger_span": [2287, 2322], "answer_text": "Because governance is the measure of sustainability.", "answer_span": [2419.0, 2455.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "investment.S38.Q5", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 2730, "question_text": "Why is does sustainability help outcomes?", "trigger_span": [2693, 2703], "answer_text": "The private sector is paying attention.", "answer_span": [2823.0, 2855.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+SpeechAct.Result+SpeechAct"]}
{"id": "homeless.S39.Q5", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3209, "question_text": "Why would it be illegal to offer food to a stranger?", "trigger_span": [3180, 3208], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S41.Q5", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3370, "question_text": "Has the author been cited/hauled to jail for similar \"crimes\"?", "trigger_span": [3269, 3308], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S43.Q5", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3574, "question_text": "Why would people want to live this way?", "trigger_span": [3401, 3441], "answer_text": "Freedom", "answer_span": [3658.0, 3709.0], "answer_score": 4.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["AltLex:Hypophora", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"]}
{"id": "homeless.S45.Q5", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3711, "question_text": "Freedom from what or to do what?", "trigger_span": [3702, 3709], "answer_text": "to be sure of being able to live well and with dignity through work", "answer_span": [3798.0, 3824.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["NoRel:nan"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Condition.Arg2-as-cond", "NoRel:nan", "Explicit:Contingency.Purpose.Arg2-as-goal", "Implicit:Contingency.Purpose.Arg2-as-goal"]}
{"id": "homeless.S47.Q5", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 3938, "question_text": "How can we create this society?", "trigger_span": [3720, 3774], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S17.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 1666, "question_text": "What are the two communities?", "trigger_span": [1593, 1636], "answer_text": "Baltimore is one", "answer_span": [1678.0, 1717.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "investment.S129.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7496, "question_text": "What's an institutional investor?", "trigger_span": [7335, 7358], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["AltLex:Expansion.Substitution.Arg2-as-subst"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S134.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7578, "question_text": "Did they make the money in the stock market?", "trigger_span": [7528, 7547], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "investment.S136.Q3", "source_id": "investment", "source_cutoff": 7645, "question_text": "What's a global bond market?", "trigger_span": [7582, 7600], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Comparison.Similarity"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S26.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2260, "question_text": "Who or what is the network being referred to ?", "trigger_span": [2235, 2258], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S28.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2461, "question_text": "How are the network and the hip-hop spectrum related?", "trigger_span": [2423, 2459], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Contingency.Cause+Belief.Result+Belief", "Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "cities.S32.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2745, "question_text": "How have the effects of gentrification been documented?", "trigger_span": [2719, 2743], "answer_text": "Looking at relationships between geeks and LGBT/arts/music communities", "answer_span": [2761.0, 2803.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Explicit:Comparison.Concession.Arg2-as-denier", "Implicit:Expansion.Instantiation"]}
{"id": "cities.S36.Q5", "source_id": "cities", "source_cutoff": 2880, "question_text": "Is it that the geeks don't get along with the arts/music folks or is the LGBT community not getting along with them?", "trigger_span": [2813, 2868], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction", "Explicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S14.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1070, "question_text": "What is the answer to converting success into mastery?", "trigger_span": [981, 1026], "answer_text": "Valuing the \"near win\"", "answer_span": [1104.0, 1132.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["Implicit:Expansion.Conjunction"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S21.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1263, "question_text": "How did the archers help understanding?", "trigger_span": [1198, 1228], "answer_text": "Examining the \"archer's paradox\"", "answer_span": [1337.0, 1381.0], "answer_score": 3.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": [], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": ["EntRel:nan"]}
{"id": "nearwin.S23.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1487, "question_text": "How does the archer's paradox relate to mastery?", "trigger_span": [1337, 1381], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Result"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S25.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1703, "question_text": "How is the ice cream important here?", "trigger_span": [1608, 1644], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Explicit:Expansion.Conjunction"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "nearwin.S27.Q5", "source_id": "nearwin", "source_cutoff": 1923, "question_text": "How does this relate to mastery?", "trigger_span": [1868, 1921], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 1.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Temporal.Asynchronous.Precedence"], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
{"id": "homeless.S2.Q3", "source_id": "homeless", "source_cutoff": 239, "question_text": "Why did she want to run away?", "trigger_span": [105, 121], "answer_text": null, "answer_span": null, "answer_score": 2.0, "snippet_has_arg1_of": ["Implicit:Contingency.Cause.Reason"], "trigger_has_arg1_of": [], "answer_has_arg2_of": []}
